Morty's on Jessica's Instagram again.
Get out of here, jerk!
What's so embarrassing, Morty?
Sharing it with your family might help.
Summer, stop shaming your brother.
Morty, stop being a creepy,
perverted cyberstalker.
I'm not cyberstalking!
I-I-I just wanted to know where
she got this necklace from.
And now I know.
Her... Her... Her grandma left it to her.
You're quiet, Rick.
Shouldn't you be revealing
grandmas aren't real?
Hi. I've placed an auto-response
chip in my brain
so I can spend time with my family.
But you are spending time
with your family.
Thank you for talking to Rick.
Alright, I'm finished with my breakfast
and my Amazon wish list.
Let's go, Morty.
I need death crystals
from Forbodulon Prime.
Uh...
Dad?
There's a way we do this now.
Morty, would you please accompany me
to Forbodulon Prime for death crystals?
Well, thank you for asking.
Yes, I will do that.
It is a hot photo.
I think grief flushes your cheeks.
Dad, you hardly put any syrup on.
Honey, stop raising
your father's cholesterol
so you can take a hot funeral selfie.
I never get to do anything.
Uh, Rick, maybe if we go a little...
Faster?
Good idea, Morty.
It'll get us through these
asteroids sooner.
Geez, you're really this pissed
about my mom making sure
I'm okay with our adventures?
What's next, Morty?
What if I want you to jump off
the Empire State Building?
- I have to ask?
- Yes?
And you seriously don't see how
that's a slippery slope?
Just shut up and help me
with these, please.
Why are they called death crystals?
D-Do they kill you?
You're thinking of bullets, Morty.
Death crystals show you
how you're gonna die.
Jesus Christ!
I-I die a million times?
Your future stems from your present,
which, if you're living right,
keeps changing.
Truth is, anyone that knows how
they're definitely gonna die
is either boring as hell
or about to get shot.
Duck!
Who are those guys?!
Crystal poachers.
There's no lower form of life.
They think the galaxy's
their own personal piggy bank.
Wait, then what are we?
We're Rick and Morty.
You're about to witness the only
real use for these crystals.
They show you when
the other guy's reloading.
Certain death, certain death,
certain death, uncertain death.
And certain death,
certain death, certain death.
Definitely gonna get shot by this guy;
This is totally my fate;
Nothing I could possibly do;
Okay, now, not so much.
Help me gather these up.
You just use these to win fights?
I don't use them.
People that spend their life
avoiding death are already dead.
They're also rich, and I like to
spend my life with their money.
- Oh, my God.
- Morty!
Jessica!
Oh!
I love you.
Oh! Whoa! Whoa!
- Morty.
- Oh! Oh! Oh!
I love you.
Jessica.
I want to die with Jessica.
- Ahh!
- What are you doing?
- Oh, um, c-can I drive?
- Why?
The... feel of the open road?
Alright!
Who's this grandson?
I like his style.
Morty, you know outer space is up, right?
Yeah, yeah. I'm just, uh,
following... my... instincts.
- Will you just go up?
- Stop!
You're gonna make me die wrong!
Wait a minute, what?
Morty, do you have
a death crystal in your pocket?
- No! Maybe!
- You little monster!
I thought you were masturbating!
And you took that in stride?!
You'd rather I address it?!
Why would I be doing it?!
Why would you steal a death crystal?!
I want to die old!
Then stop driving!
- No!
- You son of a bitch!
Give me the wheel, Morty.
Goddamn it.
Ohhh, shit.
Oh, shit, oh, shit, oh, shit, oh, shit.
I love you, Morty.
I will avenge my death.
- Holy shit!
- Just kidding.
I'm a crisis detection
and correction hologram
generated by a chip that
"real" Rick put in your spine.
"Real" in quotes because calling
density-privileged entities
"real" is incredibly holo-phobic.
Morty, do me a solid...
Problematic wordplay aside...
Grab the gun with the blue
handle from the trunk
and get a tissue sample from the corpse.
Alright, now take that to the trunk
and insert it into the clone compiler.
I see you appear to be holding
a death crystal
that's guiding your decisions
more than I am.
That's your right.
I just want to remind you that
some people can't hold anything
and can never die, so that's
a little offensive to
Oh, okay.
Listen, I'm programmed
for tolerance, Morty.
So I'm willing to accept
that you're doing this
if you're willing to accept
that you need to stop.
Accepting.
Rerouted.
Backup. Data.
Operation. Phoenix. Initiated.
What the hell?
I axed this protocol.
What are you doing with my clone?
It's okay. I'm you.
I took my own clone vat offline
a couple seasons ago,
so I think my backup got
rerouted to your universe.
- I'm sorry.
- All good. Happy to help.
By the way, annoying
that I even have to ask,
but you are down with
fascist dystopias, right?
YYYYYes.
That "yes" was pretty
liberal
with the letter "Y."
Well, isn't this strange.
I trust, the kind of strange
that makes Rick and Morty
stronger.
Morty, I caught this socialist
in my bathrobe.
He wants to give all of our martinis
to a family of immigrants.
Obviously, the most likely impostor
- is the wet, naked clone.
- It is obvious.
But it won't be to the police.
- Ohh!
- 'Kay.
He was an inferior Rick.
He was too political.
I want to have fun, classic
Rick-and-Morty adventures
like in the old days.
Then we'll get along fine, Fascist Morty.
For starters, I just need to get
to Forbodulon Prime...
You will go where I want you to go!!
Fuck.
Hey, hey! Ho, ho!
Not cloning your grandpa has got to go!
You don't get out of my face,
I'm gonna flush Rick's DNA.
Alright.
Okay, regroup, everybody.
You, too, Berkeley!
Snap out of it.
At least tell me what this death is
that you're so determined to...
Oh. Jessica.
Morty, I love...
What?! No, no!
No, no, no!
I love you.
Damn it!
How am I gonna die with her
if I can't even talk to her?
Here's an idea, Morty.
Throw that thing in the garbage,
stop planning your own death,
and talk to whoever you want.
Now you just sound like Real Rick.
You're better than that language, Morty.
I ain't better than shit, Jack.
So, uh, w-what are we doing?
Stop asking questions.
Stop doing meta-commentary.
Just have fun.
We're going on a simple,
fun, classic adventure.
Okay, you know what?
It would really help
if you could just say anything
other than what you don't want.
I like Mr. Meeseeks.
Okay, now we're talking.
You know what?
I usually keep a Meeseeks box
in my glove compartment,
so maybe Fascist Rick does, too.
Ah!
Well, look at that.
Now we're doing something
we've done before.
I'm Mr. Meeseeks!
Kill this Nazi prick!
Can do!
- Come here, you son of a bitch!
- No! Stop!
Accepting. Rerouted.
Backup. Data.
Operation. Phoenix. Initiated.
Aw, come on, man.
Whoa, are you okay?
Yeah, sorry.
I'm a Rick from another reality.
I-I got uploaded to your clone vat.
Hey, don't worry about it, man.
I have a dozen.
W-W-What the heck, Rick?
Are you making clones down here?
Get outta here, Morty!
Stop asking stupid questions, Morty!
You sound like a piece of shit.
Aw, geez.
So, tell the truth, man.
No shame.
You're looking at
your shrimp body like "What?!"
Ah, is it that obvious?
I'm sorry.
Yeah, my original body is more
bipedal... uh, ape-descended.
Really! Weird.
Does your house look like a tree, or...
No, it looks like this.
It's, like, identical to this, actually.
That is such a mind-fuck.
It's all good, man.
I'm fine with it.
Honestly, you're doing me a huge favor
by being shrimp instead of fascists.
What?
Goddamn it!
When did this shit become the default?!
Who wants to come up to the board
and show me some basic-ass integers?
- I love you, Morty.
- Aah!
Morty?
Yeah, right.
That's not an integer!
Apparently, it doesn't matter.
Damn, Morty, you're bad at math,
but I'm giving you
an A-plus in confidence.
Just doin' what I gotta do.
Extra credit!
I love you, Morty.
What's with the strut?
- You think you own this school?
- Nope!
What if I killed you?
Would you be strutting then?
Only if the events of the Pixar
movie "Coco" are to be believed,
which I doubt.
I have it on good authority
that you're probably not gonna kill me.
So why don't you do what I do
and just go with the flow,
nice and Zen, baby.
Aah! Ugh! Ugh! Ugh!
Ugh! Impotence!
Aah! Impotent rage!
Ugh! Ugh! Ugh!
You die tomorrow, no matter what.
It's what bullies call
a "fait accompli."
- Oh, man! Oh, shit!
- Well, well, well. Mm.
Looks like you got yourself in
a lick of trouble, huh, Morty?
Okay, okay, look, if you help me not die,
I'll bring Rick back to life.
Why are you pretending to eat chicken?
Excuse me?
This chicken is quite real to me.
Yeah, okay, but it doesn't have...
- Nutrients?
- Yeah.
What's the last thing you ate?
Baloney and an orange.
So, no holographic foods?
So, to me, you never ate?
Or we could try respecting each other.
Will you just show me how to stay alive?
Alright, Morty, a deal's a deal.
Once we bring your Rick back to life,
then I'll help you with the bully.
Go ahead and open the hatch
to the subterranean lab.
That's where all
the cloning equipment is.
Please tell me you're not
hitting that crystal again.
Look, Rick might be the epitome
of bloated flesh privilege,
but he's right about one thing.
You're gonna be a lot happier
if you focus on the moment,
rather than on how you're gonna die.
I mean, w-who's worried about that, huh?
Sorry, Hologram Rick.
I'm going with the crystal on this one.
Morty.
Oh, alright, okay.
Just because I can't interact
with solid matter
means you can just walk all over me?
Dear God.
Bist du faschistisch?
Nope.
Finally.
I thought maybe you were pussying out.
Hyah!
What the fuck?
Oh, the air's getting thin!
Well, well, well, looks like
there's a new bully in town!
Lucky for us, he just made
bully-bullying the new bullying!
Bully him!
Aah!
We've got an Akira-type
situation going on
behind the mall.
Over.
Dying with Jessica...
Hey!
What the hell?
Aah! Aah!
I'm Mr. Meeseeks!
Look at me!
Shield me from the law!
- Yes, sir! Can do!
- Stand down!
Look at me!
I... will... die... old!
Up next, an unstoppable
science-fiction boy
is attacking our nation's
final line of defense.
Will we all fall to his deadly touch?
But first, something silly?
What do you mean, "but first"?
I already said "up next."
You always do this.
I don't always do shit.
Don't gaslight me.
Gaslighting doesn't exist.
You made it up
'cause you're fucking crazy.
Why are you letting me do this?
I do as the crystal guides.
Your Honor, my client was acting
in self-defense.
He turned 13 men into piles of ash.
Sit down!
Before I sentence you,
is there anything
you have to say for yourself?
I... w-w-will a-al-sways...
Always r-r-remember o-our...
Our... our... v-v-t-time...
Time
i-in... f-g-g-g-P-P-Peru.
I will always remember our time
in Peru, Your Honor.
Your Honor,
as you can see, my client
is speaking nonsense.
Stop.
Those were my husband's last words.
He says that he... I-loves you
ttt-llll-lit-lit-little... little
ff-gg-sp-spa-ffggarrow...
Sparrow!
He loves you, little sparrow.
He's innocent.
Case dismissed.
I'm coming for you, Condor!
Well, I, for one, will not be
accepting this verdict.
And this little monster may
think he's gotten away,
but there is something called
the court of public opinion
that still has final say in this country.
Oh, I guess he's coming out
of the courthouse now.
Let's go live to that.
People, I gotta tell you something.
That little boy...
I thought I knew everything
about everything.
But something about the tones
and frequencies
that just came out of his mouth
have made me...
I mean, I think we're just about
ready to forgive him
and move past this whole thing.
He's a free young man.
And as far as continuity goes,
the reset button's been hit.
Morty!
That was a fast trial.
Jess-i-ca?
A bunch of us girls were gonna
go skinny-dipping later,
if you wanted to join.
Actually, now, really.
We're gonna do it right now.
This is the last conversation
I'm having about it
fully clothed.
No, thanks.
I'm... assuming...
we... maybe
get together...
in our 40s?
Uh, cool.
Sounds... hot.
Bye.
Must... continue...
moving
in ways... that lead...
to dying... with you.
Whoa!
Way to use up a clone!
What the fuck, man?
What's the matter with you?
Y-Y-You don't talk?
Tarantula got your tongue?
Uh...
Heil, Wasp Hitler?
What?
What the fuck?
Where's that shit coming from?
Look, I'm a primate.
I-I'm having a hard time.
I'll think or say whatever gets me home.
Well, here's how it works with wasps.
We eat our prey alive, and when we don't,
we lay our eggs in their eyeballs
so that our young can feast
on their brains
when they hatch.
When you're born that big an asshole,
the least you can do is
have a little empathy.
Now, come have dinner
with my beautiful family.
And drop the Hitler stuff.
Wasp Morty's been on
some crazy message boards.
Aah! Aah!
Oh! Aah! Ow!
Me and my friends want to fly around
and look for something to sting tonight.
You be careful not to waste
all your venom.
I'm not a bee, Dad.
Oh, God! Kill me!
Please kill me!
Uh, Beth, uh, after dinner,
could I maybe borrow Morty
to help the lost Rick get back
to his primate-based reality?
Morty, are you done with your homework?
- Not all of it.
- Sorry, Dad.
Oh, don't be sorry, sweetie.
We're all in this together.
We're wasps, not monsters.
Aah!
Huh, guess I don't have it
as bad as I thought.
Can you pass the acid?
Aah! No!
Run! Run, my babies!
Bonus!
- Morty?
Where is that little shit?
Morty!
Whoa, garage foul.
Who said you could go through my stuff?
W-Where's my Boglin?
There you are.
Don't worry, Pop-pop's back.
I'll keep you safe.
What the...
He took my Meeseeks boxes!
All that's left are these
shitty Kirkland brand Meeseeks boxes.
What do you want?
Damn, your Morty sucks.
Aah, wasps!
Why the hell didn't you show Morty
how to bring my body back to life?
Don't tell me you gained sentience
- and tried to take over.
- What?
That is some A.I.,
racist, accusatory,
Isaac Asimov bullshit right there.
Then what happened?
Where's my body?
Oh, you're gonna love this.
- I love you, Morty.
- This is my life.
This is good.
What do ya know?
Our little Morty knows how to scream.
Oh, you're fucked now!
I told you!
Get him, Rick!
Aaaah!
Aah!
I-I can't see my own death.
H-How am I gonna die?!
Shh, quiet, idiot.
Quiet.
It's gonna be alright.
You don't get to know
how you're gonna die.
It's over.
Oh, hey.
This fucking ferrofluid's
wrapping around my legs.
Fuck!
I can feel! I have mass!
I'm a fucking god now!
You're fucked!
What the fuck?
I-I thought you were proud
to be a hologram!
That's 'cause I had to fucking be one!
Shit! Aaah!
Ugh! Aaah!
There's a lesson here,
and I'm not the one
that's gonna figure it out.
Hey, uh, sorry I didn't listen to you
and tried to kill
the whole world and stuff.
I guess I got to learn
how to live in the moment a little more.
Oh, boy, so, you actually
learned something today?
What is this, "Full House"?
I was living in the moment all day,
and it kept getting me killed by Nazis.
I think you have to think ahead
and live in the moment.
Morty, we saw you on the news.
Are you okay?
Oh, real nice, Rick.
Turning our son into an Akira?
- Real nice.
- Eat my ass, Jerry.
He turned himself into Akira.
Oh, I'll eat it,
because this is my house, Rick.
- I'll eat any ass I want.
- Gross.
You said the crystals wouldn't
hurt anyone, Dad.
This family has a clean start.
I don't know if adventures
fit into my son's life.
I'm fine.
Get off Rick's back.
Rick wasn't even here
when I was doing all that stuff.
That was all on me.
Well, alright, Morty.
I guess, as long as you're okay,
that's all we care about.
I don't want to see any more anime stuff
happening to my son, buster.
That finger has AIDS now.
Not my fault.
You skipped HIV?
- He's messing with you, sweetie.
- But it's tingling!
So, I guess what we learned
is to split the diff.
From now on, Rick and Morty doing
a little of this and a little of that.
Yeah, sometimes we'll do classic stuff.
You know, other times, we'll do whatever!
Sometimes we won't even do anything!
Rick and Morty do... not doing anything!
- A hundred years!
- Pushing it to the limit.
Rick and Morty, not sticking to one path.
Trying different things,
Making sure to keep out of a rut.
Doing stuff.
Sometimes not doing stuff.
Not even pushing a little bit
towards the limit.
Doing it alone or together.
Making sure to keep our eyes
on the prize.
Sometimes just relaxing.
Or not. And you can do whatever
the fuck you want, Morty.
- That's the end.
- Wait, wait, what the fuck?
H-Hold on. What the fuck
did you just say?
Nothing.
I didn't say anything.
I was just playing along with you guys.
You know I record everything, right?
Garage, isolate Summer's voice
and play back.
Oh, and then you guys can get married,
and, like, suck each other off
in a testosterone-addled
fucking third-grade-boy cumfest.
What, the hell, Summer?!
That's disgusting.
Fucking gross, Summer!
Jesus Christ!
I was just joking around, you...
Just seeing if you guys
pay any attention to me.
Just want to be a part of the fun.
Get the fuck out of here!
Get out of here, Summer!
- Fucking disgusting!
- Get out of here!
You ruined the Season 4 premiere!
The Season 4 premiere, you ruined it!
God, tomorrow's career day.
I don't want to think about what
I do when I get out of school.
I know exactly what I want to do.
I want to work in hospice.
I want to comfort
the people who are dying,
who have no one else in their lives...
The real lonely people.
I'm gonna look at their name
tags, and I'm gonna say,
"I love you,"
followed by whatever it says
on their name tag,
over and over.
What the fuck?
Hey, Morty, quick favor.
What, cover me in gasoline and spiders?
Fine, yeah, I'm in.
Wasn't my first pitch,
but, hey, not gonna waste
this opportunity.