Are we -- are we gonna put it
back when we're done with it?
Why? The only thing of value
on it is the secret treasure map.
The rest is just instructions
for running a country,
and I'm pretty
sure they're online.
It just feels a little wrong --
Morty, are you gonna
be a fucking America nerd
or are you gonna be cool
and steal the
Constitution with Grandpa?
Here, hold this while I
crack the hermetic seal.
W-Why not just use this again?
Morty! You just
destroyed the map
and activated the giant assassin
hidden in the Statue of Liberty!
I'm sorry -- w-wait, what?
It was a Trojan horse,
Morty. Never trust the French.
Alright, fun's fun, but now
the federal government's
gonna be pissed
again. Way to go.
And on America's birthday
or whatever the
fuck Thanksgiving is.
Rick and Morty!
You are under
arrest and surrounded
by an anti-portal shimmer!
Come out with your hands up!
Well, Happy Thanksgiving to me.
Can't wait to see what a
"shimmer" does to my prostate.
Dad, can you please
just end whatever this is --
I understand you're
upset, Mr. President.
It's honestly all Morty's fault.
But in the meantime, you
really want to keep your army
of pointlessly camouflaged
Eagle Scouts off my lawn.
Don't tell me what I
want, you anti-American
piece of shit, you terrorist!
You know, you use
that word so much
it's lost all meaning, Mr. P.
It's like, at this point,
what's a terrorist?
It's a guy you
don't like. Big deal.
Hoo-rah!
Told you to stand down.
You just lost two soldiers
over here. Good men.
Might be time to look at
the terrorist in the mirror.
You want a war?!
I'll put your outer-space ass
in a goddamn Phantom Zone
with a bar of kryptonite
soap around your neck.
You're done,
Sanchez! You hear me?
Oof. He's really
pissed this time.
Why don't you guys just
fuck and get it over with.
Okay, well thank you, Summer,
but I think I've
got a better option.
Dad, no. Ehh...
hands are tied, sweetie.
I have to turn myself into a
turkey and trick the President
into giving me a
Presidential turkey pardon.
Again? How many
times have you done this?
I don't know, Jerry, how
many years have I lived here?
Careful how you answer that.
Geez, Rick, y'know,
y-you've done this a lot.
Don't you think the President
might see it coming this time?
He probably will, Morty.
That's all part of the dance.
In the past, I've
inserted myself
into the potential turkey
pardonee population
by brainwashing the
presidential turkey wrangler
prior to the ceremony.
But this time, the turkey
wrangler's been euthanized
and the turkeys
will be transported
by armored military vehicles.
Vehicles manufactured by
ghost corporations that I control.
- Which we have audited.
- Allowing me access to...
- Central computers...
- To track the...
Real armored transports,
which he can never...
Totally track and sneak aboard.
And even if he does,
he'll be on a truck
full of turkeys and
fully armed marines.
Who won't recognize me
because the human eye
is inherently face
blind to turkeys.
Fortunately, those marines
won't have human eyes.
They'll have turkey eyes.
Jesus ever-loving
Christ, why don't you two
just fuck and get it over with?
Careful, Dwayne.
You're only Vice President
because I need
10% of the white vote.
There's a giant French
assassin attacking New York,
and you're using the war
room to measure dicks
with your alcoholic
sci-fi boyfriend?
Rick Sanchez is more dangerous
than some steam-powered
French bitch,
and New York can handle
its own global emergencies.
General? Initiate
Operation Deep Gobble.
Coop, not on Thanksgiving.
It's what I trained
for, Mary Lou.
- It ain't our fight.
- Baby.
That little race car driver
you got bakin' in your belly.
What world you
want him rearin' up in?
One where some...
spiky-haired Doctor Who
in a lab coat can change
the color of the sky?
Or a world where he can
fill his pickup with hot dogs
and drive it to a jukebox
full of our demographic's
current favorite music?
Obviously the latter, but --
Well, that world, Mary Lou,
the one with those meals,
vehicles, and songs people
in this 30-mile area prefer...
that world needs a few good men.
In a secret Pentagon lab.
Turning into turkeys.
You come back
without feathers, Coop.
God, I love this country.
Hoooo-ah!
♪ I got a pregnant girl
and a pickup truck ♪
♪ I got one by choice
and the other by luck ♪
♪ But now it's time
to turn into a turkey ♪
♪ I hope there can
be peace one day ♪
♪ Till then, I pray my DNA
♪ Gets backed up
These pills contain
tracking chips
that identify each
of you as individuals.
That will be important later.
♪ Gobble, gobble
♪ When I turn into a turkey
Alright, boys,
search every bird.
If Sanchez is here, I
wanna hear you gobblin'.
Let me look at you, scum.
Get outta here, you wobbleneck.
Sarge, this -- this ain't
like the simulation, man.
I don't like it -Keep
it together, Martinez.
Eyes are on the ground, sir.
- No sign of Einstein.
- Stay frosty, gentlemen.
I want this pardoning
pipeline airtight.
Sir! We have hacked
the garage door.
We are in. Eyes on the bogey.
Or you've got eyes on a robot.
All due respect, sir, I
know flesh when I see it!
Those flesh-covered robots
should buy us some time.
The pardonable turkeys
should be on that truck.
Ship, go stealth.
Rodriguez, Fincher.
Get eyes on that.
Huh. Turkey Marines.
The President came to play.
Jam those two radios.
Confirmed.
Ah! Geez!
Fincher, Rodriguez, come in!
Copy, copy, tango, all good.
Just a couple of
branches on the roof.
Don't ever turn
your radio off again.
- We will not surrender.
- We will never surrender.
- Oh, yeah?
Bring in the David Blaine box.
Damn, is that a
David Blaine box?
I told you we should have
just gone to my parents' house.
- No, you didn't.
- Well, I didn't say it out loud,
but it should be
well known by now
that I'd always rather be there.
- Oh, God, oh no!
- Aw, geez, Rick!
Sir, we've got Rick and
Morty inside the box!
- Then that confirms it.
- Sir?
No David Blaine box
can hold Rick Sanchez.
Scan the turkey truck!
Huh. That's weird.
ID chips for Fincher and
Rodriguez are glitching.
Sanchez...
I'll deal with this
bastard myself.
Sir, don't be a cowboy.
You can't get re-elected dead.
System is calibrated, sir.
That pill contains a tracking
chip that will identify --
I know, it'll be
important later!
Do it.
Moments from now,
the President will be
pardoning a turkey...
Home stretch, Morty.
Here comes dip shit
right on schedule.
Nothing can go wrong now.
Jesus, is that --Oh, shit.
The President
has the upper hand.
G-Grandpa fucked
up. Sunglasses on.
Act like a turkey. What?
Wha-- Are you scared?
Act like a turkey!
That's Rodriguez
and Fincher, sir.
It's Rick and Morty, you
useless fucking stump humper!
Sorry, don't tell 10% of
your friends I called you that.
Mr. President.
Sanchez, admit it. You lose.
Say it and I'll let
your loser ass go.
Did you just try to spit in
my face with no saliva gland?
- Just pardon me, dick.
- Why the hell would I?
Oh, I dunno, 'cause
if I move to Canada,
they'll be the best country!
I'll peck your Goddamn eyes out!
Ow! Hey!
Shit! My plume!
Hey, back off!
Blueberries! We
got blueberries down!
Hold your positions,
it's a feeding frenzy!
I-I can't see.
I mean, I can see.
270 degrees -- it's
too many degrees!
Sir, we are losing the
mental game down here.
Keep it together, soldier!
POTUS is still in that pen --
We just lost New York to France!
Pull out the
President right now!
Gobble Tango -- I want
POTUS out of that pen!
That is an order! Locate
the president's chip!
Roger, roger.
There he is, I got him.
Let's go, boys! Let's
fly out the Eagle!
Hey, that's not me!
Package is secure. Pull us out.
Reinjecting subject DNA.
Hoppin' Jehovah, you
look like five pounds of shit
in a whore's lunchbox.
You alright, Mr. President?
Yes. I am...
the President.
Clean his ass up and
get him to the War Room.
Hey! Gobble Squad!
You got the wrong
guy, you morons!
Look at this dumb piece
of shit. Gobbling away.
Get back in there!
Alright boys, you heard
the VP. Pardon is tits up.
Pack up and ship out!
As for you, Sanchez...
bon appétit.
Where is this elevator going?
Where all the
unchosen turkeys go.
The feeding chamber.
What the fuck is that?
Not what... who.
The only thing to fear is... me!
How the fuck does
the White House
have a cloned spider of FDR?
It's no clone, it's FDR.
He was a guinea pig
for the polio vaccine.
We asked ourselves
"What walks the most?"
"We?" You're
taking credit for this?
The office comes
with baggage, Morty.
Rick, I'm afraid to die!
You won't have to
be for long, Morty!
We're due to return to
human form any second!
Then what?
Then we just have to not
get eaten by the spider!
Oh, so in other
words, be afraid to die?
Morty, if winning an argument
is that important to you,
you were never alive!
Time for a New Deal... Murder!
I'm sick of hearing
how iconic you were!
Try having an historical
administration after Facebook
goes online, you
old-timey bitch!
Morty, tear open that panel!
How's this for a fireside chat?
Woof. You just killed FDR.
He was a monster, though.
Don't mythologize
him. He was a politician.
Speaking of, you kind
of saved our bacon there,
so I'll make you a deal.
You pardon us and
I'll make you human.
Wrong turkey.
Man, the face blindness is real.
I'd like these... men...
turned back into humans, please.
Uh, yes, of course,
Mr. President.
But I thought we
already rehumanized
all the turkified marines.
I'd like these men
turned back into humans.
I am the President.
Yes, sir. Uh, sure thing.
Increase their
strength by 1,000%.
But... that wouldn't be human.
Turkeys have always
been more than human.
Okay, uh, so right there,
now I'm starting to --
I am selling New York to France.
And giving all of the
money to Congress.
Now that's how you do it!
He became President today.
That's right, murmur!
And when you're done,
get me some pants.
If you're the President,
who the hell have we been
governing the country
with for the last three hours?
An impostor, you
good for nothing idiot!
You humanized the wrong turkey!
It's possible.
We shouldn't leave
anything to chance.
Wouldn't want Congress
working with the wrong president.
A very good point,
Mr. President.
Do we believe
this fine feathered,
collaborative gentleman to
be our commander-in-chief?
Or are we gonna let "Mr.
Cash Bar at the Christmas Party"
stay in office?
All in favor of
Turkey President?
You can't be serious.
You think he cares
about America?
Is that why this is
happening to you?
Because you cared about America?
Guards, these men are...
oh, what is the word?
Uh, terrorists.
Okay, screw this. Go,
Go, Sanchez laser fists.
Oh, shit, I was a turkey
for a while, wasn't I?
Okay, guy's pretty strong.
Mary Todd Lincoln!
Who's dead weight now, bitch?
You should regain feeling
in your ass in a minute.
Sorry my turrets blew
up your motorcycle.
Just give me some
goddamn clothes.
Must suck to have your
only safe haven be my house.
Y-you want your regular outfit
or should we dress
you like a terrorist?
I don't need to be here,
and I'm still the President.
Oh, glad to hear it. That means
you can give me that pardon.
Or -- Or I could put
you out with the trash.
What is your problem?!
Why do you hate this country?
I hate every country
in the universe, brother!
They're job placement programs
for the politicians
that invent them --
Okay, Fight Club.
I get paid to protect
the sidelines you sit on!
You get paid to make
sports metaphors!
I clean your litterbox!
So your little nerd
paws don't have to touch
another nerd's nerdy
poopies while you're flexing
your grody little edge
lord anus all over it!
Guys, maybe you're
both right and both wrong.
Shut up, Morty!
You little bitch, you
destroyed the Constitution.
You're the biggest
booger eater here!
Do not talk to my son that way.
Sorry, Mrs. Smith.
The two of you are
ruining Thanksgiving.
Together.
And you can both
either come to the table
and eat food with my family
or you can keep doing what
you're doing at the corner bar.
Bars actually suck
at Thanksgiving.
I'm still trying to
sort through this.
One of you wishes you
had the personal quality
known as courage
but the other two of you
want actual vital organs?
This Charlie Kaufman
reboot of "Wizard of Oz"
is destroying itself.
That's why I need a brain!
I'm doing a terrible
job writing this!
Pass the potatoes.
Thank you. Mm-hmm.
Good green beans, Mom.
The turkey's raw,
Dad. Shit's potato bunz.
Sorry, Summer, the
United States enclosed us
in a shimmer bubble that
scrambled my oven timer.
So I guess elections
do have consequences.
Eat my ass, Jerry. I've
seen your IRS records.
You can blame me once
you have taxable income.
Yes, Jerry is a piece of shit.
I agree.
Um, guys? What's that?
Paula, as you can see,
President Curtis has enacted
a plan to turn all
turkeys in America
into hybrid super soldiers.
The move has 100%
approval from Congress
following its third
pay raise in six hours.
Back to you.
My God, the bastard's unhinged!
There won't be a
single bird left in DC!
Oh, wow, wiping out a native
population on Thanksgiving?
- That's never happened before.
- What did you just say?
Well, I-I associated
Thanksgiving with genocide.
It's what young people
do. I wasn't trying to --
The Crypt of the New World.
That could be our one
chance to turn this thing around.
You know about the Crypt?
Ugh, so the treasure's
already gone.
Wait, is that why you were
stealing the Constitution?
You old fart dick.
The Crypt of the New
World isn't a treasure.
But it might be our
only hope. Come on.
But isn't the crypt
underneath DC?
The Turkey
President's got an army.
An actual Army.
And an Air Force.
And Marines --Slow down, Morty.
Walk us through
every military service.
Does somebody have a pen?
We've got something
more powerful
than every army in the world.
Well, no, we don't, but
with the right speech,
we could get a handful
of well-trained hillbillies.
Eh, it worked against
the British. I'm in.
Birds replacin' people.
What would Johnny Cash
or Dale Earnhardt say?
He'd say "It's time
to walk the line"
or "Drive very fast
between two of them."
We don't serve your kind here.
Oh, my God, are you serious?
Read the sign.
He's my boss, Marvin.
It's okay.
Mistrusting Presidents
is a patriotic duty.
And that guy on TV isn't me.
He's a turkey
infused with my DNA.
I'll be damned.
Well, I'm racist.
You better not be here
to take my man again.
- Mary Lou.
- I'm poor!
And pregnant!
With a poor person!
And I need you.
And 10% of your baby.
Now, look, I know it's gonna
take more than some speech.
But what is a speech?
Isn't it just a question?
And isn't that a question too?
Speeches are words.
Repeated words.
Listed words.
Repeated lists of
repeated words.
None of that matters.
You know what does matter?
Me. Asking you.
"Will you do what I say?"
Just two questions, Chief.
Lock? And load?
They're rhetorical, sir!
Lock and load!
Sir, we've got Rick and Morty
coming in what appears to be
an unlicensed "Star Wars" AT-AT.
Or as the millennials
say, A-T, A-T.
So it begins.
Gobblers!
Tonight, we rise!
Aww, geez, geez, geez.
Nice driving, Sanchez.
Wire's down, pen is clear.
You know the Goddamn rules!
If you see something
clucking or pecking,
put a buckshot in its panties.
Jesus Christ!
T-they got Johnson!
He got off easy.
Hold off the bastards!
What now, Rick?
Time to turn up the broiler.
Whoa, i-is that --
The Crypt of the New World.
The treasure you were after
is this country's oldest secret.
One disguised by centuries
of Thanksgiving folklore.
Is that... a turkey dinosaur?
America's original rulers.
Merciless beasts, grazing on
the flesh of cowering humans.
Then, in the 15th
century, a vessel crashed.
Two vessels, really.
On board -- our saviors.
Sanchez, pull that lever
at the same time I do.
Oh, shit, they're gonna fight!
No, wait, they love each other!
They were at war
when they arrived,
but they united over
their hatred of turkeys.
And what they love even
more than each other
is kicking turkey butt.
Gentlemen!
Ba'ruka Dar Tin'in Yo-Tei!
Coooooooooorn!
It's working!
Come on, Sanchez, let's
power down the humanizer ray.
Whose side are we on?
I don't know, but we've done
enough to pay for college.
Look, we're almost there.
Sorry, my turn for a surprise.
Damn, this guy loves
arriving from the shadows.
Look around. You can't
beat our ancient warriors.
Can't I? My kind has
always dealt with predators.
That's why we sleep in trees.
And that's why,
in the wild, we fly.
Now you must choose ---
Fight me, or stop that
weapon from turning
all of America's turkeys
into a new master race.
You dumb dip shit,
there's three of us,
and two of us are spacemen.
Obviously they're
gonna save America
and bring that monument home,
and I'm gonna kick your ass.
Oh, and, Sanchez?
You got your pardon. Aw.
Shut up, Morty. Come on.
Let's go, bitch.
So be it.
Is it true what Turkey Man said?
That turkeys sleep in trees?
Who the hell cares, Morty?
Let's just deactivate this shit.
Calibrating.
Targeting all American turkeys.
Oh, my God, they
gave it a voice?
Who is this for? We're in space.
Geez, Rick, I-I-I guess them?
Morty, use this carefully.
Crack the humanizer
core and cut the blue wire.
You hear me? Blue wire.
Wha-- Why don't
we just blow it up?
It's a national
monument, fuck nut!
We just got pardoned.
You really wanna do
this again next year?
You forgot something,
Turkey Man.
No matter what you
got people to believe,
I'm still the Goddamn President.
And you forget, in the
one day I've had your job,
I've learned 10 times as much.
I've underestimated you.
For the last time.
Rick, they're not
exactly primary colors!
A-Are -- Are we cool
with, like, t-turquoise?
Are you kidding me, Morty?
Just cut the damn thing!
Oh, shit, oh, fuck --
- Targets acquired.
- Activating weapon.
Oh, shit! Oooooooh!
Heritage destroyed.
Morty!
God damn it, you had one job!
I beat you.
Look at me, you
turkey ass bitch.
Wait, why are you --
Is that a wishbone?
I wish to explode.
The Berlin Wall has come down.
Man ♪ It's called
the Playstation.
- The winner is...
- "Shakespeare in Love."
- Playstation 2.
- Hurricane Katrina
- slams Louisiana...
- Playstation 3.
- This is Maroon Five...
- Playstation 4.
- The Cubbies win!
- I want a Playstation 5.
I wasn't sure when
to pull you out.
I-I assumed you were
running through your whole life.
Yes.
And what a life it was.
Gentlemen, thank you once
again for saving this nation.
Slloosh garg blurrg.
I don't speak googa.
The CIA only taught me
your activation phrase.
But if I could say anything...
I'd say give America
one more chance.
Kalaak 'ha benben prilo garg.
Oh, my God, they're gonna
fight. Th-They're really gonna fight.
- Aw, they love each other!
- Never gets old.
I'll never get tired of that.
So... after those aliens
discovered America...
They went into hibernation,
leaving us the technology
we used to lead the free world.
That and also to
do stuff like slavery.
I always thought we were...
more special than that.
Like we invented
everything and did everything
and that's why
we own everything.
Now I- I- I- I don't
know what to feel.
Feel thankful, Morty.
Feel thankful.
Improved by KID
Resynced by KID
Enjoy the movie(s) / show(s)
I know, baby.
Coop, honey, should we get
Lucky Charms or Kibble Bibbitz?
You know we can't afford either.
Baby, the President
owes you. You saved him.
Ain't his fault our
insurance got cut.
They gotta build missiles.
Ugh, fine, just -- Can y'all
hold Jakey for a second?
What the hell's he doin?
I think he's foraging.
Crazy bastard
thinks he's a turkey.
Well, I refuse to pay for
this man's health care.
Did you get any of that?