Boob world, boob world.
It's a world for you,
but it's actually two.
Boob World!
I gotta say, Morty, it's weird
that you wanted me to come,
but I'm actually
exstyched about it --
that's excited,
stoked, and psyched.
I didn't want you to
come. Talk to Rick.
Truth is, Summer, Boob
World's been at the center
of a few protests
every day for 30 years,
so they've recently rebranded as
a boob empowerment experience,
and if we bring a
female, we get in for free.
So, I'm, like, what, a Coke
can you're taking to Six Flags?
No, 'cause once
you get into Six Flags,
you can throw your
Coke can away.
No fucking way.
It can't be.
Holy shit, holy shit,
holy shit. Oh, look at that.
- What is it?
- It's a GoTron ferret.
It's not a GoTron ferret, Morty.
It's the blue GoTron ferret.
- Boob World is canceled.
- No, Rick, no.
You promised.
You always do this.
Tell you what, Morty,
I'll let you choose.
Do you really think Boob World -
- Yes.
- Let me finish.
Is more important --Yes.
Let me finish!
Than have all five
of the only five GoTron
ferrets in the universe?
Are you finished?
Yes. So, let's go.
Summer, help me hook
the winch up to the ferret.
- Sure.
- What the hell?!
You said you were
letting me choose.
Yeah, whether to
break my fucking heart.
You chose badly.
That's how it all began.
To my sister, it was
just another game.
But what she didn't know --
That was the moment
everything changed.
Wait. What?
I had gotten my first taste of
respect and my first voiceover.
I can hear you. Can you hear me?
And I knew then and
there I wanted more of both.
Hello?
Beth, Jerry, do
something fun with us.
A giant monster is attacking
in the Nibblenug system.
Your suits are in the bathroom.
Mine smells skeletony.
I have a chiropractor
appointment.
What are you involving us in?
Rick's been collecting
GoTron ferrets,
and now that he has all five,
we can combine them into --
Morty, for Christ's
sake spoilers.
Spoilers, Morty.
WE don't need to
sell this to anyone.
There's a giant
monster attacking.
In the Nibblenug system.
Since when does this
house care about alien lives.
We don't even watch
British television.
Told you. Let's just
get Gene from next door
- and a homeless guy.
- No. Hold on.
Fuck Gene. Fuck the homeless.
Your kids and their
grandpa are asking you to do
an activity with them.
When did that stop being
a parent's wettest dream?
I guess around the
time our family created
a giant incest baby,
and the government
launched it into space.
Oh my God, we made
a giant incest baby.
Oh my God, you might be a clone.
I exist because you
guys failed to abort me.
We get the family we
get, not the one we want.
And if you want to
keep the one you got,
get your asses into
some anime spacesuits.
- Fair enough.
- Okay.
- Good work, Summer Camp.
- Yeah.
I'm exci-toked about this.
Sure you are -- now.
Something new was forming,
and I was at the bottom of it.
- I let Morty have his voiceover.
- It's really all he had left.
Okay, can you hear me or not?
Do you mean can I,
Summer, hear you?
No. My voiceover can
hear your voiceover.
What's the difference?
One would be telepathy, dumbass.
Now what?
Now, we --
Go, Team GoTron!
Where are we zip-lining through
futuristic metallic tunnels to?
Each robot ferret is at a
different location on Earth.
You're going to the
center of a volcano.
Thank you?
Okay, well, this isn't not fun.
Regroup on me.
I'll shoot a portal
to Nibblenug.
Did I just monorail from
my kitchen to Hawaii
just to regroup in outer
space above my kitchen?
- Uh, Summer?
- It's cool, Dad. Shut up.
Everybody, attack one at a time!
Is that the best way to --
Tee up something
awesome? Yes. Follow me.
Guys, we did our best,
but there's only one hope.
Activating link-dock.
Inter-Morphs -- rad-ified.
PostiTrinos -- maximized.
Holy shit, I-I can't
believe this is working.
Go, go, team! It's GoTron time!
Oh, my God. Hell yes!
This is amazing!
Okay, now we can
knock it around a little bit,
but trust me, we're still
building to something.
How do we --Just hit buttons.
we're too big to fail.
I kicked him! That
was me, right?
Uppercut!
I can't believe I almost
went to the chiropractor!
I've been waiting
a long time for this.
Form Luminous Energy Sword!
That's your ass, Mamma Jamma.
These were the good times,
when we felt like
we could do anything.
But anything is
never quite everything.
And pretty soon...
That was nothing -- nothing
compared to what we can do.
There are infinite universes
where I still don't have all five ferrets.
Th-th-those versions
of me would do anything
to complete their collections.
Okay, but Rick, remember
what you told me to remind you?
Sometimes, enough is...
Sometimes, enough is enough.
Morty, what are you doing?
He gets obsessed, Summer -
When are you going
to find your shame?
- I have more.
- Grandpa just gave
everybody the high
point of their lives,
and before he did,
every single one of you
was trying to
talk him out of it.
Wait. Yeah.
Wha-wha-what the fuck!
Now, he says we can go
higher, and big surprise,
it's time to drag
him down again.
Well, I vote --No voting.
No debate. It's not a democracy.
It's a Rickpublic.
You're in or you're out.
Obviously, I'm in. I
never said I wasn't in.
Me, neither. Tell us
what we're doing next.
Uh, I want to put
together a cookout.
That's it? I was honestly
prepared to blow someone.
- Jerry.
- I said "prepared" and "someone."
Rick invited five
versions of our family
from different universes,
each with incomplete GoTrons.
I didn't have anyone to talk to,
since the other four Mortys
had been to Boob World.
Did you walk on the beach?
The beach that's all boobs?
No, the beach that's all sand.
Yes, the boob one!
Rick was in the garage with
the heads of the five families.
Ugh, and Summer.
In that first sit-down,
it was Big Fat Rick,
Ricardo Montaya,
Hot Head Rick --
he got that name because he
was prone to dramatic outbursts -
and Lil' Ricky Wrap-it-Up,
who was always great
at the end of a meeting.
At the head of it all,
me and Grandpa Rick.
Now, don't get me wrong, C137,
we're happy for
your good fortune.
But we did not
travel to your universe
just to have it
rubbed in our faces.
Come on, Big Fat
Rick, you know your face
is too small to rub anything on.
My face is the
same size as yours.
Wow. Huh. Hold on.
I'll be damned.
You're so fat you're
an optical illusion.
Summer, give 'em the pitch.
We're offering to help
each of your families
complete their full GoTrons.
In exchange for
some concessions.
Ever since I was a
little boy in the slums,
I have dreamed of
having a complete GoTron.
But concessions?
I hope you mean the
kind from a counter.
I hope she means ice cream!
We'd like you to
relocate your families
to this universe, and
let me make some
modifications to the GoTrons --
in the interest of us
all working together.
Want to know what I think?
Sure, Hothead Rick, just don't
unexpectedly fly off the handle.
I think you guys got a lot of
nerve acting better than us!
This is the family that
made a giant incest baby!
Had the government
launch it into space!
It's still floatin' around
out there somewhere!
Are we ever gonna
live that down?
If I get a full GoTron, it
won't be by kissing your ass,
it'll be by taking
what's mine -- yours!
Hey! Gross! No need.
And you were
driving... a ferret?
We all are, moron! Give me key!
You'll regret this, you
level-headed fucks.
Obviously, we predicted
that might happen,
which is why we have
Yo-Yo Rick on standby.
Anybody got beef with Yo-Yo?
Some people think
he's lame, but to me,
he's lame in a cool
way because he owns it.
Cool. That concludes
business. Lil' Ricky Wrap it Up?
Raise 'em up, boys! Oh-pah!
And so, we helped our
people find their ferrets.
How they got them,
not our problem.
Then, we got down to business.
Here's how it worked --
if a giant monster
attacked your planet,
we all got the alert.
♪ Hey, hey, mama mia's
♪ Got a plate of
spaghetti for the takin' ♪
♪ Papa pia's got a great
big robot that he's makin' ♪
♪ I got the moon
in both my eyes ♪
♪ You got a bowl
of pizza pie, hey! ♪
♪ A bit of pasta with some
anime combined, yeah ♪
We formed five GoTrons.
And those GoTrons
formed the GoGoTron.
Go, GoGoTron!
♪ Take it away, boys!
I will never get sick of this!
If you were a giant monster
at that time, in our universe,
you never had a chance.
♪ A bit of pasta with
some anime combined ♪
♪ 'Cause we're two genres, but
each one is intertwined, yeah ♪
Mine needs a
weapon like a Yo-Yo.
And a Yo-Yo on the chest.
Are you listening to me?
I-I need you to
respect this partnership.
I kept Rick removed
from the ugly stuff.
If you got in his way, I
got you out of the way.
And that made more
room to move up.
The head of my right arm.
Me? I ended up the
left foot of the left foot --
I guess because our robot
didn't have an asshole.
Well, it had one.
Bitch! When are you gonna
stop breaking my balls?
You win, okay?
We're not competing, Morty.
And there's your answer.
I could move you up if I could
trust you to put family first.
H-how is that
putting family first?
Show me all the blueprints!
I agree. That's an issue.
Big Fat Rick, his flask stays full
or your locker gets empty. Thanks.
I know it feels good
when he likes you,
but that doesn't mean him
liking you makes you good.
Solid babble, Morty -- like a
fortune cookie written by Borat.
Yeah, I'm not as smart as you.
That's why I know
you know what I mean.
You mean, if I really
loved my family,
I'd give control of it
back to your jealous ass.
Green Ferret Four needs a
wash, and we're out of detergent.
I just bought a box.
And Grandpa snorted it because
you make him feel fenced in.
Sum-Sum?
Get two boxes.
We evacuated one of
the planets we saved,
and built a secret
nightclub on it,
a place no enemies
could find us --
unless you count my brother.
I didn't even have my
own ferret anymore.
Summer made me something called
an "associate security chief" --
whatever the hell that means.
Look at this guy.
And look at this guy.
Look-look at this guy over here.
Oh, there she is!
My Baby Princess!
Get up here. Stop the music.
This. Is. Our. Queef
-- O-our Queen.
She saved my life.
She-she set me free.
We wouldn't have what we
have without this crazy bitch.
And she's got a
special announcement.
Summer, tell 'em
wha-what we talked about.
Now? I don't think --
Okay, I'll do it. God damn.
The new job did
have some perks --
like, I got to be around
the night Summer realized
she was in over her head.
Okay, I've got 90 extra ferrets,
which means I need 10 more,
and then four of you
get your own GoGoTron,
and 20%of you get a GoTron,
'cause we're all gonna
have a fucking GoGoGoTron.
He's very excited. Um...
Oh-pah!
I hate my family.
You should.
Get in.
How's it going with your
grandpa's compulsiveness?
Is your sister still
enabling it? Huh?
Who are you people?
Let's just say we're the
rightful owners of these ferrets.
Then, why were they scattered,
and buried across the universe?
We mean in a more
general, cultural sense. Arrrgh!
What your Grandpa did
is called "appropriation."
Not cool! Hunnnnngh!
Look, Morty, we've
been watching.
We know you're the one
that knows what's best.
Work with us from the inside.
Help us take over
this operation.
We're literally designed
for it. Mm-hmmmmmm!
Nobody will know it was you.
Then, you can get
back to what's important.
Are those Boob Bucks?
Legal tender at every
kiosk and ride! Huuunh!
I can't.
Summer's treating me like
shit, but she's still my sister.
That's really noble, Morty.
If you were in our family,
your loyalty would be rewarded.
But you're not in our family,
which means we can kill you.
Oh, yeah?
And sure enough, just
when I stuck my neck out
for the family, it got
stomped on anyway.
- Dad!
- Mom! Dad!
Hothead Rick, baby!
I set myself up for that!
- What the hell happened?!
- Hothead Rick.
How did he get so close to us?
Morty was supposed
to be security!
- Morty?
- I-I-I stepped away, alright?
But-but not to let that happen!
Morty, we're not
attractive strangers
next to you on
a flight to Paris,
traveling alone to
get over a breakup,
so this is no time to be coy!
- Oh... pah.
- Lil' Ricky.
I'm all wrapped up, Summer.
Guys, I know you don't trust
me, but what have we become?
Why are we doing this anymore?
Because it's
fun, you little rat.
Now go home, and
play video games
while we clean up these bodies,
or your mother and I will hire
people to break your knees!
This is $16,000 we
got from the deep state
for stepping on
that trailer park.
That should be enough for
school lunch and home repairs.
Now, I gotta turn
my back on you.
No!
With Morty out of the
way, things were looking up.
But looks aren't everything.
Hi, Summer. Um, my
cockpit's not getting Wi-Fi.
Dad, you know that's
not what I do around here.
Oh, I'm not your Dad.
I'm a version of him.
This is my first day here,
and I-I'm not sure what
you do around here.
- Then fuck off.
- Oh, fuck you.
Excuse me? I want your ID.
Mom. Are you Mom? Can
you control your rookie Jerrys.
Sweetie, we're all a
little overwhelmed -
Good point. You're
not a war-time Mom.
Why don't you find
your version of Dad,
and take a break,
take a holiday.
I don't have time to
wait for your confirmation,
so let's just say, if
you're here in 10 minutes,
I'll have you removed.
And then, the GoTrons
make the GoTrons,
make the GoTrons.
Couple of snags, but I
know how to speed things up.
Remember when we talked about
how the best thing we could do
for the family is to
recruit outside the family?
Yes. Way ahead of you.
Summer, I want
you to meet Kendra.
She's from a temp agency.
She's got an entire
workforce ready to go,
and all of them have previous
giant robot pilot experience.
So, we'll be ready to
go ahead of schedule.
Well, I don't know
about that but --
Well, Kendra knows. So...
So...
You here to break my legs?
No. We're here to talk
shit about your sister,
because she just fired us.
- You're kidding.
- Arrogant little bitch.
- Should we clip her?
- No. She's not worth doing time.
You wouldn't do time. You
brought her into the world.
So, I can take her out.
You thought there
was an actual law?
It's a joke mothers say.
What kind of fucked up
world have you been living in?
Uh, one where your
mother murdering you
isn't a comedic premise?
Guys, there's a little
adjustment period,
but pretty soon, you're
gonna to return to normal,
and you're not going
to want to kill Summer.
You're not even
gonna be mad at her.
Nah, fuck her. She's my enemy.
Should we kill ourselves, so
we can get to hell before her,
and hide near the entrance?
I like that.
Rick fired me.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay, baby?
What happened to us?
We lost our minds.
I did it. Morty was right.
I got addicted to
making Grandpa happy.
It's only because your Grandpa
inflates the value
of his happiness.
That's a good point.
I mean, look at me.
I'm easy to make
happy, which is why
nobody gives a shit if I am.
I appreciate it, but
there's something else too.
I've been really sensitive
about family lately
because of something
I've been keeping secret.
Okay. Who's on
the Supreme Court,
and what state do we live in?
It's been years since
I've thought about this.
No, I'm not pregnant.
But as you guys recall, and as
a lot of people keep bringing up,
Morty and I did accidentally
create a giant incest baby,
which the government
did launch into space.
And I'm not sure
how to tell you this,
but it is still alive, and I
have been in contact with it.
There were soldiers waiting
for me outside school last month.
They took me to the
Pentagon, and briefed me.
And from there, I was shuttled
to a secret base on Mars.
They had captured
him, and wanted to see
if he'd respond to me,
instinctively, being his mother.
And he sure did.
But what they didn't expect
was that I'd respond to him.
I was supposed to
help discipline him,
so they could turn him
into the ultimate weapon.
Instead, I trained him to
love, to believe in himself,
and finally, to escape.
The government doesn't want
anyone to know it happened,
but it's only a matter of time
before the story comes out.
And when it does, all we're
going to have is each other.
And you guys are a
couple, and Rick has Morty,
but I'm the odd one out
So, I wanted to make
sure we stuck together.
But instead, I drove us
apart, and Rick replaced me
with an anime girl,
so all I've got is myself
and my giant, tortured,
government-trained rogue
incest monster baby out
there in space somewhere.
Oh, baby. What the fuck.
And then, you have to wonder, what
else are they doing with our taxes?
Wait. Summer,
what did you just say?
Morty, a lot.
He replaced you
with an anime girl?
Big eyes? Plus signs for teeth?
Ends sentences with
weird sounds that don't fit?
Yeah. That's going to
be his whole crew now.
And they're about to run their
first test on the GoGoGoTron.
Those people want
to steal the robots.
Th-they're gonna kill
Rick. He's all alone.
We-we-we've got to go save him.
Right. Or... you know, fuck him.
- I'm good with that.
- Yeah, fuck him.
Guys, a great leader once told
me you get the family you get.
Alright. It works. Now, we
just got to find a giant monster.
My sensors have
picked one up, Rick.
Okay. Okay Lock
onto its location.
Yeah, got it.
Oh, it's you!
Huh?
What the hell is this?
Thanks for making the
biggest robot ever, Rick.
We'll take it from here.
You little assholes!
You son of a bitch!
Lock a load, boys.
Say "hello" to my little me.
Give up, old man.
The G3 is ours.
And last I checked,
your "family"
wasn't coming to save you, hmm?
Go go goo goo.
Holy mother of mercy!
My God. It's beautiful.
Yeah! Family!
-Is that -- -It's exactly
what it looks like. Yes.
Congrats, man. I
see the resemblance.
Form the Energy Sword!
Activate the Goddamn sword!
Oh, man, the sword. Maybe
we didn't think this through.
They're not actually gonna
attack a space baby, are they?
I never thought I'd
be the one to say this,
but you need to watch
more anime, Mom.
Whoa, easy now, Naruto.
Bahbah go bye-bye!
What the hell is wrong
with you people?!
You just have an incest space
monster in your back pocket, huh?
Welcome to the Smith family.
Shit. Put that down, Naruto.
Your great-grandpa is in there.
What do you say?
One last zipline?
Incest space baby. Nicely done.
After that, things pretty
much went back to normal --
some version of it, anyway.
Rick said GoTrons were
lame little kid bullshit,
and we never talked
about them again.
Except all those gigantic space
bugs were still runnin' loose,
and there were no
GoTrons left to fight them.
Yeah, millions die every day.
But you want to know
what they could never kill?
Family.
- Where's Jerry?
- Help!
Help! I'm still out here!
Yep, nothing's
more important than--
Hey! Hey! Whoa-whoa-whoa!
Ugh!
And just like that, I knew
our goose was as cooked as --
Voiceovarians. Ugh.
Improved by KID
Resynced by KID
Enjoy the movie(s) / show(s)
♪ Come day or night,
and feel around ♪
♪ This is the world for you ♪
♪ No matter where
you've ever been ♪
♪ This is the place
your life begiii-i-ins ♪
♪ Boob World ♪
♪ It's a world for you,
but it's actually two ♪
♪ Boob Wo-o-orld ♪
Samansky, you're late!
Won't happen again, sir!
Bugs. Look to your left.
Now, look to your right.
None of you are
coming back. Not one.
In the entire history
of this program,
not a single bug has returned.
Alright. Bring it in!
What are we?
- Normal-sized bugs!
- What do we do?
- Travel through an interdimensional
gateway to a planet
with tiny people!
- Why do we do it?
- To spread the cure for AIDS!
Hey, Sarge, how do we
know if these little people
can understand us?
I mean, do these
even speak Buganese?
Funny, Palicki. That's
why we say it very loud.
Guys, you'll still be the same
civilized bug on their side.
It's not like
interdimensional travel
strips us of our clothes, and
makes us screaming monsters.
Or maybe it does.
It's impossible to know.
Now, get out of here!
My clothes -- where'd they go?
Did you get any of that?