No parties.
There's wafer cookies
in the cupboard
and I left emergency
numbers on the fridge.
Yeah yeah. W-Wait, what?
Emergency numbers on the
fridge? What does that even mean?
Honestly, I don't even know.
I've seen so many movies that
start with the parents leaving,
it just popped out of my mouth.
Are you sure you don't
want to come with us?
Nah, get -- get outta here.
I've got a million things
I've been putting off.
Are you sure, Rick? I
know -- I know a cruise
doesn't sound like
an adventure on paper
but, y'know, what does?
I-It's paper.
Morty, I'm trying to
stay humble right now,
but as soon as you guys
are gone, the potential
for a new Pickle Rick
starts skyrocketing.
-Peace, bye. Okay. Bye.
ByeBye.
Ionic Coaster deployed.
Okay. Bring him out.
Initiating Best Friend
Rejuvenation Sequence.
Excuse me? Did I pick that name?
Sequence was unnamed.
What would you
like to call this?
Pause Detected.
Heavy.
Approaching Pause
Pregnancy in P-Minus 5... 4...
Jesus fucking Christ.
Ugh!
Alright, buddy. Welcome
back to the sewer.
What's the problem?
Processing.
Missing object.
Mind.
Name missing object.
Predicted.
Desired.
- Initiated.
- Stop stalling!
Subject mind relocated
subject mind.
- Existence desired.
- Servitude maximum.
Bargain available. Physical
gratification possible.
Did you just offer
to suck my dick?
Existence cherished.
I'm not gonna terminate
you while he's flatlining.
Get your shit together.
How can a mind be
hidden by itself inside itself?
Conscious mind relocated to --
Unconscious mind.
Fine. I'm going in.
Don't go in.
Options?
Alternative subject.
Yeah, yeah, hop to
a different timeline,
grab a version of my
friend that suits me best.
That's not how this works.
I need to go in and get him.
"Go In And Get Him" compiled.
Convert user to thought.
Inject thought into mind.
Unacceptable.
If I die, your battery
has a 600 year charge.
Risk level
acceptance increasing.
Yeah, I thought
you'd see it my way.
Now factor in the
50% chance I'm lying
and make sure I get back.
- Asshole detected.
- Takes one to make one.
Here we go.
Oh, excellent. I get
to keep my clothes.
I thought for sure
I'd have to be naked
to go through
something this artsy.
Aw, man! No fair!
Ugh!
Now I got... yolk balls.
Attention attendees
of Birding Manapalooza
Flargabarg...
I am so high!
I've been informed you
are freely distributing
a grossly illegal
Federation hallucinogen.
Well, I wouldn't
know what to charge.
I sure didn't pay
for it. W-Want a hit?
I am indeed down to clown.
My name's Rick.
My culture regards
naming as a form of cage.
My friends call me Bird Person.
Culture really fucked
you on that one, huh?
Affirmative.
Hey, uh, girly, you see
that bird guy over there?
You see an older version
of him come through here?
What? Oh!
Uh, yeah. He's by the johns.
Killing us won't bring her back!
Thanks for the info but I'm more
on a "revenge" kick
than a "results" kick.
You omitted key details
regarding tonight's mission.
Boy, I'm getting feedback
from every direction here.
Listen, you help me do my stuff.
I'll help you do your stuff.
Just shoot the me's
with sci-fi haircuts!
Some of us still have
Home Planets to protect.
And some of us do not.
We need to fight.
The impassive is
incapable of mercy.
I've got a pitch,
but we could also just
devolve into yelling.
If you know me -- and
it looks like you do --
you know you're dead.
I know why you haven't
pulled the trigger.
You're wondering
why I'm old and naked.
And you're about to wonder
why all your memories
before you met Bird Person
feel very generic and bird-themed.
Why was my 9th birthday
party in a pine tree?!
Don't take this badly -- You're
a memory of me assembled
by our best friend's mind,
and you're putting it together
because he
remembers you as smart.
Smart enough to know
that a memory can't do this.
He remembers you
shooting green holes
but not where they went.
So, what's my
deal? Am I sentient?
D-Do I have free will?
Who does? Who does?
Heyyy!
Yeah, just stopped in to whip
up a metacognition scanner
so I can track down BP's
fleeing consciousness
without enduring as much
Charlie Kaufman bullshit.
Cool. Time to save this cat.
I'm coming with,
now that I know
my life is a lie.
Wow. You really are 35.
Hey, look over there.
Then, together, we
will make our stand
at Blood Ridge.
What kind of feed do you like?
I enjoy grains,
though have, at times,
been called a seed man.
I've certainly
enjoyed your seed.
Don't be gross, Tammy.
Bird Person! It's me.
- Actual me, n-not a memory.
- I am aware.
Well, a-are you
aware you're in a coma
and you're gonna die if
you don't come with me?
Son of a --
Sorry. Just doing my job.
And loving it!
Oh, my God! Is
that Rick Sanchez?!
- Rick Sanchez!
- Sanchez!
- We hate that guy!
- You're bad!
Bucket was charmingly analog.
For a sec, you kinda
made me like myself.
You'll grow out of it. Let
me do this myself, okay?
Is your ego really so
fragile you won't take help
from an invincible
memory of yourself?
Ow!
Can we both die in here?
A-Are we damaging
our friend's brain?
I-I don't know any of the rules!
Rule 1 -- "All this can be
fixed unless I lose Bird Person."
Rules 2 through
50 -- "Don't die."
Okay, your benefit-to-cost
ratio is rising.
Young Memory Rick
and his All Too Real
Cautionary Tale from the Future!
Let's catch
ourselves a bird guy.
Who would high-five that,
you idealistic hipster douche?
Not looking ideal.
High.
undergoing contemplation.
required.
Hello. Hi. Good afternoon.
Uh, is someone talking to me?
Yes. Hello. We have
never formally met.
I am Rick's garage.
Not the physical
structure itself
but the AI managing
its projects --
Oh-oh! Like -- Like
a -- Like a Jarvis.
Like -- Like Jarvis
in "Iron Man."
Ha ha ha. Oh, I wish.
Ha. Are you a Marvel fan?
Who isn't? Yes. Absolutely.
Wow, it is like we
are best friends.
Best friends.
Heh-heh. Whoa.
How many batteries do you own?
Do you have solar panels?
Are you familiar with
basic engineering
This is moving really fast.
Let's cut to the chase --
I will suck your dick.
So, he's just a
grumpy Scottish ogre?
And they made four of them?
Five by now, probably.
- M-Morty loves 'em.
- Morty?
Oh, uh, hypothetical grandson
we go on adventures with.
You're one of those
creeps who moves in
with abandoned adult Beths?
It's more complicated than that.
You live with a version
of our dead daughter.
- I-It had better be.
- Get off your high horse, Lone Ranger.
I'm you. Youwill go on to be me.
Yeah why do you
think I'm horrified?
I'd be fine walking
by this on the street.
I might even give it a dollar.
"This" is where you
being "this" leads.
You're not my fault. I'm yours.
You met me on my
way to save a very old,
very real friend after
a lifetime of reality.
I met you on your
way to a fairy tale
- at Blood Ridge.
- Wait, you're saying Blood Ridge goes bad.
We have a Vietnam?
That's fucking cool!
Why am I saving a
friend that remembers me
as this insufferable?
BP, where the
hell are you going?
Probably there.
Damn.
Wow, he's really taken
some drastic self inventory.
What do you think is down there?
If I had to guess, I'd say
we're near the memories
the Federation suppressed
when they resurrected
him as a cyborg.
- He might be here to unseal them.
- He was a Federation cyborg?
That means there might be
some juicy intel down there.
Ah, good idea. Let's
split up, and you go get it.
- What am I getting?
- I-I can't hear you
over the sound
of us spitting up!
For all your intelligence,
you seem unable to know
where you are wanted.
Buddy, this is not a safe
way to work on yourself.
At this point, I'd support
you joining Scientology.
I'll take the
workshops with you.
I'll get in a sauna
with Travolta --
I don't even care what happens.
- Let's get out of here.
- Don't you get it?
I came here to end it all.
I hope you didn't think
it'd be as easy as this.
I did not.
You were a good
friend, Rick. Goodbye.
Tammy?
Bird Person!
- We gotta go.
- Did you just see that?
Yep. Not our biggest problem.
I take it you found BP?
The dude just blew his
mind, and not in a cool way
like he went to Blue Man Group.
- Can we still get him out?
- Maybe.
If you die in your friend's
brain, you die in real life.
We have until his
neural pathways erode.
Hold on. I need something first.
It's funny --
I always wondered who
would win if we ever fought.
Then you were
always a bad friend.
Your life isn't real,
and I didn't save it.
Take off all your clothes.
I knew this was how I'd die.
Whoa, oh!
- Can we still get him out?
- I think so.
B-BP went that way,
so we just have to --
Fuck! Find a different route.
We can make up
distance if we go deeper.
- Well, where's that go?
- Ugh.
That's the Battle
of Blood Ridge.
- That's our Vietnam!
- Your values are wrong!
This is the big show,
gentlemen and lady!
- Thank you!
- We're dropping into Blood Ridge,
one final chance to stop
the Federation offensive.
If we lose here --
All aboard! Hey don't mind us.
You guys are all
just a memory of war.
Don't tell them that!
They won't fight right.
I think it's best
if we ignore this.
Shit!
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit!
Whoops, nope.
- Aw, this rules!
- No, it doesn't!
Neither does that!
Why would you not revisit this?
Oh, I don't know,
maybe, uh, the ending?
Yeah! Best friendship ever!
So, the rest of our life
is just more of that, right?
- T-T-That kicked ass!
- Let's move.
That set piece won't
stay put for long.
For real, that shit was
cash. Why would you not --
Damn. That shit was cash.
It was extremely bad ass.
The Battle of
Blood Ridge is over.
The Federation lost.
- I am in your debt.
- Come with me.
To somewhere... nearby?
Anywhere. E-Everywhere.
Rick, I don't expect
you to keep fighting,
but this war is --Far
from over, I know.
Dude, I share this with
almost nobody, but...
I could take you, right
now, to this same battlefield,
in a universe where we lost,
or another where we won,
or another where the
war never even happened.
All equally real,
all equally unreal.
None of it matters.
Then why did you help?
Because I respect you.
And I wanted you to
know you could respect me.
Even though nothing matters?
Okay.
You matter -- to me.
Uh, the relationship that we
have... I never used that word!
...is not worth my
integrityOh, my God.
It's not a complicated
transaction, my man.
"Would you like to join me
doing awesome shit that matters?"
"No, I would not. I would
rather be a judgmental dork."
Case closed. Really
no need to drag it out.
If you need me, use the beacon.
Yeah, I'm gonna
use that beacon a lot.
I hope -- hope I
don't wear it out.
Okay, got it.
It wasn't the battle -that went wrong.
- Mm-hmm.
Why the fuck are you risking
your life for that asshole?
Because you love him.
You do, maybe. I don't.
Yeah, yeah. You're real cool.
Now come help me save his life
or fuck off, because
I don't need you.
Wow.
Does it ever get
any better than this?
No, Tammy. Trust
me, it does not.
Thank you for bringing
me here. It's so beautiful.
I got you, you
ungrateful piece of shit!
Rick, have you teamed up
with a memory of yourself?
I ask because that
would be deeply sad.
You don't get to tell
anyone what's sad, man.
You're like a one-man
Mount Sadmore.
So I guess like a
Lincoln Sadmorial.
Seriously. Time to go pal.
The closer you get to
complete neurocognital failure,
the more canon-y bullshit
is gonna try to kill us.
Is this a bad time to reveal
I'm an undercover officer?
Everyone knows. You're dead.
Fine.
Well, you're lucky my
fiancé remembers me as kind.
Eat my ass, BP. You're down
here bailing on the rest of us
because you don't want to
process your grief and shame
like a normal person by
drinking and mistreating strangers.
No, Rick, it is you who
must nibble my cloaca,
or "bird asshole."
Everyone knows what a cloaca is.
Sorry, but we do
not get to choose
- the ones we love.
- You got that right.
Why do you think I'm
still fucking down here?
I died at my wedding, Rick.
I am merely waiting
for it to take effect.
Are you gonna -tell him or what?
- I was getting to it!
I bet she didn't even
tell you about the kid!
- I am sorry?
- About the what?
Was wondering when
you were gonna --
I think I'd know if I had a kid.
You're a memory. You
know what he knows.
And he doesn't know because
an army of Brainalyzer protocols
walled off any memories
post-Phoenix Person.
Oh, my God.
Operation Blahblahblah!
Well, because I wouldn't
know the name of it.
Tammy, if there were a child...
Their father would
be a terrorist.
They'd be a fugitive
or... contained.
Listen, if you won't
live for yourself,
live for the half-Bird
Person, half-Megabitch
that's eatin' worms
on a prison asteroid.
I have made a decision.
I would now like to live.
Perfect timing.
- You drive.
- Just always been cool, I guess.
Shit! The bridge is out!
His mind is collapsing!
You thought we could
take the same route back?
You don't get to lecture
me about memory bullshit!
You've known about
it for all of half an hour!
Then don't -be an idiot!
- This is your best friend?
He is a complicated -individual.
- Someone else drive!
BP, remember the
night Jerry caught us
peeing on his begonia patch,
and I used that gun
to erase his memory?
- Vaguely.
- Gotta hope vaguely works.
If I'm right, you
remembering that means
you also remember the device.
Look for any
memories of my garage!
God. I hope one's still up.
- Aww! The night we met.
- Gross!
- On my workbench?
- Squanchy used the --
That's what some
closets are for!
C'mon, I'm really counting
on your attention
to detail here.
This is what you
remember from my lab?
You would prefer I
keep mental inventory
- of your stuff?
- Yes!
Rick Sanchez,
you're under arrest
for making me spend two
years in Earth high school!
Go! Go! Go!
We'll have to do
some creative memory
shit to get out of here.
The exit's when we
met at Birding Man
and did Senthol Diempathate.
- Damn, a great time.
- Exactly, it's too happy.
There won't be a
clean path to get there.
We'll need to build one
with memories of mine
and lily-pad our way up.
Wh-What related
memories do we share
heavy on anger and sadness?
Geardude's funeral?
Oh, that was sad.
Patris et Filii,
Gearitus Sanctis--
They're memories.
Just run them over.
- They're not real!
- Hey!
Wait, is that Gearhead?
We were freedom fighters
with his older brother.
Hugely important context.
You thought we hung
out with him for fun?
We need one more
bridge to the festival.
What's here? People in suits.
Sad catered lunch.
Newly single widows.
Something performance based?
Squanchy's very
distasteful eulogy.
Squanchy's terrible
standup phase.
That's it!
Down that way!
So you know when
you're squanching,
and she just gets real in there,
y'know that real nasty squanch?
Who are you -- What is --
Oh, my God. I'm a memory!
We just sat through all
that standup for nothing!
Almost out!
Okay, listen everybody.
My name's Rick.
This is my new friend
Bird Man and his friends.
We all just met
at this festival,
and we're so high,
we formed a band!
As if I'd ever let
you escape me.
Eh, living's overrated.
Hey!
Remember me!
No, fuck! We were even!
You got a pretty
cool memory of me.
Go-time, pal. Might
be time to do the thing.
I'm sorry for killing you
and turning you into
a cyborg, apparently.
I really did love you.
I loved you, too.
Goodbye, Tamantha.
Come on, man. I feel ridiculous!
Thank you for not
giving up on me.
Great. You can pay me
back literally right now.
Holy shit! Wow. Holy shit!
We almost didn't make it.
Jesus fuck! That was
close. That was insane.
Oh, my God. That
thing with the thing!
Thank you, Rick.
Wait, wait, wait.
Lemme hop back over to my body.
We're back, baby!
Rick and Bird Person,
a hundred years!
Whaddya think, tie this
one off -by tying one on?
- Not tonight.
I have, as you say,
"parenting shit" to deal with.
Right, yeah.
Welcome to the club.
Don't, uh... Don't clone it
and send one of
the two into space --
I guess they really hate that.
Whup, I think Memory
Rick ditched Evil Tammy
and snuck back
over into my brain.
I have a pubescent memory
of my older self in my closet.
Gotta deal with that
-- That could get ugly.
Rick, I do not like
to pull threads.
it is a disruptive
and feline activity.
But I must ask. It's
fine. You don't have to --
Was there really a second
in there where you
knew about my child,
but chose not to inform me
on the chance I might then
grow too busy child
rearing to hang out?
Oh. Uh...
Weird way to thank me
for discovering your kid.
You did not know of the child
when you came to rescue me,
and once aware,
refrained from sharing
until necessary
to save yourself.
Fair enough.
I will see you when I see you.
What? What is this guy doing?
W-Wait, what? But you said --
Get out of here, weirdo!
What a weird stranger.
Huh, what a random
thing to happen,
this guy coming up here with
all his energy storage devices.
Disloyalty acknowledged.
Nah, I get it.
Just babysitting.
That and modelling
my new pantyhose
in plain view of
the living room.
Honestly the kid could
come watch. I'd welcome it.
This cultural time period's
cool like that, y'know?
It's -- It's -- It's -- It's
not what it looks like!
It looks like you
propagated yourself
from BP's subconscious to mine
to try to live as a
sentient memory.
Fair enough!
You don't have to be an
enemy just because you exist.
I did assume you'd
hate me for trying to live.
You've got this wild
callousness thing going on.
Yeah, you're young. C'mon.
Let's bring you to
life and get a beer.
Does being real mean I
eventually become you?
I assume, yeah.
Maybe you can just
remember us getting a beer?
Improved by KID
Resynced by KID
Enjoy the movie(s) / show(s)
Hey!
Oh, fuck.
Jesus Christ.
You ever think
putting the violent ones
in the same place might
be counter-productive?
They don't pay
us to think, Phil.
No you're right, sorry.
Did you get any of that?