Got some fresh cod, whiting, bass,
dabs, conger, dogfish, coalfish...
Just cod.
Fresh cod it is, then, Doc.
Let me see now.
Not the whole fish. A half fillet.
Right.
Of course.
Yes.
No shame in cooking for one.
At least you're still shaving.
That's a good sign.
Most men get to your age with
nobody - throw in the towel.
Hygiene's always the first to go.
Like they think, 'Nobody
cares about me, I
might as well sit
around in my Y-fronts.'
Tragic it is, Doc.
You just hang on in there.
What's for you won't go by you.
Anything else?
No.
Martin.
Hello, love.
Clive!
Oh... you're not due back
till the 11th.
Well, it is the 11th.
You're a sight for sore eyes.
Oh, Clive! No, no, no. Oh, no.
Erm... I'll just put these flowers
in water.
Just wait a second, Sal.
There's something I want to say.
There's something I need to say.
I have decided to retire.
And you're to do the same.
What?
No. I'm too young to retire.
And too beautiful to stay stuck
behind the counter every day.
I want us to live, Sal,
while we still can.
Well, I thought you'd be happy.
Well...
it's just a surprise.
I mean, everything is a surprise.
Yeah.
Well, you think on about it.
I've got an appointment with the
doctor now for this damned arthritis,
so I'd best hobble on over there.
You hurry up, then. He's a busy man.
Don't want to keep him waiting.
No. Don't want to make things worse.
We're worried about the photos.
Can't show anyone the honeymoon
snaps with...
With this.
Look up.
Easy. I'm a married man now, Doc.
Can't have the wife getting jealous.
Have you being kissing
more than usual?
Well, it is our honeymoon.
It's stubble rash.
Avoid excessive kissing.
Well, what if we um...
Can't.
You need to shave at
least twice a day to
avoid exacerbating
your wife's reaction.
Well, for better or worse,
in sickness and health.
I shall shave for you, milady,
as often as is necessary.
(GIGGLES)
I had to send her home. She was
all shivering and shaking away.
Yes, but you should have checked
with me first.
It's this flu bug that's going around.
Surprised we're still standing.
But we don't have a dinner lady now.
What about tomorrow?
It's taken care of.
Really?
Yeah. I got someone to cover.
Who?
Bert Large.
There wasn't anyone else?
You're sure?
I asked around, but no.
Bert was the only one.
Hm. These notes are a mess.
Yeah. Well, the rig medic,
he gets a little er...
distracted at times.
As far as I can see, it was the jolt
from a fall that inflamed your hip,
and you felt the arthritis
for the first time.
One moment I'm on the tower,
the next I'm on the ground.
Take off your trousers over there.
Do you know who else had arthritis?
Lucille Ball.
Didn't stop her from pursuing
her dreams, though.
When I first met my Sally,
I thought she was
a dead ringer for her.
A proper beauty.
Right. Keep your left leg straight
and bend your right knee.
Straighten the right
and bend the left knee.
Hm.
Your right calf is significantly
thicker than the left.
It's swollen.
Really? I hadn't noticed it myself.
Though it has been smarting
since I took a tumble.
Bloody hell, Doc.
Give us a warning
before you start the torture.
Shouldn't be that tender.
In the infirmary, did you
take any exercise at all?
They just told me to lie there
and relax.
'Don't speak, Clive' they said.
'Don't exert yourself. Stay there.'
How many days? Pull your trousers up.
Ten.
Why? What do you think it is?
There's a possibility it's
a deep vein thrombosis,
caused by prolonged
rest, not a fall.
You need to get to the hospital
immediately. If it is a clot,
it could travel to a lung,
causing a pulmonary embolism.
I'm guessing
that's not a good thing.
A clot could block an artery to
the lungs, killing you instantly.
Bloody hell.
Not like you to abandon post.
No, I was just going back
downstairs.
How was... Doctor Ellingham?
Might be bad news.
I need to go to the hospital
for scans.
Do you ever get that feeling, Sal,
that...
one day you wake up and realise how
much of your life you've wasted?
How much you've let pass you by.
I do, yes.
Right.
I'll get the kettle on, then,
shall I?
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
Louisa.
Come in.
How are you?
Well, OK.
I don't want to keep doing this, but
I've got a bit of a problem again.
I need you to look after James
tomorrow.
Mum's still recovering from
her operation, and I can't
take him into school with
this flu going around.
And there's nobody else?
School's short staffed,
everyone's got this bug, and
I thought his father was
preferable to a stranger.
I may be wrong about that, though.
No. It's fine. Just...
I have consultations.
You have Morwenna.
It's not in her job description.
It's just one day. I have to take
the rest of the week off.
No, tomorrow is fine.
Thank you. Don't worry.
You're away in a couple of weeks.
It won't be a regular feature.
You are going to come and visit
James, aren't you? Yes.
I mean, properly. Every weekend.
Cos I don't want him
being messed around.
Every weekend would be difficult.
But most. Definitely.
And we still have his christening
to arrange.
Right. We'll see you tomorrow, then.
Good night.
Good night, James.
Bye, then.
Babysitting is not
in my job description.
Yes, I know.
(SIGHS) If I do this,
can I get a raise?
No.
A longer lunch?
Oh, come on.
At least ask me with a smile.
Morwenna.
Fine. Hand it over.
Thank you.
Act in haste, repent at leisure.
A baby's not some fashion accessory
for you young ones.
That's for life, that is.
You think this is mine? Seriously?
Look at the face.
I'd never have a baby like that.
No offence, like.
I brought my scans.
Doc's waiting for you.
Oh, that's nice.
For Clive.
You'd better stay here, Sal.
This might be bad news,
and if it is, I'd rather
you heard it from my mouth
and not some doctor's.
(BABY CRIES)
As you can see, I was right.
Deep vein thrombosis.
So...
I could drop dead any time.
Not if you begin treatment, no.
Your notes say that you can't take
Warfarin,
so a better course would be a
daily injection of Heparin.
Lift up your shirt, please.
You need to inject yourself
as close as possible to your navel.
Inject myself?
Every day.
I can't. It'd be like stabbing
myself in the belly.
No, it wouldn't.
It would.
No, it wouldn't. This will stop
your blood from clotting.
(BABY CRIES)
Maybe...
Maybe Sal could do this.
She is a medical professional...
of sorts.
She could it every day.
What are you crying about?
All you do is laze around
all day, eating and
burping, people waiting
on you hand and foot.
Sh-sh-sh-sh-sh.
You're a natural, Mrs T. Surprised
you don't have one of your own.
Could if I wanted.
Yeah. Bit late, though, now,
isn't it?
Or not.
Sal.
The doc needs you to give me
a daily injection of Heparin...
whatever that is.
Heparin comes from the ancient
Greek word hepar, which means liver.
Why have you got my baby?
James Henry was crying and I don't think
Morwenna is qualified to look after him.
And a waiting room is hardly
a suitable place for a baby.
Lots of patients coughing,
spluttering germs.
Yes. I'm very aware of that.
And I would be more than happy to
look after him for you, Doc.
Allow you to get on with your work
in peace.
Right. Good. Yes.
Erm... I'll collect him at lunch.
Lunch?
Yes.
Right, Sal. Give it a go, then.
Mr Tishell, would you?
If you... Here you go, little one.
That's right. There's a good boy.
Thank you.
Inject as close as possible
to the navel.
Good technique.
Thank you, Doc.
If you could just take it.
Thank you.
Hello, my sweetheart.
Right. That's it, then, Sal.
Homeward bound.
Doc... you're a genius.
Yes. He is.
So I will see you later, then...
Doctor.
Yes.
Brown rice? Couscous?
Bert.
Whatever happened to liver
and bacon? Toad-in-the-hole?
Our menu is organised
in advance.
You're here to cook the
food, not change the menu.
Mount Everest. 1966 World Cup.
Battle of Hastings.
You can bet those men weren't
running on rabbit food.
Actually, a vegetarian diet
provides more than enough nutrition.
Mum, what are you doing here?
What... are you all right?
Yeah, yeah. Just getting a bit
bored, lying at home, recuperating.
I thought I'd come and see
my little girl at work.
Yeah. I'm just a bit busy right now.
Too busy for your old mum?
I'm working
and I have to check on a class.
I can wait.
Vegetable fried rice?
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
Come in.
Doc.
I'm here about my eyes.
Yes, I can see that.
Think it might be a side effect
of that flu bug going round.
Do you have any flu-like symptoms?
Not really.
Then it's not that, then.
Any sensitivity to bright light?
Blurred vision? Ocular pain?
Yes, yes and...
not sure what the last one means.
But the pain bit sounds about right.
It looks like iritis to me.
I'll prescribe you some drops.
It's bloodshot in the other eye,
as well.
That's right.
So why are you wearing
a single eye patch?
Well, come on, Doc,
I'd look a bit stupid wearing
two eye patches, now, wouldn't I?
Be blind as a bat.
Mm... Needs more salt.
Ooh. Put some basil in.
You're meant to be recuperating.
Maybe you should give your
mouth a rest and all.
Louisa, tell this man to add basil.
He won't listen to me.
The children will be here soon.
Is it ready?
I need two vital ingredients.
Peace and quiet.
I heard you were putting a shift
in here.
Hello, Al.
Need a hand?
Hello, boy. It's under control.
Sure you can cook all this?
That's just what he was saying.
Oh, thank you, Al.
Mum, stop buzzing around them.
It's not your job.
Leave them to it. Come on.
Couscous?
Not exactly sticking to the menu,
son.
Improvisation is the key.
It's funny seeing you at work.
Laying down the law.
It's like you're a real teacher
or something.
I am a real teacher.
Well, you know what I mean.
Like a proper teacher.
Mum...
I know. I know.
Look, what I'm trying to say is...
You know...
I'm proud of you.
And?
That's it.
No. There's always something else.
This place has made you paranoid.
I'm leaving Portwenn.
And there we have it.
Just for a little while.
I got a really good deal online.
So when are you off?
Later on today.
What? I can't face winter here.
It goes right through your bones.
Are you planning on coming back?
Yes. Fly south for the winter,
back for the summer.
It's just that...
with Martin leaving here
as well, I wanted
to check it was OK.
I didn't want you feeling
like everyone's deserting you.
I don't.
At least, I didn't,
until you mentioned it.
It's fine.
It's gone beyond stubble rash.
Yeah. And I shaved, like you told
me. More. Three, four times.
Do you have any allergies?
Nuts. But I've been careful
not to eat any.
And duck feathers, but -
We brought our own pillows.
Any other changes?
Washing powder? Cosmetics?
No, it's like Michael always says -
I'm a creature of habit.
She really is.
I am, you know.
We were so looking forward to
taking photos, showing our friends.
Are you doing anything differently?
Well...
we did try some new er...
Positions.
..in the bedroom.
If that's what you mean.
No, it isn't.
Are you using any different products?
Right. No. No, don't think so.
The free ones.
We've been using the little
bottles you get in the
place we're in.
One of the perks of being away.
A lot of bathroom
products contain nuts.
Your wife has a nut allergy.
You should check that.
Oh, my God. The shaving cream.
I'm so sorry.
That's OK.
You can get some anti-histamine tablets
from the chemist. If symptoms persist...
We shan't be bothering you again.
We're going home today.
Yeah. Honeymoon over.
Back to the grindstone.
You're lucky, you know,
living in a place like this.
You're so, so lucky.
♪ Down will come baby
and cradle and all ♪
Found it.
Found what? Oh, dear.
The perfect one.
We don't need a car.
Not a car, a mobile home.
Why? Are you going somewhere?
Not me, Sal. Us.
This is our big chance
- out into the big,
wide world, spend some
proper time together.
Visit places we've dreamt of.
Southend-on-Sea.
Doncaster.
Peterborough.
I... I don't want to.
Why wouldn't you?
Look, I'll go scrub up and change, we'll
go out for lunch, have a nice chat.
I won't let this go, Sal.
Sometimes in this life,
if you want something,
you've got to take it.
Hello.
The doctor sent us to see you.
The doctor sent you to see me?
Oh, you're staying at the Castle?
Yeah, yeah.
Had such a wonderful time.
You ever been?
No. Never.
We were just telling the doctor
how lovely it is.
Genuinely jealous of the couple
that get to stay there next.
Such a shame the
honeymoon is over.
It doesn't have to be.
If you wish upon a star...
if you hope with all your heart...
if you believe in love,
the honeymoon can last forever.
Poetry at the pharmacy.
I love this town.
And what a lovely baby.
It's his. The doctor's.
He wanted me to leave him with me,
cos we're very close.
How much do we owe you?
No charge.
No charge at all.
Really?
Um... thank you.
That's... that's so kind of you.
No. Thank you.
What do you want?
Doc said I've got to have this.
We are closed for lunch.
No, you're not.
Oh, well, come on, then.
Got to make it quick.
Take it away.
(HORN HOOTS)
Are you hurt?
No.
I can't see a thing, Doc.
It's those eye drops you made me
get. They're a nightmare.
Let me see them.
No! This is Pilocarpine.
You were meant to take Atropine.
I just handed over the prescription.
But they're opposites.
Atropine makes the
pupils wider, Pilocarpine
makes it smaller.
He's blinded himself.
I didn't hurt anyone, did I?
I'm going to the chemist.
Come with me.
Doc...
(GIGGLING)
What a lovely couple.
Tosser!
(LAUGHTER)
What's wrong?
It's closed.
It's vital I get my eyesight back
ASAP.
She has my child. I told her I'd be
back at lunch to get him.
I'd suggest she might have taken him for
a walk, but the buggy's still in here.
Very irresponsible of her,
Leaving a baby alone like that.
Says the policeman who just drove
his car over the harbour wall.
Mrs Tishell!
Step back, Doc. This one's on me.
Ow.
Out of the way.
Mrs Tishell!
What's the bloody noise for?
Where's your wife?
Look at that door!
Who's going to pay for that?
Is your wife upstairs?
I was in the bath.
Out of the way.
Mrs Tishell?
Found these upstairs.
Paroxetine and Modafinil.
That's worrying.
Yes. It is.
Very.
Paroxetine is used to treat
social anxiety.
Modafinil has sometimes been marketed as
an intelligence drug. Taken together...
So basically...
there's a drugged-up lunatic
on the run with your baby.
When did you last see her?
About 15, 20 minutes ago.
Did she have my baby with her?
Yeah, she did.
Martin, she left a note.
Dear Martin, I got your message.
I will meet you at the Castle.
I think you'd better tell me
what's been going on, Doc.
What do you mean?
My Sal, she's an attractive woman.
Alone here, while I'm away
on the rigs.
Don't be ridiculous.
Did you send her a message?
No.
What castle?
I don't know.
Maybe she means the Castle.
What?
The Castle Hotel. Most folk call it
the Castle.
Where is it?
I know the way.
You can't go charging off
without telling Louisa.
Yes, I know that.
(SHOUTING)
It's chaos here. They haven't been fed.
They've been waiting for half an hour.
Everyone, I've told you. Be quiet.
Please just tell me
if the food's ready.
Any minute now.
I told you. Nothing to worry about.
Over here. Let's dish it up.
A bit overdone.
(CHILDREN GROAN)
Just a tiny problem.
Bert. We could buy some oven chips,
shove 'em in, ten minutes.
No. There are strict guidelines
concerning the children's diet.
Louisa.
Can I speak to you?
Excuse me.
Is something wrong?
I wondered if Mrs Tishell had been
in contact with you.
No. Why?
She was looking after James
for a little while.
And she seems to have disappeared.
What?
It's nothing to worry about.
You gave our baby to Mrs Tishell?
I think we both agree
that Mrs Tishell is
a more responsible
person than Morwenna.
So where's our baby?
I have reason to believe she took
him to the Castle Hotel.
Why?
She wants me to meet her there.
What? But why?
She's been self-prescribing a
combination of drugs and...
seems to have formed
a fixation on me.
Right. I'm coming with you.
You're in charge.
Right.
Who'd like some chips?
(CHEERING)
She doesn't look very happy.
No.
Bet the doc's in trouble.
Yes.
She probably wants to kill him.
♪ The wheels on the bus
go round and round
♪ Round and round, round and round
♪ The wheels on the bus
go round and round
♪ All day long ♪
Oh, that's a lovely one.
Yes.
Me and his father are very happy
together.
Well, you have been blessed,
haven't you?
Yes. We have.
We have been blessed.
Stop staring at my baby.
Get your own.
Don't worry, Louisa.
We'll get your baby back.
Every man has a moment
where he becomes a hero.
I won't let you down.
Joe, please. You're giving me
a headache and it's not helping.
Just trying to reassure you.
Your baby will be OK.
And how do you know that?
Because of the one thing
a policeman can always
rely on - his instinct.
Isn't that right?
Much as I'd love to agree with you
and say the child is safe,
none of us knows what
psychological state Mrs
Tishell is in and what
she's capable of,
especially if put in a situation
where she feels threatened.
She has newspaper cuttings about me
pinned up inside her wardrobe.
You mean, like some sort of shrine?
Yes.
You've got to be joking.
Women, eh? (LAUGHS)
It's understandable to
be worried, Louisa.
If you need to cry or...
eat something...
I won't waste my energy
getting wound up.
We'll find her and
get our baby back.
Tishell. T-I-S-H-E-L-L.
She has our baby.
Neck brace.
Carrying a baby.
Past childbearing age.
Acting erratically.
I've not seen anyone like that.
Has anyone checked in
in the last hour with a baby?
I'd need to get permission.
You need to tell us if anyone has
checked in with a baby. Yes or no?
The duty manager's busy.
We've got a wedding.
I am two seconds away from charging
you with wasting police time.
That's not helping.
I'm doing my best.
This is ridiculous. Both of you,
stop bullying him.
And you, stop snivelling.
A child may be in danger.
So grow a backbone, check
that damn machine, and
tell us whether a woman has
checked in with a baby.
Right.
Yeah. About an hour ago.
A Ms Smith checked in.
Requested a baby cot.
Room 117.
Ms Smith. An alias if ever
I've heard one.
Does she fit our description?
I didn't check her in.
Give me the keys.
We're really not meant to.
Please.
(MOUTHS SILENTLY)
Mrs Tishell?
Empty. Almost too empty.
She must be somewhere else.
Where, though? There's two
restaurants and cellars and grounds.
She's obviously not thinking
rationally. She could be anywhere.
Ms Smith was marked as joining
the Edmondson party downstairs.
Why didn't you say so before,
you imbecile?
Please wait, sir!
Mrs Tishell!
Police! Nobody move.
Where are you, Mrs Tishell?
Or should I say, Ms Smith?
Uh... hello?
(MOBILE PHONE RINGS)
It's her!
Be calm, Martin. You don't want to
upset her.
I know.
Don't bark at her.
I'm not going to.
I've had training for this.
Where are you?
Don't worry. I'm waiting for you.
So clever to send that lovely
couple to tell me where to go.
I'm here. I'm in the hotel. Come down
to reception with the baby - now.
Hotel?
Oh...
Oh, Dr Ellingham, you're
playing games with
me, aren't you? Ooh!
I'll see you soon.
Just tell me where you are.
What did she say? Did she mention
the baby?
She's not here. She said something about
a couple to show her where to go.
A couple of what?
A couple. People.
What people? I don't know.
Stop asking inane questions.
Doc...
Be quiet.
I passed a couple before,
coming out of the chemist.
Could only have been 15 minutes
or so before Mrs T disappeared.
Woman had a red, blotchy face.
Might be nothing, but...
Stubble rash.
Martin...
Shush.
I'm supposed to be in Bude
by three o'clock.
He should be back here any minute.
Well, you told us that
15 minutes ago.
(PHONE RINGS)
Yes? Doc.
You're about to have a full scale
riot on your hands here.
All right. Take it down a notch.
Let me check.
Michael and Mallory Wilson.
Renting that holiday place
up at Carmore Point.
Pentire Castle.
James Henry.
Oh.
I could have sworn I...
Oh! Oh...
Oh.
Doctor wouldn't be happy if I lost
our child now, would he, now?
No, he wouldn't.
You good little boy.
I think it best that you stay here.
I'm police. I have to be there.
You wait.
I actually have experience of this
kind of thing.
Village Fete, 2003, ring any bells?
Of course it doesn't.
Pig of the Year contest.
Turned nasty, till I stepped in.
How wonderfully reassuring.
I may have to get a little
harsh with Mrs Tishell.
Hostage situations
are like that.
I'd rather you just kept quiet.
Or maybe softly-softly. 'Trust me,
Mrs T. I'm on your side.'
You do realise we're dealing
with a highly volatile person?
There's no knowing how she'll react.
You're not playing in a Hollywood film.
You're not Clint Eastwood.
Of course I'm not.
Just you wait, little one.
Any minute now. Knock, knock, knock.
And my Romeo will have come.
It is the east,
and Juliet is the sun.
Doc...
You can't just barge in.
If she gets a hint that
something's amiss, you
could endanger the child.
Do you expect me to knock
and politely wait?
She's right. You have to stay calm,
for James Henry's sake.
Mrs Tishell!
Martin.
Don't alarm her. She's not herself.
Yes, I'm well aware of that.
Then why bang on the door
like a madman?
And you both arguing about it is
going to take us so much farther (!)
(KNOCKS) Mrs Tishell?
Hello?
Doctor?
Doctor!
Oh, you came.
All this way, alone.
I knew you would.
Just bring the baby down here now.
Oh, you almost sound angry.
Martin, let her think you're happy
to be here.
No. Delusions are only reinforced by
pretending you think they're real.
I don't care about her.
I just want my baby back.
Why don't you just come down here
and we can talk about it.
I don't want to get hurt.
My poor heart couldn't take it.
Nobody's going to hurt you.
Bring the baby downstairs.
The first day you came to town,
everything changed.
Yes, I realise that, Mrs Tishell.
I mean, I... I've been waiting
for you so long,
while you've been running around
with that school teacher trollop.
One moment you're together,
then you're not,
then you're getting married,
then you're not, then she's gone,
then you're going, but you don't,
and then you have a baby
and you're living together
and then you're not, and
then you're going away and
I can't stand it anymore!
Mrs Tishell, you have been taking a
combination of Paroxetine and Modafinil,
and as a result, you're having
a psychotic episode.
No! It's allowed me to feel free!
To be smarter.
I've never seen anything so clearly.
I see everything.
My hopes, my dreams, our future.
You called the police!
No, I didn't.
Yes. Well, then, why is PC Penhale
standing there, then?
No, no, no, no.
No, this won't do.
No, this is wrong.
You lied to me.
No, I didn't.
I wanted him here because I...
What?
Because...
(Share our wonderful love.)
No. Let her know you're
concerned about her
and she needs help.
Let her know you care.
And you love her.
That won't help.
I wanted him PC Penhale here
because...
I wanted to share our wonderful love.
What, you mean...
you want everyone to know?
What - how you feel about me?
Yes. That.
Really, Doctor Ellingham?
Yes, really.
I always thought you saw me
as an intelligent person.
I do.
As an intellectual equal.
Absolutely.
Then why are you telling me
all these lies?
I'm not.
If you wanted to tell me how you
felt, why have you waited so long?
You've had so many chances.
So, so many chances.
Tell her to come down
so that you can talk about it.
No, no! you need to convince her
that you really do care.
Why, Doctor?
You know nothing about psychology.
Tell her you know you're a difficult
person.
What?
Tell her you're a difficult person.
I'm a difficult person.
And I waited so long because I'm...
an idiot.
I think I've how I felt since
the first time I met you...
From the first time I saw you.
And I know I'm hard to talk to
sometimes.
I'm aware of that.
And I do hate Portwenn.
I hate the people.
Their pinched faces
and their ridiculous accents,
and their unerring
knack of catching any
virus that comes within
a five-mile radius,
then spread contagion like
a bush fire.
But it's where I want to be.
Because you're here.
Because of you.
Because if I'm with you...
nothing else matters.
What I'm trying to say is...
I love you.
Oh, Martin!
I love you too.
Why don't you come down here
and be with me?
Give me one last chance.
Please.
That poor, deranged woman will probably
throw herself out of the window now,
as an expression of her love.
I think she's coming down.
Oh...
Oh. Oh.
Why is she here?
Because you took my baby.
No, no, no, no, no.
You're meant to be with me.
This isn't how the fairytale ends.
It's the handsome prince and the...
The erm...
The married pharmacist
who needs to come with
me because she's suffered
a psychotic episode
brought on by excessive
dosage of prescription drugs.
Doctor?
You must go with this Dr Ellingham, who
will give you anti-psychotic medication
to counteract the effects
of the drugs you've taken.
I don't think you understand
what love is.
What?
Don't worry.
Just a bit of a tumble.
I'll be OK, probably.
Mrs Tishell, I'm arresting you
for kidnapping a minor.
No, you're not. She's ill.
She needs help.
Don't know why I bother
getting these things out.
Help me get her to the car.
I called her husband.
He's on his way.
Clive?
Don't worry. You'll see him soon.
No. Dr Ellingham!
I'll wait for you.
Does he seem all right?
I think he's fine.
He seems fine.
Did you mean what you said
about staying here? Or was that...
No, I meant it. All of it.
I've waited so long to hear you say
nice things.
And I'd given up.
I'd completely given up.
And then to hear you say them
today... to someone else...
It doesn't matter.
No, it does to me.
No. I mean, everything.
What school James goes to. London.
None of it matters to me.
I'm not going to be like my father.
And he's not going to be like me.
And I do love you.
Say it again.
I've already said it twice.
I know, but... say it again, anyway.
I will always -
Sorry, guys.
I must have dropped my police radio
when I jumped from the balcony,
and well... they make you pay
for them if you lose them.
So er... you carry on.
Hm.
Subtitles by APOLLO
www.addic7ed.com