Mom! We're gonna
miss the movie!
No, we're not.Okay, but we've
been here for hours.
I-I don't want to hang out
at the stupid horse hospital.
This stupid horse hospital
puts dinner on your table.
It wouldn't kill you
to take an interest.
W-What's this thing?
I-In the middle of the room?
With -- With the hole
in the end?
That's a breeding mount.
The nurses use it to collect...
reproductive material.
[ Click, whirring ]
[ Squishing ]
[ Click, whirring stops ]
Okay, let's go see this
latest piece of Marvel shit
you kids are jizzing over.
Yeah.
A-About time.
So, d-does your hospital
ever need, like,
after-school
volunteers?
Wow. Who are you and
where did you put my son?
Ha! No, no. Seriously.
I-I'm very interested
in -- in your work.
[ Birds chirping ]
[ Sighs ]
Morty, you dirty little doggy.
[ Liquid sloshing ]
Ugh! Come on!
[ Grunting ]
[ Liquid sloshing ]
Hey, Rick.
Oh, hey, kiddo.
How's your Saturday?
You know, super chill.
W-W-Whatcha doin'?
Eh, nothing adventurous.
You know that race of
Underground Dwelling Cannibal
Horse People that
we're always fighting?
Yeah, the CHUDs.
W-W-What about 'em?
Well, don't tell anybody,
but I'm working on
a bioweapon
to use against them,
so I got this barrel of horse
semen from your mom's hospital
and I'm just gonna,
you know,
subject it to
some otherworldly forces.
Guess I should test it,
make sure it's --
Make sure it's what?!Horse semen, obviously.
Okay, but it says it is
right on the barrel!
You're not being
very scientific, Morty.
Measure twice, cut once.
Especially with semen.
Did you even ask Mom
if you could have this?!
Morty, if I wanted
to steal horse semen, I'd --
Yes, I asked her.
What is at stake for you here?
Why don't you trust labels?!All right! Fine!
I won't test it!
God damn. Your generation really
picks random hills to die on.
Don't get too close.
I'm running an inhuman amount
of power through this semen.
Should be safe, though,
since the semen itself is,
you know, also inhuman.
Here we go.
[ Crackling ]
[ High-pitched whine ]
[ Rumbling ]
[ Creature growling ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Snarling ]
[ Glass shattering ]
W-What happened?!
The sperm, Morty!
They're super monster sperm now!
I blame myself.
Unless there was something
about the sperm I didn't know.
Are you -- Are you saying
that to mess with me?
What?
Mess with you how?
Like, trying to get me
to say something?
Morty, I have no idea
what you're talking about!
For real?
Yes!
Okay. Good.
Then -- Then it's your fault!
♪♪
Beth: Dad, what the hell
is going on?!
Beth, sweetheart,
Can you give me a minute?
I'm trying to steer around
the bodies of our neighbors.
[ Thump ]Oh, that felt like Gene.
That's on you, Beth.Dad, I swear--
Mom, it's -- it's not
Rick's fault, it's --
Space Sperm.
What?!
Yeah.
Space Sperm.
I-I've seen em' before,
but n-n-never like this.
SpaceSperm?!
Sperm from Space?
Very impressive verbal
forensic work, Jerry.
Holy shit.
How big are space dicks?
Don't answer that!
Damn, they must be huge.
[ Tires screeching ]
Oh!
[ Laser pistol zapping ]
Oh, shit,
oh, shit, shit.
[ Roaring ]
[ Snarling ][ Pistol clicks ]
Mr. Sanchez!
The President is very eager
to speak with you!
Morty, look,
you gotta do me a solid here.
Y-you want me to keep the secret
of where these things came from?
Yes, technically, it's a lie,
but I messed up,
and I'm embarrassed 'cause it's,
you know, science.
No problem.
I got your back, dawg.
Really? Okay. Cool.
And thanks, Morty.
I thought that'd be
a harder sell.
Y-You did a shameful thing.
Dwelling on it isn't gonna
help, you know, am I right?
Sometimes you just gotta
wipe it off,
toss it in the trash,
and head back to study hall.
Uh, not getting the metaphor
but I'll take your hall pass.
Sanchez!
Get the hell in here!
Space Sperm?
Jesus, how big
are space dicks?Same page club.
Well, Mr. President,
the theory of Cosmic DNA
has been around for decades --
Chupacabras, Yeti,
Stonehenge, Ancient Rome.
Are these all myths,
monsters, legends,
or different names
for sperm from outer space?
I'll tell you what I think,
Sanchez.
I think either
youcaused this mess,
or it's those godforsaken Horse
People that dwell underground.
CHUDs.CHUDs.That's them.
Ugh, if they're behind this,
so help me, God.
Morty, you've always been
a straight shooter.
You can't prove that!
Wait, what?
Oh -- oh. Right.I can protect you,
little man.
Blow that whistle.
Toot, toot.
Is this
your grandpa's fault?
Here's what I know, sir.
This is the greatest country
on Earth.
It invented apple pies
and lasers.
Mm. Keep talking.And that sperm...
We don't know
nothin' about it.
Then the CHUDs
just got themselves a war.
And you just dodged
a personal drone strike.
Hello! Hello.
Sorry, I'm late.
This is Professor Shabooboo, the
world's leading expert on sperm.
Thanks for getting here
so fast.My schedule was wide open.
I have been tracking
our new sperm friends
since their arrival,
a-and if my calculations
are correct,
they have gathered here.
Why would the sperm
go to the Grand Canyon?
Why are you looking at me
like the answer is obvious?
Oh, you can't be serious.
Are we in middle school?
You think sperm
are instinctively
heading for America's --Don't high-road us, lady.
It's where they went.
Now, how do we deal
with these...
"Orgasogoblins"?
No takers?
Okay. These...
"Cumplestiltskins?"
No? Dumb?
These, uh, "Skeet Boogins?"
Oh, yeah, yeah,
Skeet Boogins.
Really?
Skeet Boogins?
We'll use it as a placeholder
and beat it later.
Mr. President, i-if I may?
Luckily, I was able
to secure a specimen.
Now, obviously our first steps
will be to analyze its DNA
and figure out what
these beautiful creat--
Oh, why?!It-it had a gun!
Are you out of your mind
bringing an armed sperm in here?
But they can't holdguns!
The boy literally
never lies!
Look, if you want
these things gone,
give Rick and me a plane
and some nukes.
We'll wipe 'em out
and leave no trace of them.
Only one way
to deal with it.
He's right.
[Burps] I'm a scientist.
Fair enough.
Blow 'em to hell.
What are people gonna do,
complain we made
the canyon grander?
Jerry, we're being bad parents.
Do something!
I-is this water
for everyone?
Yes, and I'd love a glass.Comin' up!
What are youdoing?
And, Rick, to make sure
you don't screw anything up,
I'm sending
my best men with you.
And women.It's a fine suggestion,
but I doubt their leader
will be a sexy queen
that needs to be kickboxed.
100% male Marines!
They say cutting
a sperm's throat is like
running a warm knife
through butter.
I'm gonna make these things
pregnant...with death!
No fear!No humility!
Both:
Zero chance of consequences!
Hey, gentlemen's bet -- which
of these background Marines
you think will last
the longest?
I'm not betting on
human lives, Rick.
All of these people
are gonna survive,
but obviously that guy
the longest.
Yeah, he's my pick, too.
What's his name?
Blazen? Pretty cool.
Yeah. He's, like, meditating
through turbulence.
Psh. I bet if
something fell,
he'd like, catch it
without opening his eyes.
Totally.
Should we throw
something at him?
I-I got a pencil somewhere.
[ Both scream ]
[ Marines screaming ]
Who-who's shooting at us?!
Oh, wow, that's unexpected.
The sperm made a catapult?!
A-A-Are they getting
smarter?!
No, you're getting dumber
because that's a trebuchet.
Nobody knows
the difference!
They're reloading
that textbook trebuchet!
Time to fly!Aaaaaah!
Oh!
♪♪
We gotta keep moving.
So cool.Not even a scratch.
Okay, girls, and I mean
that derogatorily.
We just took a fat "L,"
and what we need is a fat "P."
A plan.
I take the lead here.
You two watch the flanks.
Blazen, bring up the-- Hey!
Please, one person
draws the plan!
Skeeters!
-Jipers!
-Ropers!
I'm sorry, but what the hell
are we calling them?
Agh! Oof.
Fine. I'm dying,
so I get to pick the name.
Crispy Cremes with a "C"!
Whoa!
[ Grunting ]
[ Snarling ]
Whoa. E-Easy there, little guy.
It's okay.
I-I-It's okay.
Do you...recognize me?
Do you know you
came from me?
I'm Morty.
I'll call ya "Sticky,"
'c-'cause you're sticky
and -- and you're stuck.
Oh. [ Chuckles ][ Purring ]
Step aside, Morty.
It's okay.
Y-You don't gotta do this.
It's haploid genetic code,
Morty,
a biological
fertilizing machine.
W-What's gotten into you?
Rick, let him go.
Ugh.
Morty, don't fuck
with me.
What the hell's
going on with you?
I think I know exactly
what's going on here.
Kidding.
This shit is totally random.
Let's keep moving.W-Which way?
[ Inhales deeply ]
When one sense is bound,
the others are released.
[ Sniffing ]
Holy shit.
He -- He can smell caves?
I'm not trying
to smell anything.
The whole planet's
a dorm room trash can.
Sir, Rick Sanchez
has gone dark.
I knew we couldn't
rely on him!
Well, maybe the pilot
got too horny
as they approached
America's Vagina.
If you're gonna hang out
in my war room,
you can't just
make snarky comments.
At least do something useful,
like Jerry.
Right to the top,
just the way you like it.
Here's our situation.
Rick's gone,
and so are all our nukes.
Now what?
None of you have an idea?I do.
That's right, me --
the girl.
Gentlemen,
what do sperm want?
The same thing as a lumberjack
in the morning
or a fox at night.
Pants!Eggs.
Pancakes!Eggs.
You want to control giant sperm,
you need a giant egg.
W-W-Wait a minute.
Wait -- wait a minute.
Sperm are hunters.
And what do sperm hunt?
Eggs.
Exactly.
And what would happen
if we enlargedone?
They'll head right for it!
Get MIT on the phone.
And get this guy
a Nobel Prize.
[ Applause and laughter ]You became a woman today.
[ Ominous music plays ]
[ Devices whirring ]
So, Blazen, you got kids?
The battlefield is
myfamily.
So cool.Wicked badass.
[ Sperm snarling ]Go.
I'll hold 'em off.
Blazen, you don't
have to do this.
Shh.
It is my destiny.
He's right, Morty.
It's the price of being Blazen.
Let him do his thing.
[ Sperm snarling ][ Grunts ]
Blood for blood.
Cream for cream.
[ Grunts ]
Oh, no.
I can't reach that!
Idiot!
What?!
They're comfortable!
You should try them!
Eh, ah! Ohhhh.
That'll do it.
I'm worm food.
Morty, find my wife.
[ Straining ] Tell her I wasn't
wearing her thong.
That's a photocopy
of "Sports Illustrated"
swimsuit model
Kathy Ireland.
It's -- it's my wife.
We have sex.
Here, hold that picture up so
we can have sex one last time.
I-I know how to
suck myself.
What?![ Sperm roaring ]
Ugh, I was so wrong
about this guy.
He didn't even
buy us any time.
[ Sperm snarling ]
Morty, get ready
for some fireworks.
[ Beep ]
Ugh!
Uh-oh.Oh, gross!
This is the first time I've ever
regretted being taken alive.
Wait, who the fuck
is that?!
Silence in the presence
of me.
I am The Sperm Queen,
and youare of
special interest to me.
Hey, what the fuck are you
doing with my stuff?
A-And why do you have
the horse jerkoff machine
from my daughter's hospital?
We need it
to create our army.
Well, you need more than that,
dummy. You need a horse.
Oh but our stallion
is already here.
Isn't that right, Morty?
Or shall I say...
Father?
Morty, you nasty, lying,
little world-ending pervert.
I-I-I'm sorry.
[ Sobbing ]
What was it like?Fantastic!
Rick, I'm sorry!
I-I just thought maybe
I could have repeated sex
with a horse machine
without it becoming Armageddon.
I-I realize that's on me.
Yeah, not exactly
accepting apologies
while I'm stuck here
as Handjob Solo.
This is all your fault
for being ashamed of us, Morty.
How many millions went
to their graves for you,
hurling themselves
into the void,
only to discover
a grody sock
or a carefully folded
landing strip of toilet paper?
How do you know all this?!
Oh, honey, because we're
the very essence of you.
We are
your shame incarnate.
And once we're through
with you,
our sperm army
will take over the world!
Put him on the machine![ Machine whirring ]
Rick, do something!On it.
[ Grunting ]
Wh-what did you do?I got out of your eyeline.
Oh, no. Oh! Oh!
Yes!
The end is near!
Any last words?
Ohhh![ Explosion ]
Sticky!
Gross.
I know you're not a wordsmith,
Morty, but --
No, no, no, my-my sperm friend
is here!
Ugh, never give 'em
a name.
♪♪
Fools!
You can't beat me!
You didn't bring a woman
that can kickbox!
[ Grunts ]
Is that all you got?
Damn, that's some quintessential
underdog shit.
Kill them!
[ Sperm roaring ]
[ Groans ]
[ Coughs ]
Yeah! Whoo-hoo!
I-I should've told you
the truth, Rick.
Let's save the world first.
Now, reset those nukes,
and let's turn this canyon
into a can't-yon.
[ Device whirring ]
There usually earthquakes
in Arizona?
[ Roaring in distance ]
They're heading for Vegas,
which doestrack on many levels,
but why now?
What the?
President: Let's hear it
for Professor Shabooboo
and his brilliant egg.Um, hello?
Aren't you
forgetting someone?Oh, good point.
Big thanks to the cast
of Cirque Du Soleil's "Zumanity"
for the impressive
and erotic routine.
Mr. President,
Rick Sanchez is on the line.
Good.
Put that asshole on speaker.
Well, well, well.
No thanks to you,
we're luring the sperm
with a giant human egg,
even though,
symbolically speaking,
Vegas should be enough.
Rick: A human egg?
Where-where-where
did you get it?
Glad you asked.
It's your granddaughter's,
so at least you contributed
somethingto this.
Morty: Mister President!
It's Morty!
It's my sperm!
I-It's all mine!
What?! I'm a dirty little
perverted maniac.
I spent a week pleasuring myself
with animal equipment,
and my sperm got turned
into monsters on accident
because I kept lying about it
because I was ashamed!
You should be!
My God, man,
we were all 14 once
but it's called
self-control.
Don't let them reach my
sister's egg, Mr. President!
You'll be making a giant --
Incest baby.
What?
Who told you that?
I-I was finishing his sentence.
Oh. Right.
Come with us.
The sperm is Morty's!
We're about to make
a giant incest baby!
Aw, well, now we're all
in our darkest hour.
Launch the egg!
Launch it now!
B-But that'll take
30 minutes.What?! Why?!
That's how long
every space launch takes!
No one realizes because
they only show you
the last 10 seconds!
Uh, uh, help me out here.
Hey, it was your idea,
right?
Okay, okay, n-no need to panic,
everyone.
I have a simple solution.
See you all in hell!
[ Splat ]I don't see how
that'sgoing to help.
Form a perimeter!
Protect that egg at all costs!
I always knew your hormones
would cause a world war
between humans
and Cannibalistic Horse People.
I just didn't know
it would be like this.
I can't change my nature.
What are you, a scorpion
in a Navajo fable?
Everyone can change
their nature, Morty.
It's what defines
our species.
Look at Iron Man.
That actor was an animal
in the '90s,
literally waking up
in bushes.
His agent had to catch him
with a butterfly net.Silence!
Rick Sanchez,
you know why you're here.
Yeah, it was
my grandson's fault.
You slept
with my daughter!I did?
Oh, shit, I did.
[ Belches ] Forgive me,
Your CHUDness.
I'm a changed man
starting now.
You come to the Kingdom of CHUDs
for forgiveness?
CHUDs don't forgive humans.
CHUDs eathumans!
This is out there,
even for us.
They can hear you, Morty.
All: Boil him up!
Yum, yum!
Spice him right!
Oh, boy!
Eat the flesh!
Yum, yum!
Not the bones!
Oh, no!
Belly ache!
Ouch, Ouch!
Father! [Whinnies]
Stop this at once!
Princess Poñeta!You can't kill Rícko!
I -- I love him!
[ Crowd gasping ]
Right! I-I love you, too,
Princess Poñeta.
This love is forbidden.
My daughter,
you are a CHUD.
Rick is a human [whinnies]
and age-inappropriate.
Then you leave me
nochoice.
By the 17th Article
of the CHUD-stitution,
I offer Rícko Sanchez
horsemunity
and demand a equestri-truce
between all CHUDs and humans!
[ Crowd gasping ]On what grounds?
On the grounds that Rícko
is the father of my child.
I have an heir.
I have a substance-abuse
problem.
The Prophecy has come true!
Also, did someone drop
a scroll?
Here we go. Over here.
[ Whinnies ] Sorry.
♪♪
Where did you get
all that?
-It's Vegas.
-Sir!
The Strip has been evacuated,
but I'm worried
we won't be able
to hold the perimeter.
Then deputize
Las Vegas regulars.
Everyone's a patriot today.
Even me!
Take three steps back,
Amazing Johnathan.
Men and their guns.
Metaphorical and not.
Tell me about it.
Get ready, boys!
The last thing this world needs
is a giant incest baby.
-Oorah! Here they come!
-Nice!
Do not let a single sperm
get through to that egg!
[ Gunfire ]
Um, should we be concerned
about that scary bomb-laden one?
Honey, let the men
handle this.
I think we know
a thing or two about --
Ugh! Ready for
all the responsibility
with none of the credit?
Let's Nancy Reagan
this bitch.
Ah!
♪♪
[ Grunting ]
Dammit!
We can't stop them.
We don't have the manpower!
Rick:
What about horsepower?
[ Whinnying ]
Sweet Lady Liberty.
That sonofamare Rick has ended
our centuries-long war
with the CHUDs.
-We made peace with the CHUDs!
-The CHUDs are our buds!
[ Sperm roaring ]
Rícko! The hoofless --
they need us!
Let's do this.
CHUDily dudily, ho, ho, ho!
CHUDs:
♪♪
Mom, I promise to use condoms,
even when it's butt stuff.
Okay, we have a lot
to talk about tonight.
♪♪
Is this your heart?
It's a play on,
"Is this your card?"
You don't have a heart,
uh, but this is probably
some kind of organelle,
in charge of pumping
endoplasmic reticulum
throughout your membrane
and therefore,
relative to you,
functions asa heart.
So, I ask you again,
is thisyour heart?
[ Gasps ]
Morty, look!
I won't just be thrown away,
Rick!
The egg is mine!
Sticky!
It's all you, bud!
♪♪
Noooo!
[ Crowd cheering ]Sticky!
[ All gasping ]Fuck!
We got a heartbeat.Screw that!
That's a human life,
and this is an election cycle.
You have to do something!Nope.
[ Beeping, rumbling ]
It's space's problem now.
Oh, this sucks.
You're "Sports Illustrated"'s
Kathy Ireland.
You were with my husband,
Blazen, when he died.
Please tell me...
was he wearing my thong?
He probably told you
not to tell me.
He was ashamed of it,
but he didn't need to be.
I hope he waswearing it.
Always be honest.
Sometimes it will
hurt people.
Sometimes it will help.
But always be honest.
Huh. Yeah, yeah,
he -- he waswearing it.
Ew!
That gross animal pig!
So, trying to boil this
all down,
I-I want to say
it's import--
Shut up, Morty,
I got my own epilogue.
Oh, Rícko,
I love you.
[ Burps ] Prove it.
[ Smacking and heavy breathing ]
Oh, I love kissing those
big ol' horse teeth.
It's like lickin' tile.
Oh!
I swear...
it's time someone made
an honest man out of me.
Whatever you need,
the whole nine yards,
you got it.[ Whinnies ]
The thing is, Rícko...
it's time.
Oh, shit, oh, shit.
It's time!
Oh, my God,
it's wonderful.
[ Groans ][ Splat ]
[ Whinnies ]
Oh, wow. So we don't have to,
you know, r-raise it?
Nah. They're ready to go
right out of the box.
Cool, cool.
So...bye?
Yep.
Take care of yourself, Rick.
Yep. Same.
[ Whinnies ]
That was easy.
♪♪
Houston, permission to open
the starboard panel.
Houston:
Permission granted.
Firing breach now.
Explorer, our readouts
show a pressure spike.
Everything alright?
Honestly, sometimes
staring back at Earth
makes me think about
the people I left behind --
my wife, the son she had
to anchor me there.
I tried to be a parent,
I really did,
but I've come to find I'm only
suited to be a spaceman.
The nicest part
of being up here
is there are no reminders
of the guilt
I sometimes feel about
abandoning my family.
[ Indistinct babbling ]
Sorry, Houston,
I thought I heard something.
Negative on our end.
No, wait,
there's something big
and it's coming right at you!Goo, goo, gah, gah.
Dear God.
No! You can't be real!
Explorer, what is it?
What the hell do you see?!
My conscience.
Explorer! Explorer!Aaah!
Are you there?Aaaaaah!
Geez.
Not gonna miss that guy.Aaaaah!
Right? So dramatic.
Man:
Did you get any of that?
♪♪