All right, Norman. Let's go to work.
Oh, Dr Ellingham...
Oh, can I just say...
I think you made the right decision.
About you and Louisa Glasson -
never meant to be.
What's happened to your face?
My face? Nothing.
Oh, unless you mean my new lipstick.
I thought I'd try a different shade.
Right.
And you probably noticed
my hair too. No.
Oh, Dr Ellingham, always teasing me!
(NERVOUS LAUGH)
See you later.
When I first opened the sanctuary, I
got maybe one unwanted cat a month.
Now I get two or three a week.
Is that right?
Which is why this fundraising
evening is so important to me.
Yeah. You keep saying.
So I hope you've bought
plenty of food and drink.
I'll get it when you've paid me.
Paid you?
I've told you,
I need the money up front.
You said there'd be no cost.
I said the wine would be AT COST.
If you think I'm going to give you
a whole lot of free food and wine,
you're barking up the wrong tree.
Well, I'll have to cancel
the evening.
Well, I'm sorry, but times are hard.
They are, if you're a cat!
I don't know how
I'm going to feed the poor things.
I mean, are you quite sure...?
Ow!
Here, Doc, Doc! Hang on.
I need your help. It's Mrs Dingley.
She's come a cropper.
Ohh! Ow!
Shush! It's nothing serious.
Just put a bag of ice on it.
Do you have any ice?
Some.
Not a lot.
Could you fetch it, please?
If the pain gets any worse,
come and see me in the surgery.
Oh, right.
Oh, Doctor.
Do you think I could ask...?
If you pester me for a donation,
the answer's still no.
Well, you can't blame me for trying.
Yes, I can.
Miserable bugger.
I heard that.
So you'll go to Clappy-Time
at the library? Yeah, maybe.
Or Sing-Along-Susie
at the Harbour Cafe.
Well, we are spoilt for choice,
aren't we, Jim-Jim?
It's James.
(SCHOOL BELL)
I have to go. You will find
something nice to do, won't you?
Yes, I expect so.
Aw, bye-bye, darling. Be a good boy.
Go!
Hey! Inside!
Looks like you're busy.
But you're going to come in anyway.
Are you here as a patient?
Yes and no.
Are you considering
changing your mind about Louisa?
No.
So, as your doctor,
what can I do for you?
I've run out of Oralube.
You could have telephoned
for a repeat prescription.
I assumed you'd want to see me.
My symptoms might have changed,
my condition deteriorated.
Has your condition deteriorated?
Not in the least.
So... you're going up to London
as planned,
and Louisa will stay here
with the child?
Yes.
Good.
You parents stayed together
for your sake.
No-one got out unscathed.
We don't want a repeat of that.
Well, this has been fun (!)
If you want to discuss it further,
Martin,
you know where I am.
Thank you.
Hello, there.
We're looking for Bert Large.
He's around somewhere.
OK, we'll sit here
and you can run inside
and fetch him for us, yeah?
What do you want?
Oh, where are my manners?
I'm Alastair Tonken.
And this here is
my little boy Norman.
All right?
You work here, do you?
Off and on.
Oh! There he is.
Hello, Bert. (CHUCKLES)
Lovely to see you again.
You can probably guess
what we're here for, I'm sure.
Can we talk about it somewhere else?
No. Here is quite nice,
thank you, Bert.
All I want to know is -
have you got it? (MOUTHS)
Got what?
What's he on about, Dad?
Dad?
Your dad has borrowed £1,000.
You what?
Ah, don't worry.
He can probably pay it back.
The only thing is that if he can't,
then there might be some of those -
oh, what do you call them?
What is the word I'm looking for?
Repercussions.
That's it. Yeah. There might
have to be some repercussions.
You didn't see the sign?
Says you shouldn't
park in the harbour
when the tide's in.
If we had seen the sign, we never
would have parked in the harbour.
Couldn't get near the car last
night. The water was up to here.
So you just left the vehicle
where it was? No!
We drove it away and
we put it back there just now (!)
Of course we left it where it was!
Was anything stolen?
No. Somebody smashed the back window
and fiddled with my wife's clothing.
You didn't put your wife's clothing
in the boot?
It's just a coat.
Real fur, though.
Fox, not mink.
You went to a loan shark?
That's not what he calls himself.
But you know that's what he is.
And if we can't pay him back,
there's going to be repercussions.
Come on, that could mean anything.
Exactly. And you saw Norman.
If he wants to smash up the
restaurant, who's going to stop him?
OK, things don't look good
right now.
You told me, Dad,
you said you went to the bank.
I admit I've been economical
with the truth.
It's a shame you weren't
economical with anything else
because we're going to go bankrupt!
Well, if you hadn't spent
all that time with Ruth,
instead of helping me here.
So now it's my fault?
I'm not saying that.
I'm just asking you to help me.
No, Dad. You got us into this mess.
You get us out.
Well, thank you very much.
(SEAGULL CALLS)
Are you open?
The door's unlocked.
Most people would take that
as a good indication.
You told me to come and see you
if the pain got worse.
You got any time today?
See the receptionist.
I want to see the doctor.
Has he got any time today?
Do you want those cuts looking at?
No, I don't.
They're just my cats.
I've actually come about my knee.
Do you want to see it?
No. No.
Sit down.
Go on.
(BABY GURGLES)
Any chance of a cup of coffee?
We're not open.
I don't think there's a cafe
in this village
that isn't full of kiddies crying
or even worse, someone singing
to try and stop the kiddies crying.
It's lovely to be somewhere
so peaceful.
Shame about the coffee.
I'm trying to think.
What about?
Well, if you must know...
the restaurant's in trouble and I'm
trying to come up with new ideas.
Well, why didn't you say so?
I ran a very successful restaurant
in Andalusia for seven years.
I am full of good ideas.
If you fancy a brainstorm...
over a nice cup of coffee.
Black or white?
(BABY WAILS)
I'll be back in five minutes.
You get that percolator on.
If you'd elevated your knee,
it wouldn't be this swollen.
By coming to see me
to tell me that it hurt,
you've made it even worse.
Are you going to give me
a lift home?
You can put my bike
on the top of your car.
I'm a doctor, not a taxi driver.
Stay off your feet for at least
two days. Stay off my feet?
Who's going to feed
my cats and kittens?
They can't feed themselves.
Get someone to help you, then.
I can't even afford to feed the
animals, let alone pay an assistant.
Sit down with your leg up as often
as possible with your foot raised.
In the meantime, I'll give you a
prescription for some
anti-inflammatories.
Your glasses have broken.
I know that.
They're my old ones.
Do you have a new pair?
Somewhere.
I don't know where they are.
These do the job,
if I want to read something.
You should go to the optician
and get some more.
What, and waste all that money?
Give that to Mrs Tishell.
Oh... Will she be able
to read your writing?
If she holds it the right way up,
yes.
(ENGINE TURNS OVER)
(ENGINE FAILS TO START)
So come on!
(RETRIES ENGINE)
(ENGINE FAILS TO START)
Have you flooded the carburettor?
Eh?
I've no idea what it means,
but it's what people always ask me
when my car fails to start.
You really need to think about
getting this tractor repaired.
And the bowser can't hold its water.
Should I call the vet?
No, the water bowser.
By the time I get to the pasture,
there's nothing left
for the sheep to drink.
That's IF I even get there.
I can probably fix the bowser
myself,
but you should think about getting
a new tractor one of these days.
I don't imagine they come cheap.
Well, maybe three or four grand
second-hand.
Let's deal with one thing at a time.
For the fencing in the top field,
you needed £800.
No, sarge, I have yet to release
the vehicle to the registered keeper.
I want to know what to do with
the big rock in the back of the car.
Might be fingerprints or...
No, I know it only appears
to be criminal damage,
but there are traces of blood
all over the broken window.
Should I take samples for DNA?
Hello?
(SHOP BELL)
For my leg, keep the swelling down.
Yes. Oh, yes, yes. That's what
I would have prescribed myself.
While I'm here,
I want to ask about some glasses.
What about them?
Well, have you got any?
Help me with my reading.
I don't want anything too pricey.
All my spectacles are on the rack
by the door.
I got the message that you were
holding some pessary rings for me.
Oh, yes. Yes, Dr Ellingham,
I've got them right here.
Are these for long sight
or short sight?
I was just thinking...
Erm, perhaps we could meet tonight.
For a chat... about everything?
The pessary rings.
How much for these? Oh!
Oh! Ow! Oh, my eye!
Oh, God!
Oh, my eye hurts. It really hurts.
Ohh!
Take your fingers out.
Hold your head still.
Tilt your head up. Look up.
What have I done? I've hurt it.
Be still. Hold still.
Have I damaged it?
No, it's just some arcus senilis.
What's that, for heaven's sake?
A cream-coloured circle
around your iris.
It's common in people of your age.
It can be a symptom
of high cholesterol.
Come to the surgery.
I'll do a blood test.
I can't come today.
I've got people coming
over from Delabole to
look at some cats.
If cats are more important than
your health, I couldn't care less.
Or I'm also free tomorrow night.
Just put the pessary rings
on my account, please.
(SHOP BELL)
Thank you very much. Oh, it's you.
How's James Henry?
Fine.
What are you doing in here?
I've come to buy him a dummy.
No. He's not to have a dummy.
Louisa and I have discussed this.
I'm sure you've discussed lots of
things, but people change their minds.
No! No dummies.
You're not to sell this woman
a dummy.
Whatever you say, Dr Ellingham.
Do I have your permission to
purchase James Henry some nappies?
Yes, of course.
Hello, Sally.
Hello.
Oh. And hello to you, James Henry.
Don't you look just gorgeous today?
Yes, you do!
There was blood
all over the vehicle.
I've taken some samples.
But I need your help to identify
any possible suspects.
My help?
Mm.
Now, I know you can't show me
any medical records
or discuss individual patients,
but if I were to mention a few names
and one of those names
were to coincide
with someone who came in here
for treatment
to cuts or abrasions
to their hands or arms...
Mrs Dingley cut her wrist.
Florence Dingley.
Runs the cat home.
Is that Dingley with a D?
What's going on?
Nothing, Doc.
I was just...
Just...
Telling me off
for dropping litter in the street.
It will never happen again, Officer.
Yes, well...
you see it doesn't.
Otherwise...
Spanish theme night?
Yeah.
We do the place up
like an Andalusian bar.
We serve tapas -
that's little Spanish dishes...
and we keep the sangria flowing
all evening.
Just one problem - I can't afford
no tapas nor that sangria.
Well, what's in your freezer?
Right, I'll chop these up small,
fry them in olive oil,
lashings of garlic.
As for the sangria...
we take your cheapest plonk,
add orange juice and cooking brandy
and (SNAPS FINGERS) ole!
This looks like rubbish.
Hang on a minute.
That's the new house red, that is.
Perfect.
Right,
I've got to pick up my grandson.
So I'll start on the tapas tomorrow.
Who's got the baby?
A girl called Angie Grappy.
She only wants two quid an hour.
(LAUGHS)
(BABY WAILS)
Thursday is Spanish theme night.
No, it's not.
Listen, we ask the Tonkens
for a few more days to pay,
and in the meantime, we make a
fortune with this tapas and sangria.
No, you will never make a fortune
selling anything,
whereas I...
have £800.
Now I've got a bit in the bank,
there's some cash around the house.
We put it all together,
and we might have a grand.
That's great.
Yeah.
But what about the interest?
What? What interest, Dad?
The Tonkens don't lend money
for free.
We've got to find another 100 quid.
Oh, Dad.
Don't worry.
We'll manage.
Yeah, but how?
Out of the way! Out of the way!
What are you doing?
800 quid there.
And another 200 quid here.
Quite a lot of loose change,
I'm afraid. Hope you don't mind.
Not at all, Bert.
I'm a very reasonable man.
Pleasure doing business.
Not that our business is concluded
just yet.
No, I know that we owe you
another 100 quid for interest,
but if we can have
until the end of the week.
You don't owe me 100 quid.
Really?
You owe me 350.
BOTH: What?
There's a late-payment penalty
clause.
So we're wanting 350 quid
from you two by this time tomorrow.
Six o'clock.
We can't do that.
Well, you'll have to, unless
you'd rather face the consequences.
You said there'd be repercussions.
They're very similar
to consequences.
What on earth is it, Norman?
Look.
I think he's bothered
by them marks on your neck.
Are they contagious?
No. Just...
Better wash your hands, Norman.
Martin.
Louisa.
I haven't got long before school.
I brought my notes
on the christening.
Some ideas for catering, a guest
list and suggestions for music.
Who's got the baby today?
What?
Who's taking care of James Henry?
Well, my mother, of course.
Are you sure about that?
Why are you asking?
Well, I saw... I thought I saw
a girl wheeling James
in his pushchair yesterday.
Martin, my mother's looking
after the baby all day today,
just like she looked after him
all day yesterday.
I'm sorry, but I'm late.
Could you have a look at this? Yes.
(WINCES)
You OK?
I feel a bit sick.
I think one of them prawns was off.
Shall I chuck 'em?
No, shove them back in the fridge.
Stop scratching.
It's driving me mental, Doc.
Stop it! How long have you had it?
Started itching yesterday.
Changed your washing powder
recently? No.
Tried a new aftershave?
You been in close contact
with any domestic animals -
cats, dogs? No.
Are you suffering stress
at the moment?
Well, life with Dad
is always stressful.
Hm. Put your shirt on.
They're hives.
They'll go of their own accord.
In the meantime, I'll prescribe you
some ointment to ease the irritation.
Hives?
Well, how comes I've got 'em?
What are they?
Circumscribed dermal oedema.
Patches of irritated skin
caused by any number of reasons.
But you say you can rule out stress?
Yes.
Al! I was just on my way to see you.
Well, I'm sort of busy, so...
My son would like a word.
Norman, show him your hand.
It seems Norman has caught
whatever it is you have.
It's only hives.
I see you've been to the doctor.
What did he say?
He asked me if I'd changed
my washing powder or my aftershave.
He give you a prescription?
Yeah.
Excellent.
(SHOP BELL)
Oh!
Good morning, Al.
And how are you today?
Been better, Mrs T.
Got this.
Is it hives
or something more serious?
I never discuss
my clients' prescriptions.
But you can tell us
if hives are contagious?
If you want medical advice,
I suggest you ask Dr Ellingham.
What is it about me
that women don't like?
You know that Mrs Dingley,
that cat woman,
she couldn't bear to look at me,
let alone hold a conversation.
Were you asking her for money?
I was asking her for MY money.
You leave her alone!
This is only for external use.
(PHONE RINGS)
Ooh!
Would you excuse me?
Here we go. Here.
Thank you.
Hello.
Ahem!
And thank you in advance for the 350
quid we'll be collecting tonight.
There's no way...
We'll be at that restaurant at 6pm.
You make sure you're there.
(GROANS)
Agh!
You look absolutely terrible,
if you don't mind my saying so.
I think I'm going to be sick.
It really hurts. Just here.
Should I take those prawns
off the menu?
I think I'm gonna use your loo.
Ugh!
All right, Ange?
No. I'm knackered.
Miss Glasson's mum's too ill
to look after the baby today,
so I've got him again.
Any chance I could see the doc?
I'll have to check.
Why have you got my baby?
Eleanor's not very well today.
Did you have him yesterday?
Yeah.
But I'm not here to talk about
the baby. It's my ankle tag.
Your what?
My ankle tag.
If I start to sweat,
it gets really sore,
like it's rubbing against the skin.
Can you take a look, Doc?
LOUISA: This is really super.
Carry on, children.
Be back in a moment.
What's wrong?
Why have you got James?
I thought it was better I have him,
rather than leave him
in the custody of a child convict.
What? Your mother subcontracted
to a girl called Angie.
Not Angie Grappy?
I don't know what her full name was.
No doubt PC Penhale will have it
on his police computer.
Right, OK, I'll deal with it.
Well, will you?
Or just return him to your mother
and hope for the best?
You've made your point.
Now will you please go away?
Your mother couldn't care less
about our baby.
Oh, but YOU could (!)
A man who's about to leave his son
and move hundreds of miles away
for the sake of his career?
Oh, yeah, you really care
about our baby.
That is a complete distortion.
No, enough!
I'm in the middle of a lesson.
And what about James Henry?
Not your problem, Martin.
Right. We have a visitor.
CHILDREN: Aw!
This lot ought to make a profit,
but I'm not sure it'll be 350 quid.
Of course it won't.
Anyway, they want it tonight.
So what are we going to do?
We could act like men.
How would that work, exactly?
We stand up to the Tonkens.
We say,
'No, you can't have your money.
Now, leave us alone.'
You want protection? In case
they don't like us acting as men.
The son Norman,
if he takes a swing at my dad...
he'll probably kill him.
But you don't know he'll do that.
Just to make sure he don't,
can you come with us?
I'm not some kind of bodyguard
to be used as and when
you feel you might be in danger.
But you've got nothing better to do.
That's where you're wrong.
I'm in the middle
of an ongoing enquiry
concerning criminal damage
to a motor vehicle.
I'm just waiting
to hear back from the CRB.
That's Criminal Records Bureau.
And then I intend
to interrogate the suspect.
Can't it wait?
No.
Anyway, your business
with a loan shark is a civil matter.
So I can't get involved.
What do you mean by 'civil matter'?
It's not a criminal offence,
if you don't pay back a loan.
Mr Tonken can take you
to a civil court,
but if he's not licensed
with the Office of
Fair Trading, he
probably won't risk it.
So what you're saying,
what you're actually saying, Joe,
is you're not going to help us.
I'm saying I can't.
My hands are tied... by the law.
You know what, Joe?
The law is an ass.
Why do you ring me
when the surgery's right there?
I didn't want to see HIM.
I need a lift to another doctor.
Isn't there a clinic in Wadebridge?
I can't believe you let
Angie Grappy look after my baby!
I was ill.
I couldn't cope with a baby.
But you're well enough
to come and cook for Bert?
Please don't tell me off!
You can't even look after
your own grandson?
Not now, Lulu,
I'm not strong enough.
(AGONISED GROANS) I feel sick.
In that case,
you're coming over the road with me.
When did the pain start?
It only got really bad today.
I think it's something I ate.
(SCREAMS)
This isn't food poisoning.
It's an umbilical hernia.
It's never played up like this
before.
What do you mean 'before'?
I had it checked over in Spain.
Why didn't you get it dealt with?
I had places to go, people to see.
It's obstructed your intestine now.
Morwenna!
Congratulations.
You have a strangulated hernia
and need an operation
as soon as possible.
Morwenna! Call an ambulance
and tell them it's urgent.
They'll probably guess, if I've
dialled 999, cos people only do it...
Just call them!
(TAPS KEYBOARD)
Call someone and have it repaired.
It'll be cheaper than paying you
to stand around staring at it.
Yeah. OK.
I think it's time you told me.
Told you what?
What it is that's bothering you.
It's... erm...
It's nothing. Just...
Your work has ground to a halt.
You have hives and insomnia.
You look as vacant as the chickens.
It's clearly not nothing.
Look, I just...
I don't really want
to talk about it right now.
Al...
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
My... My dad borrowed some money
from a couple of blokes
and I had to pay them back.
Or they were gonna...
Well, we don't know
what they were gonna do,
but they were gonna do something.
That's not a good situation.
Very uncomfortable, I imagine.
I was just trying to help Dad.
I... er...
I gave them your fence money.
I see.
And were you going to tell me this?
Probably not.
Right.
I was gonna find the money,
before I had to pay for the fence.
Oh, Al...
That is, once I'd found the money
from somewhere.
In the meantime, you'd just keep
fobbing off the old lady?
Sorry.
Morwenna! If you're asking about
the ambulance again, don't bother.
Is it here?
It's not coming.
They put the call down
as Portweggan.
The ambulance has just arrived
there.
Call another one.
Yeah, I did ask.
They're trying to find one.
Are you happy to wait?
Of course not!
What happens if this one takes ages?
(AGONISED YELLS)
If it's left much longer,
the intestine will
become gangrenous and
she'll die of septicaemia.
Or she'll need major surgery
and a colostomy.
Which is why I'm going to operate.
What?
Wash your hands.
Why? You're going to help me.
Yes! Only do what I tell you to do
when I tell you to do it.
Right. I won't have to use a needle,
will I?
I'm really not good with needles.
Shut up.
A scalpel I could probably manage.
Or I could help instead.
Erm, no.
Martin! I was just going to get
some surgical packs.
You will look after her?
Yes, of course.
I'll carry out the procedure
to the best of my ability.
It only takes a few minutes.
My first incision's about 5cm long,
just above your mother's navel.
Then I use forceps
to hold the skin back.
Then I'll go in and cut and remove
the hernia sac.
All right?
Yes, OK.
Aren't you forgetting something?
What?
I'm still awake.
Yes.
And you will be
throughout the procedure.
I thought that injection
was supposed to knock me out.
No, that was morphine
to numb the pain of your hernia.
Oh, God.
You keep that thing away from me.
Shush.
I'm just going to give you
a local anaesthetic,
so you don't feel anything
when I make the incision.
How long does it take to work?
Just a few seconds.
I like to listen to some music
when I'm at the dentist's.
You're not at the dentist's.
So just... be quiet.
Charming!
I'm going to make the first incision.
Are you ready to swab the blood?
Blood?
OK. I'll try not to pass out.
What are you doing now?
Be quiet.
Right.
What are you doing?
That's it. Just need to close up now.
I can close up, if you like.
I'll give it a go,
if you talk me through it.
Don't be ridiculous.
You can go in here.
You'll like it together in here.
You go in with Sammy.
Oh, no, you don't.
(SIREN BLARES)
(SCREAMS)
Mrs Dingley?
Oh, you coming to us, and early.
I like that.
Well, you won't like this.
We're not gonna pay you.
(LAUGHS)
That's funny.
Well, we mean it.
You've still got an hour
to change your mind.
Now, if you'll excuse us, we've got
to go and see little Mrs Dingley.
And I've got a feeling she's not
going to be too pleased to see us.
What a shame (!)
Norman!
Thanks, Martin.
Yes.
Right.
I'm going to take James
in the ambulance with Mum. Right.
Are you sure it went OK?
Yes.
(PHONE RINGS)
She'll be fine.
Doc, PC Penhale's on the phone.
He says he needs you.
Doc's on his way. When he heard it was
me, he said he'd drop everything.
Well, didn't exactly say
that, but I know that's
what he meant from the way
he hung the phone up.
TONKEN: What's happened here?
Ow!
It's all under control.
We want to talk to Mrs Dingley.
But if there's been
some kind of an accident...
Oi! You leave her alone.
I was merely enquiring
after Mrs Dingley's health.
Course you were (!) These are the
loan sharks I told you about, Joe.
Who are you calling loan sharks?
Mrs Dingley?
Over here.
I'm not here to ask Mrs Dingley
for money.
You say that now
with the police here,
but we know you've come to bully her
till you get what you want.
I don't know what you're on about.
How many fingers am I holding up?
I'm not an idiot. Two.
Follow this one
without moving your head.
I need to have a look in your eyes.
(SOUNDS OF AN ARGUMENT)
Hold still.
What are you doing?
I'm looking in your eyes.
I can see tiny spots on your retina.
Do you often get little shapes
floating around in front of your eyes?
Shapes? All I can see
is a big bright light.
Hm.
Ah! Oh, now it's gone.
Oh, now it's come back again.
Not only do you have arcus senilis,
you also have
birdshot chorioretinopathy.
Is that good or bad?
No, it's not good,
but with steroids and immune-
suppressants, you won't go blind.
Oh, that's a relief
because my poor cats need me.
(ARGUMENT CONTINUES)
Can you get rid of those people?
I could arrest them,
but only if they start
a fight which causes
terror to the public.
That's the legal definition.
(ARGUMENT CONTINUES)
Shut up, all of you!
Here, Doc. Has my son got hives?
How should I know?
Well, can you take a look?
Fleas. Flea bites.
Have you got a dog?
How long have you had it?
A few days.
Mrs Dingley gave it to Norman
because she didn't have the...
Well, anyway, she just gave it him.
Does it sleep in the van?
With Norman.
And when did your rash first appear?
Dunno.
It was yesterday.
Right, then.
That's where your rash came from.
Would you like a diagram?
I have a patient.
You heard the doc.
Get rid of the kitten.
No.
It's for your own good, Norman.
We're not going to pay you
any more money.
There's nothing you can do about it.
That's right.
Oh, there might be nothing
I can do about it perhaps,
but I wouldn't like to predict what
Norman's gonna do the state he's in.
He's like a wild beast
when he's upset.
Can I just stop you there?
Up until now
this has been a civil matter.
However, what you just said
sounded like a threat to me.
I wasn't threatening anyone.
Good.
That would be a criminal matter
and I'd have to take action.
If you harass these gentlemen,
I will arrest you.
But... But they owe me money!
Mrs Dingley does too.
You can't expect me to just...
walk away.
Walk away? No.
Drive away? Yes.
I don't want you coming
near this village again.
If you do, I shall have to take
a close look at this van of yours.
Check it's roadworthy,
check it's taxed, check it's insured.
That will take a very long time and
I will do it over and over again.
Do I make myself clear?
Go on, Norman, get rid of the cat
and let's get out of here.
(BABY VOICE) Bye, Mummy! Bye!
You know, you wouldn't fall so much,
if you bought some new spectacles.
Yeah, I know. I will, I promise.
A little soap wouldn't go amiss
either.
Can I question this suspect, Doc?
What do you mean 'suspect'?
I believe Mrs Dingley knows
something about criminal damage
to a motor vehicle
in the harbour car park.
Oh, God.
I don't think this is a great time.
No, I want to make my confession.
Mrs Dingley,
he's a policeman, not a priest.
I broke the window in that car.
Well, I saw the tide was coming in
and I saw this dog on the back seat.
There was a dog?
No. It turned out to be a fur coat.
So you broke the window to save the
dog that turned out to be a coat?
Yeah. I know. I'm sorry.
I'll pay for the window.
No, I can't, actually. I can't.
(TEARFULLY)
I'm very sorry, but I can't.
(SOBS) Sorry. I'm so sorry.
Never mind, Mrs Dingley.
No harm done.
Apart from the criminal damage.
But... we'll say no more.
Right, boy, we do one of these every
week, we'll soon be in the black.
Proper job.
Right, I'll go and check
on the prawns.
Thanks for coming.
So you have a proposal for me?
I've been thinking.
What if I offered you...
10% of the restaurant's profits?
And... And... And also my scooter.
And I'll pay you back in one go.
Well, almost.
Well, thank you, Al, but I don't
think you've thought this through.
How are you going to turn up
for work without the scooter?
Er...
I sort assumed that
I didn't work for you any more.
You didn't for a while.
Could you get me a glass of Rioja?
Si.
(SPANISH THEME MUSIC DRIFTS IN)
How's your mother?
Comfortable.
Whatever that means.
But the consultant said
you saved her life.
Yes, and her bowel.
I'm really grateful.
So...
Did you enjoy it,
being a surgeon again?
I didn't do it for fun, Louisa.
Still...
it must have been nice
to have a bit of practice
before you go back to London.
I was just going to ask if you
could look after James for a while.
Now? Yeah.
Why?
Well, you could just say,
'I'd be happy to help.'
I would be happy to help. Good.
I wanted to pop across the road.
It's Spanish theme night
at the restaurant,
and Mum asked me to report back.
Yeah.
I'm assuming you don't want to come.
No.
No. I didn't think so.
Er... right.
I'll be back in a while.
Thank you.
Er, Louisa?
Yes, Martin.
Could you ask them to switch
the music off? It's very loud.
Yes, Martin.
Mm.
Just finish off the washing up,
and we'll have some fun.
Martin!
Hello, love.
Clive!
She seems to have formed
a fixation on me.
Why?
I think you'd better tell me
what's been going on here, Doc.
Sync and corrected by APOLLO