Aah, aah!
Oh, my god.
Holy oh.
What are...
What are these things?!
Do I look like I know?
Last thing I remember, I was,
ugh, in a cave.
Looking at some wet egg and...
Oh, that probably did it.
I told you not to look
at that egg!
I-it was too wet.
You don't get to tell me
what to look at.
I've seen your pornhub account.
Also, who makes
a pornhub account?
The algorithm learns your
preferences better that way.
Plus if you get in kind
of a cool enough relationship,
You can sort
of follow each other.
And check out
each other's kinks, you know?
Alright, god damn, sold.
- How do we get out of here?
- Morty, relax.
They're face-hugging parasites.
I don't think their society's
gonna be that hard to navigate.
Okay, yeah, this might be
a little harder than I thought.
Holy
they've got an m&m's store.
This is bad, Rick.
Th-th-th-th-this is really bad.
Just be cool, Morty.
All we gotta do is blend in,
find our ship,
And get the outta here.
Alright, Morty, here's the plan,
put this back on your face.
I-I'm not putting that back
on my face! Relax. It's dead.
Okay, now it's dead.
Come on, hurry up.
Rick, I-it's bleeding.
I-it's bleeding acid.
Alright, well, that should
be the last of it.
If not, then just gimme
two tugs on the arm.
Seems like a self-destructive
life cycle.
Is that gonna happen to us?
You feel an egg in your stomach?
- No.
- Well, glass half full.
How's it going?
'Sup.
- Glory to glorzo.
- Totally.
Love glorzo.
Glorzo is peace.
Peace is glorzo.
Wow, just cogs in the machine,
y'know?
- Ma-makes you think...
- Yeah, I'm sure you'll make this.
Into a beautiful short film
that your parents'll pay for,
Morty, but right now, we really
just need to find my ship.
You sure you're not
just jealous?
Looks like I'm kind of
a celebrity around here.
The future is glorzo!
Oh, my god.
I was just reading you.
Congratulations on making it
into print media.
Real bright future there.
Honestly, it's shocking to see
the two of you together.
Because we're both geniuses?
No, because I've seen
your videos,
And you make me sick.
Fix him.
Glory to glorzo.
Sir, you shouldn't
wander off like that.
We've been looking
all over for you.
The project is ready
for your approval.
Sir, is this man bothering you?
Um, no, h-he's fine.
Uh, what... what project?
Jesus christ,
who the was I?
Here's a scientific fact
I'm not allowed to say...
Our hosts are biologically
designed to incubate our eggs.
If that "triggers" you,
off.
If it doesn't,
please like and subscribe.
New videos every glorzday.
God,
was I at least rich?
I mean, d-d-did
I at least sell out.
And sell vitamins or something?
Rick, I've watched enough
pornhub to know.
What a studio apartment
looks like.
God damn.
Jesus, your glorzo got
done.
My lord,
we await your command.
Oh, to...
Shoot it?
A-at people?
Glorzo is peace.
All shall be made glorzo.
Glory to glorzo.
I... Did this?
You and the amazing technology
you both brought us.
Yeah, makes sense.
A-and where was this heading?
Earth?
Probably earth?
The humans call it "earth."
Yeah, well, okay,
first of all, great work.
You guys obviously put a lot
of work into this.
Okay.
And y'know, it shows.
I-it really shows.
But um...
I-I've been thinking,
and, you know,
Maybe we should
just call this off.
Sorry, is... is there more?
Nope, nope.
I-I guess, uh, that...
That's it.
Just don't glorzo earth.
Just would've been nice
to have heard this sooner.
Before we spent all day on it.
Yeah, well, I-I'm just hearing
about it, too.
You ordered it.
Right.
I-I did, and, um...
I'm just saying for next time,
maybe put more thought.
Into it before a whole day of...
Okay, well, I'm sorry I made you
do your job for a day!
You look like you were
all really busy.
Before I came
and it all up.
Boy, oh boy, huh?
This guy's a genius, but at...
But at what price,
you know?
Y'know, you,
Rick!
Who's... Rick?
Yeah, well, if we're free
to ask questions,
Why haven't you blinked,
uh, for 20 minutes,
And why, uh, doesn't
your mouth move when you talk?
Ah, geez, look at me.
I-I feel down on...
On... on the floor.
Oh, let... let me, uh, help...
Help you out here, buddy.
Ah, thanks, man.
Thanks, pal. That's right.
I'm right back where... where...
Right back in the saddle here.
Alright,
it, run.
I-I hate this!
I hate all of this!
Yeah, yeah, keep that feedback
coming, Morty.
It can only help.
Oh,
aw, man!
How big is this city?!
I know,
it's like pick a lane.
Are you face huggers
or industrialists?
Damn, feels kinda good
when there's no guilt, huh?
Yeah, it's...
It's like in "star wars."
Yeah, just like
in "star wars."
Go nuts!
Nice, Morty! Give a little
"yee-haw" if you want.
They... they always do a little
"yee-haw" like a cowboy.
Yee... yee-ha... yee-haw.
Good enough.
God, I needed this.
Honestly, it's been a while
since I've been able.
To just let loose,
you know?
Just have fun.
I'm... I'm...
I'm sorry if I've been
taking it out on you.
No, I get it. You got a lot
on your plate, amigo.
I-I just wish you'd open up.
To me more about it
sometimes, you know?
I-I-I'm your partner.
Thanks, Morty.
I mean that.
Thank you.
Sometimes, I get a little
in my head, you know?
Hey, man, that head's
a good place to be.
Just remember to let me
in sometimes, you know?
- Will do, buddy.
- Mother.
Oh, my god,
this is so much fun!
I don't want to stop!
Yeah, it's like
popping bubble wrap.
Honestly,
I'm proud of us for not.
Totally.
It would've been cheap.
Yeah, real low-hanging fruit,
and we're batter than that.
Pearl harbor,
on the other hand...
Yeah,
I think that's in-bounds.
I am the god of death!
Should've been a better species!
So, you did a 9/11?
Almost did a 9/11.
We... we went with
a pearl harbor.
We're pretty classy.
Why were either of those
an option?
Ask the saudis.
Wow. Damn.
Yeah,
getting political.
I'm political now.
How 'bout you, jerry?
You got anything to add
to the family dynamic?
I've been getting into
beekeeping lately.
Is something wrong
with that?
What's wrong with that?
Don't I have the right
to be happy? To exist?
I'm sorry I didn't 9/11
Pearl harbor before breakfast,
but I have a life, too!
I have dreams!
And how's summer?
Did she have fun, too?
Oh.
Uh-um.
Summer...
Was...
With us.
There.
You saw us take her
in the car with us.
Mm, yes.
Yes, yes, of course.
Th-that's what happened.
- And now she's...
- Sleepy.
Um, she's... she's sleepy.
Really sleepy.
That's why she's not here.
So sleepy.
She's sleepy?!
What the hell was that?!
I didn't see you trying
anything!
The bed isn't better
than not the bed!
Where's summer?!
Geez.
Oh, man.
You know, maybe we went
too hardcore on these guys.
Yeah, why do you think
we never go back.
To a place we've already been?
Do you know how many adventures
we could get out.
Of purge planet, Morty?
Gear world?
I don't sequel.
It's called integrity.
Here, put this back
on your face.
You kept it?
Oh, did you want a new one?
- 'Sup?
- Yo.
Oh,
it's them!
The worst thing
to ever happen to us!
Yeah, that makes sense.
Sorry, Morty,
we tried pussin' it.
Time to go in hot.
Rickputer, initiate
unnecessarily badass suit-up.
Let's lick.
Shouldn't we be finding summer?
Oh, right, gee, sorry.
I got caught up again.
God, d-do I need
to take more adderall,
Or am I taking
too much adderall?
Man, really shouldn't have gone
with swords.
I know.
My wrists are killing me.
Flame-throwers next time,
for sure.
Can I get a laser whip?
Okay, but there's no way
you don't chop your dick off.
Sum sum, come with us
if you want to live...
At a lower standard than this,
I guess.
God damn.
Empress, is everything alright?
Ummm...
Seize them!
Seize them?!
What?!
Summer, you bitch!
You gotta be kidding me!
You know that song,
Rick?
From the...
When the prisoners sing it?
Come on, Morty,
for sake.
It's my jail time.
I-I can spend it however I want.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, buddy!
Hey, hey, hey!
Not in here!
Aw...
Gimme that.
Leave us.
What the
took you so long?!
You left me here. We
didn't know you were with us!
Do you know how much
I've had to deal with?
You're in a cape, summer.
How bad could it be?
No bad story ends with a cape.
You don't know anything
about my story.
"I couldn't help but wonder,
was gharkhul really capable."
Of consuming a living sun,
Or was I simply getting
too close to gharkhul?
"Was gharkhul consuming me?"
Rick, can we listen
to something else?
Quiet! She's just about
to summon gharkhul.
She's been talking about
summoning gharkhul.
For three episodes,
summer.
Wait a minute,
what's that in your mouth?
It's a toothpick.
I'm a toothpicker now.
Get used to it.
God, are you that desperate
for a thing?
It is my thing.
Just like yours is dying alone
and yours is jerking off.
At least jerking off tracks
for my character, you know?
I like to jerk off.
I'm 14. I own it.
Well, I jerk off, too!
Alright, stop.
Jesus chris, I don't wanna think
about that.
Summer, keep your toothpick.
Gross!
Morty, stop talking to
your sister about jerking off.
Everyone pretend podcasting
isn't boring.
Whoa, Morty, look how
wet this egg is.
I dunno, Rick.
That looks a little too wet.
D-don't touch it.
Oh, I'm gonna touch it.
Why are you guys screaming
at an egg?
Shut up, summer!
Just let us look at an egg!
Yeah, summer,
shut the up.
Nobody wants you here.
You know, sometimes we like
to go on adventures.
And look at wet eggs,
you know? Can we just go?
This place is giving me
the creeps.
Holy
I love this egg.
Hey, look,
mine's doing it, too.
Are you guys sure that's safe?
Oh, my god!
All is glorzo.
- God.
God?
She has a toothpick.
Take it out and put her face
in an egg.
- God.
For sake, how long
have you been hatched?
30 seconds?
I've been alive seven minutes.
Think before you...
excuse me, seven minutes?
Uh, I've been here
for 29 minutes.
But yes, take the toothpick
out of her mouth.
Suck on her face this instant
and use her body to...
What was that?
That is called responsibility.
He was part of
our greatest generation.
He understood that what you need
to do is suck on a face,
Shit an egg, and die.
Wait, so, all you do is live
half an hour,
Shit eggs, and die?
Yes.
We love it.
I'll do it right now.
Okay, you guys don't have
to listen to me,
But I vote you don't do that?
And who's up for
changing things around here?
Alright, look, uh, this
been brewing for a while.
I'm not gonna win any popularity
contests by saying it,
But here's...
Here's the world as I see it.
I mean, look, we are designed
to suck on faces and lay eggs.
Life is life,
and that's the way it goes.
Hello, troy.
Hello, jez.
How is it going?
Really good, commander.
Should be ready by tomorrow.
That is what I like to hear.
Great work,
glory to glorzo.
Honestly, summer,
I can't thank you enough.
When we met, we were just
shitting eggs in a cave,
But you showed us life
is about more than that.
It is about living.
And now,
with these missiles,
We will be able to reach
the entire universe.
We say it all the time,
but I guess all is glorzo.
Yeah, that sounds great.
And you've been great.
Yeah.
You've been so great
that I've been thinking.
Maybe it's time for you
to get off my brother.
Who's your brother?
Oh, this?
Forgot he was there, haha.
Wait.
What are you saying?
I'm saying that you've
been great, steve,
But we've been thinking
it's time for a new chapter.
We?
Uh, this is shane.
He'll be handling
the day-to-day.
It's an honor to meet you, sir.
I might only be two minutes old,
but I know you're a legend.
She doesn't care about us.
She just wants her
host back.
I don't know what to do.
Oh, now you want my help.
- Too late for that.
- Come on, man.
What is this.
You don't get to do this to me.
We were in eggs together.
Oh, since
we were in eggs.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah,
now you respect, like,
The biological institutions now?
You.
All you care about.
Is "progress"
and society and skyscrapers.
You don't care about
biology.
Oh, yeah, well,
what the.
You... how you you haven't laid
and egg inside this old man yet?
Because I do what I want.
Because someone's gotta
stand up for what's right.
Why do you hate her so much?
Because she took you away
from me!
Whoa, man.
Jesus christ.
No, I-I didn't, I...
Whoa, whoa, whoa. No.
It's cool.
I feel the same way.
Oh, my god, I...
I wish we could suck
on each other.
I wanna suck on you, too.
I'm gonna suck you so hard.
Suck me.
C-c-can we do this?
A-a-are we allowed to do this?
I don't care.
I just want you.
All of this.
Let's just get the hell
outta here.
And be whatever
the we want.
That's evolution.
That's progress.
I want a family.
Can we have a family.
Yeah.
Aah, aah!
Oh, my god.
Holy
oh.
What are... what are these
things?! Do I look like I know?
Hey, wait a second.
How'd you know that last part?
You weren't there for that.
I had to fill in some gaps.
Everyone around the office
knew about steve and bruce.
I've got a plan, okay.
You just have to follow my lead.
The punishment is...
- Death.
- Mother summer!
You said you had a plan!
Silence.
The council of glorzos
has spoken.
More like council of.
- Glorzo is law.
- Silence.
The punishment is death.
By...
Getting their car.
Summer?
Shut up.
Yes, place them in the car.
Those pieces of.
No, no, no!
This is like torture.
No, I-I-I-I hate being
in my car.
You deserve it,
you pieces of.
And to make sure
the sentence is passed,
I shall be joining them.
In the car.
And we shall drive away
from here and die.
Oooookay.
Guess what, everybody.
It's me, the whiny guy
you never want to hear from.
She's trying to escape
with her family.
My time to shine.
Execute her.
Okay, plan b.
Morty, now.
Aah!
Jesus, Morty, that sucks.
Alright, stop playing,
Morty.
I-I got this.
Aah!
This is what we get
for evolving?
Sorry!
Sorry.
I-I'm sorry. We... we...
We thought you were evil.
Why would you think that?
We had a giant tower
that blared "glorzo is peace."
I know.
I... should... should we help?
- Boo!
- Oh, like that's helping.
Got it. Going.
Okay, we're gonna hit the road.
You're... you're just going?
You told us to go!
Once again,
I'm so sorry for what they...
You're part of this, too.
Boo!
We hate you the most.
Get out.
Jesus, summer,
why'd you let these things.
Stay on us for so long?
I was working with a lot.
Just let me listen
to the podcast next time.
Nailed that landing.
Huh.
Neat-looking egg.
Okay, well, I'm not
cleaning up this
aah!
Maybe we, uh... maybe we don't
tell people about this one.
Did we at least learn something?
That we suck and everyone sucks?
I guess that counts.
Later, chodes.
Hit me on the next one.
You know, Rick,
I'm sure you wanna jump.
Into another crazy adventure,
but can we just relax.
And maybe watch
some interdimensional cable?
I'm cool if you are.
Honestly, that sounds great.
W-we don't need to try so hard,
you know.
Let's just take it easy
and riff, you know.
That's what I love about us.
Me, too, buddy.
Do you suffer
from alzheimer's?
Do you suffer from alzheimer's?
- Reggie?
- Do you suffer from alzheimer's?
Reggie,
you alright in there?
Mm, Rick, do you feel...
Oh, god,
I have to shit an egg.
Oh, my god,
oh,
Oh, it hurts.
Oh god,
Is this how we die, Rick?
- I don't know, Morty. I don't know! Aah!
- Is this how we die?!
- I don't want to an egg,
- Rick! I'm sorry, Morty.
I'm sorry! It's my fault.
It's all my fault!
Hey, you two. Did you...
Beth, your son is dying!
Say goodbye!
What are you... say
goodbye to your little boy!
No, look away!
I'm making an egg, mom.
I'm making an egg!
You said you'd keep me more
in the loop this year.
Look away, beth!
Daddy loves you!
My ass!
This is it, Morty!
It's full circle from the pilot.
Full circle!
Oh, I guess we, uh...
I guess we both just had
to take a.
Yeah,
I-I-I guess we, uh...
gross.
Guys, clean it up.
Look at your dad.
Such a dork,
keeping bees.
I mean, it's... at least
it's interesting, though.
At least, like...
I wish my dad kept bees.
I mean,
it's kind of cute.
Like...
Your dad keeps bees.
How old is your dad?
He's obviously
beekeeping age.
I don't know,
I think it's kind of sweet.
Summer, I want to
your dad.
Oh, really?