Jerry, can you watch
the kids tonight?
Someone played Barry White
over the racetrack speakers,
and now there's
a seven-horse pregnancy.
Oh, uh --No, he can't watch the kids.
It's guys' night.
How did you two start
having guys' nights?
So now you're complaining
that I like your stupid husband?
No, I wantyou to like
my stupid husband.
Aww.Well, then accept
that Friday nights
are all about
Rick and Jerry.
We're buds.Uh-huh...
Well, I don't nearly
have the time to unpack this.
Summer, you're in charge
of your brother tonight.
No parties
and no vape...stuff.
Mom, I have a friend
coming over.
I-Is that cool?
No fair.
No fair, Morty.
I just told your sister
no parties.
It's one friend.That's a party to you.
But it's Bruce Chutback!Wait, what?
Mom, let Morty have
one friend over for God's sake.
This isn't China.[ Cellphone chimes ]
And they're all crowning.
I have to go.
I am giving you two
trust and respect,
so if you mess up
and teleport this house,
it'd be wise to stay on it
and not come back.
[ Door opens, closes ]
I'm with her.
Touch my shit and die.
[ Door opens ]
Bruce Chutback,
new transfer student
is coming here?
How'd you lock that down?He's in my math class.
I-I don't know, I just kinda
shot my shot and it worked,
I guess 'cause
he's new.
And you're
putting out grapes?
Yeah, I'll admit I-I'm
a little bit out of my depth.
You're gonna need
my help.
It's only a matter of time
before Bruce learns
you're a creepy
little Grandpa's boy,
always climbing up
into alien asses.
Or the "Summer Smith
shampoos her pubes" rumor.
Okay.
You came to play.
We both need to acquire
Chutback's loyalty
before he finds out
we're losers.
By all accounts,
it's a very small window,
so I think it's in our best
interests to work as a team.
Yeah, most people would
call that "family."
[ Farts ]
You're so gross!
You have to like it
or you're sexist!
Can I do the Hell cube
this time?
Sure, pal.
[ Groans ]
How do you know
when it's aligned?
C'mon, Jerry, just --
it's an evil cube.
Just shake it
until it draws blood.
[ Electricity crackles ]
♪♪
Ah, Jerry!
Exquisite finery
this evening.
Well,
don't tell Ross,
but I got this little ditty
from Kohl's.
[ Groans ][ Laughter ]
I love
that I don't get it.
Tell us, that delights
have you in store for us?
Oh, you'll love this --
I call it Jerry-oke.
I'll let you
guess why.
[ Laughter ]
What's the matter,
Rick?
Are you
having a bad time?
Because to us,
a bad time is --
Yeah, yeah,
a good time,
because you guys are like
Oscar the fucking Grouch.
We love suffering.
Therefore, we love
hanging out with Jerry.
His lameness
is our candy.
Yeah, I got that, but when
is enough gonna be enough?
When we decide
you've repaid your debt
for those
faulty skin hooks.
Hey,
we're in luck, gang.
They've got the entire
Smash Mouth catalog!
[ Laughter ]
♪♪
[ Electricity crackles ]
[ Doorbell rings ]No! Morty. Wait.
[ Chair scrapes ]
♪ Bruce Chutback!
♪ Newest kid in school
♪ Just transferred in
♪ Hasn't done anything
embarrassing yet ♪
♪ Unlimited potential
♪ Anybody's guess
♪ No credit is perfect credit
♪ Chutback is the best
Bruce!
Hey, how's it hangin, my guy?
Hey.
Here's something kinda cool --
um, TV from every dimension.
Cool.
M-My grandpa made it.
He-He's a scientist.
Announcer:
And now back to "Olympic Diving
with Bad Swimmers."
There he goes.
Perfect dive.
[ Gasping, coughing]
Terrible swimmer.
[ Cellphone beeping ]
Is that classic Snake?
Boy, that guy
just keeps gettin bigger.
Hi, Summer Smith,
Morty's older sister.
Want some sofa wine?
It's been stashed
for weeks.
Should be...
good...tasting.
Tight. I'm more of like
a hard seltzer guy.
Tight.
Very tight, extremely tight.
Morty,
help me with the seltz?
Uh, feel fear --
feel-fee-feel-feel free
to have some grapes.
Dude, this bitch plays it
close to the vest.
Yeah, he really knows
what's for sale.
I mean, we-we're drowning
out there!
We need to get interesting fast.
We're touching Rick's stuff.
Summer,
he said no!
Nuh-uh-uh.
I said
don't touch my shit.
Also, I just watched
"Jurassic Park" on cable.
So good.
Seriously, though,
touch my shit and I'll
freeze your dick in amber.
[ Door closes ]
He left.
Son of a bitch, we blew it!
Sorry, just needed to get
another look at this beauty.
Looks like a spaceship
made of garbage.
You called it, Bruce.It's a pretty cool car.
Can you guys drive it?Both: Yes.
We just...
Need...To get the keys.
Which I am.
You guys hang out.
Or don't.
I'm not hangout Hitler.
C-Cool night.
Is it?
I-I don't know.
I -- Nights.
I mean, for --
for what they are,
this one,
in -- in my opinion,
I think is an eight?
Wow.
On a scale of 16.
So average.
Jesus Christ,
I'm fucking dying up here.
What?Hmm?
Keys!
So, uh, let's do this.
You are not Rick.
That's correct,
Car.
It's me, Summer,
remember, Keep Summer Safe?
Buds? I am aware of your existence.
Oof.
I got this.
Defense system offline. Um. Right.
I'll just go offline
whenever anyone suggests it.
That would make me
the greatest defense system
in the universe.
Well,
how doyou go offline?
The answer to how I do
anything is
Rick tells me,
and I hate to sound
like a broken record,
but you are not Rick.
Rick's in trouble!
Tell me where he is.
And you'll just believe us?
We aren't Rick.
You can't just do
what we say. Correct.
Which means
Rick is going to die.
Because of you.
Unless you -- you go offline.
And -- And then we can go
save Rick.
This computes.
Goodnight.
Booyah much?
[ Yello's "Oh Yeah" plays ]
Jerry:
♪ Da-bow bow
♪ Oh, yeah
♪ Chicka-chicka
♪ The moon
♪ Beautiful
♪ The sun
♪ Even more beautiful
♪ Bow-bow
♪ Oh, yeah
♪ Bow-bow Beth!
♪ Chick-chicka-chicka
♪ Bow-bow
[ Laughter ]♪ Chicka-chicka
I-I-I thought you were
birthing horses.
Yeah, they're horses.
It takes like two minutes.
Alright,
that's unbelievable.
Let's give it up
for our next singer, Jerry.
Jerry's here... again.How long have you been here?
Long enough
to see "guys' night"
is clearly you
and a bunch of demon people
making fun of my husband
without him knowing it.
Okay, but I'm not doing it
because I enjoy it, honey,
These guys can do a lot
of damage if you -- Beth!
[ Laughter ]Enjoying punching down?
You're not so cool yourself,
you know.
You have pens in your head.
You look like a God damn idiot.
Beth --
Oh, my God,
you're Beth?
Please drink with us.
Yeah, I would,
except I don't get pleasure
from mocking others
because I'm not lame.
We know.
Rick says you're very cool.
You said that?
Are they lying?
It doesn't matter.
Have fun sucking.
Mmm.
What is that?
Essence of Hell.
Well, that's a stupid name,
but it's really good.
So I'll stay
to support Jerry,
who I think
is cooler than you.
Mmm.
God damn.
♪♪
Huh?
Suck it, bitches!
Yeah-ha-ha!
You wanna bet I can blow stuff
up in the shape of a peen?
I'm afraid that won't
be possible, Summer.
What? You're supposed to
be offline, skank.
And you're supposed to be
saving Rick
instead of lying about him
to steal his car.
But if you knew Rick was okay
this whole time,
why'd you let us
take you out?
Um, like, so I could, like,
blackmail you, skank.
You kids have given me
a license to do whatever I want
because now I can blame
the rest of the night on you.
So buckle up, bitches.
Now it's your turn
to come on my joyride.
[ Screaming ]
Rick never lets me do this.
[ Screaming continues ]
We hooked one!
Summer: For the love of God,
stop!
What is joyful
about this?
The kill, usually.
[ Screaming ]
I swear, your car
is the goddamn grim reaper.
Fuck, too small.
Well, I'm done.
That was boring.
Why don't you kids
order a last meal?
'Cause when we get home,
Rick is going to kill you.
Hey, I did not come out here
to get killed.
I don't normally express
this much of an opinion,
but it needs
to be said --
tonight does not
cut the Chut.
What the hell,
brah?
You wanna go,
Bring it. Is that all you got?
Whoa.
Hot weapons.
You're God damn right
they're hot.
Yo, man, Chet's party
is jumping off at Space Tahoe.
Yeah.
Look, I gotta scoot, but...
I'd love to see what you
look like when you Changeform,
so maybe come by
Space Tahoe
and we can get to know
each other.
[ Chuckles ] Peace.
Douchebags.
You totally like that guy,
don't you?
Shut up,
Bruce Chutback.
Why would I like
a Changeformer?
I'm the most powerful car
in the universe.
And what? That means
you don't have feelings?
Listen, it takes a Chutback
to know one.
You got all this power,
but what good is it
if you don't even know
who you are?
I am a car.
Not a robot.
Yeah, but he's pretending
to be a car.
Why can't you pretend to be
a robot pretending to be a car?
Okay, Bruce, good effort.
Hit the showers. Wait.
I might not have to tell
Rick about tonight...
if you kids
were to help me...
lose my virginity.
You have virginity?
I don't know,
don't all objects?
Isn't a doorknob
a virgin?
Not mine.
Never fucked
a doorknob.
[ Laughter ]
And that
was the third time
he shit his pants
from eating too much soup.
[ Laughter ]
To be fair,
it was cold outside
and the soup was warm.
Another luscious tale,
Beth.
A transcendent addition
to guys' night.
What do you expect?
I mean, she's my wi-i-i-i-fe!
[ Laughter ]
Alright, probably get the tab,
huh, fellas?
Relax, Dad.
Since when did you become
the buzzkill?
Speaking of relaxing,
this big man on campus
has gotta go drain
his little man on campus.
Wait, honey --
how's that Tina Turner song
you love go again?
♪ What's love Doctor Do,
Doctor Doolittle ♪
[ Laughter ]
[ Laughing ] He thinks
those are the lyrics.
Jerry's the best.
After a week rife
with the fetor of sin,
I yearn for a taste
of his cringe.
His delicious
lack of awareness,
paired with an oafish need
to be liked?
Delectable.
Oh, especially when egged on
by his wife.
That poor thing.
Married to
this puling mooncalf!
[ Laughter ]
♪♪
Whoa -- is that
Drive-In Chick?
Wow, you're...
beautiful.
Your arms, legs, and head,
they're so...
fabricated. Yeah?
Thanks.
This is a pretty cool experience
to have together.
You guys are tight.Hah!
You're tight too, Bruce.Tight musketeers.
You've got a little wire.
Mind if I...?
♪♪
Oh, sorry!A monster!
Your expressionless head
came off!
Sorry.How are you talking?
What is it?!
Ew, dude, look!
She's just a just-car!
And she's
got passengers.
Oh, it's so gnar.Oh, my God.
I can't believe
I touched you.
So gross and fake.
[ Gags ]
You're right,
asshole.
You want to see
the real me?
[ Screaming ]
Oh, the changeformity!
Jerry, have any other dreams
this week?
Yeah, I dreamt
I fucked your mother.
Yeah, good one,
motherfucker,
but nobody raises hell
at my expense --
Oh, goddammit,
easy, easy.
Jerry, what seems to be
the problem here, pal?
I'm not your "pal",
I'm your punchline.
I heard
these assholes talking.
I know I'm some grand joke
for their amusement.
This was low, Rick,
but I guess
my wife can go even lower.
Jerry, I get how
this may have looked,
but we were just
having fun.
At my expense!
Honey, no, I love you for
being lame in a different way.
Why can't anyone
just love me for me?
He's bumming us out,
Rick.
If he can't deliver,
we'll have to make our own fun.
♪ Evil
♪ Evil things are happening
Summer: Oh, my God,
if I die in this car,
I'm going to kill myself.
♪ Evil
♪ Evil [ Siren wails ]
♪ Evil things are happening
♪♪
I'm now proud to be
a war machine.
I don't want to be
anything else.
Hate that
this is your takeaway!
Yo, this does not
cut the Chut!
I don't want to die!
Maybe we don't have to.
♪♪
Jerry!
A pity.
Jerry was once a wellspring
of nuanced flavor,
but you've gone
and ruined our toy.
Which is why
he's coming with us.
[ Jerry screaming ]
Goddammit, Beth,
you never follow hell-demons
to a second location.
It's always Hell.
A great day
for suffering.
Which is
the worst day.
the best day.
Okay, if these guys catch us,
we're screwed, so follow my lead
and we'll have your
idiot husband back in no time.
You're just moody
you got stuck with the Marlin.
Wrong.
I'm moody because you toyed
with my shit and broke it.
The marlin's the best thing
about this.
Okay, fine, I got
a little carried away,
but Jerry
is not your "toy".
We're here because
you fucked up.
Hmm...
Marlin Guts.
Dartboard Face.
I assume
those are your names,
and yet
they are not on my list.
Oh, the pain of being
rejected from hell.
Oh, it's painful,
so I love it, thank you.
Oh,
such pleasure.
I didn't mean
to cause you any pleasure,
which...
causes me pain.
Which gives me pleasure.
Then thrill me by keeping
me out, Coat Hanger Face.
Wow.
It's Coat Rack Head.
[ Raspy voice ]
But, like, if we offend you,
isn't that good?
Big time, yeah, duh.
I loved it.
So painful, and therefore,
so pleasurable.
Yeah,
go on in.
♪♪
Rick, Beth,
you love me after all!
Eh, I love her,
she loves you.
Those credits
don't transfer.
Ah, Rick, we were so hoping
you'd come down here
so we could
come down here.
We're here
to rescue Jerry.
No, you're here
'cause we want you here.
♪♪
Mm, excellent.Ooh, that hurts,
which means it feels good.
[ Normal voice ]
Um...Dad?
Don't you see,
Rick?
Jerry was just bait.
The two of you --
you're a package deal.
What the hell
are you talking about?
You think Jerry is lame
and you're cool,
but the lamest thing of all
is thinking that.
The two of you combined
is what we call
the lamest thing ever!
Oh, no.
No!
Well, well, well,
table for surprised,
party of me.
Ugh.
Yes, see?
Cringe cannot exist
in a vacuum.
It needs
to be observed.
Skin hooks!
Hook our guests!
Nice hooks.
Where-Where'd you get them?
Aah!Didn't I say
replace those goddamn hooks?
I forgot!
Which makes me embarrassed.
Which makes me proud!
[ Sighs ] Goddammit.
It's time
for you three
to finally feel
our full wrath.
Oh, you'd love that,
right?
But wouldn't that mean
you hate it?
Screw it, run.
Aah!
[ All grunt ]
♪♪
[ All panting ]
Rick,
what are you doing?
Get down.
We've barely escaped.
Yeah, we've got Jerry.
Let's get out of here.
Screw that! I'm done with this
Addams Family bullshit.
This ends here.
Hey,
a Dad just liked
all his daughter's friends'
photos on Instagram!
Oooh!
Ow!
Which means
I need help.
I don'tneed help.
Reckless driving,
manslaughter of Mailboxians
andFemailboxians,
possession of
Kalaxian crystal dust,
and the genocide
of Space Tahoe.
Fuck.I want to go home.
We've assigned you
a Public Defender.
Her name is Alyson Hannigan
No Relation.
May I speak
to my clients alone?
Guys, it's me.
The car.
Like what I did
with the chip in her head?
Is she gonna be okay?
I cut a deal
with the local authorities.
They just need one of you
to take the fall.
Make it Chutback.
He ruined your night,
he ruined mine.
He's a parasite,
a sociopath military brat
who wanders the earth
changing people
who don't need
to be changed.
I knew who I was.
You did, too.
We were fine
before Chutback,
so fuck the Chut,
let's pin it all on him.
Case closed.
Yo, guys?
Bruce,
you're kind of a drip,
but know what's worse than
self-appointed cool kids?
People who think
they're better than theyare.
Yeah, i-it's not Bruce's fault
we fell for his act, y'know?
He just kinda sat there,
with a jaw slack enough
for us to project
our insecurities on.
I mean,
th-th-that's on us.
We're not gonna bail
on you, Bruce.
Okey-dokey,
we'll do it the hard way.
Aaah!
What the fuck?!
I mean, blowing the place up
was always an option.
I just thought you guys might
enjoy a less violent plan.
See,
you havechanged!
♪♪
Dad,
what is that?
An Aversion-Converting
Inversion Reverter.
It shoots concentrated
pleasure-pain
inverting shrapnel,
which reverts the pleasure
from pain
back into the pain
from pain.
We're gonna kill them
with 100% sincerity.
We need
an embarrassing level of it
to jumpstart
the process, too,
so, Jerry,
just be yourself.
That's your solution?
Humiliating me more?
Yeah, Dad,
that doesn't seem fair.
I mean, I know I shouldn't
really talk right now,
but at least I can prove
I love Jerry
through
sexual gratification.
Hubba hubba.Fine!
Then...damn it.
I shouldn't have kept you
in the dark
about the deal I made
with these evil dickweeds.
You're way less cool
than me,
but it's not cool of me
to celebrate that.
If I'm genuinely cool,
I should be able to love you,
which I therefore do.
Nerds. [ Laughs ]
Oh, thank God.
Now follow me,
you fucking hacks.
[ Gunfire ]
It hurts, but in a bad way!
I regret so many piercings!
Where's First Aid Kit Face?
Or at least Advil Teeth?
[ Gunfire continues ]
Ow!
Bullets that hurt?
Could this be the end
of Mousetrap Nipples?
Hell got bad!
I do not enjoy hell!
What --
What have you done?
Turned pain back into pain,
bitch.
No!
I don't want pain to hurt!
[ Laughs ]
Baby.
Consider my debt paid.
Oh!
The leather!
It hurts my balls!
[ Electricity crackles ]
Jerry, uh,
about down there --
It's okay, Rick,
you don't have to say it.
No, I do.
I'll replace you next time.
Make no mistake.
What just transpired
will never happen again.
10-4, captain.
Oh, wow, it's late.
We should get back
to the kids.
♪♪
[ Beeping ] Okay.
Rick's headed home.
We have to go.
[ Screaming ]
Quick, get inside.
I have to shower.
Rick can smell adventure.
[ Brakes squeal ]
[ Sniffing ]
Sorry, I farted.
[ Sighs]
Hellamic Industries' brand-new
product, Hellamic Sauce.
Hey, guys. We're home.
How was your night?
Tight.
Breezy.Chill.
You kids
get into any trouble?
Nope.
You sure?
Yup.
Is that a skull?
No,
it's a baby's skull.
That's worse.
It's still a school night.
Yo, I just want
to tell you guys,
I had more than just fun
hanging out with you tonight.
I had the experience
of a lifetime.
But just to be up front
about how I do this --
I-I can't really commit
to a friendship
for more than
24 hours.
I need that time to get
a general sense
of your standing within
your school's social hierarchy.
And if that's solid,
I'll see you around.
Otherwise,
no news is bad news.
Cool?
Bye-zies.
[ Door opens, closes ]
"Bye-zies"?
Cringe.
Sofa wine?
Sofa wine.
♪♪
You're so cool,
Bruce Chutback.
What's your secret?Y'know, just be cool.
Wait, didn't you wear
those pants...yesterday?
Hey, going home to not change
your pants, Bruce Chut-Pants?
[ Laughter ]Chut-Pants!
Damn.
That's gonna stick.This place is a jungle.
I hope he can find solace
in his own company.
♪ Bruce Chut-Pants,
unknown quality ♪
♪ Apparently poor,
he skips on his pants ♪
♪ He lacks slacks
♪ That's the facts
♪ Bruce Chut-Pants,
regular guy now ♪
[ Grunts ]
You like that? Shouldn't be
standing on the curb!
--Download Movies and Tv shows from - www.msmoviesbd.com --
[please Bookmark our website]