Are we -- are we gonna put it
back when we're done with it?
Why? The only thing of value on
it is the secret treasure map.
The rest is just instructions
for running a country,
And I'm pretty sure
they're online.
It just feels a little wrong --
Morty, are you gonna be
a [bleep] america nerd
Or are you gonna be cool
And steal the constitution
with grandpa?
Here, hold this while I
crack the hermetic seal.
W-why not
just use this again?
Morty!
You just destroyed the map
And activated the giant assassin
hidden in the statue of liberty!
I'm sorry --
w-wait, what?
It was a trojan horse, morty.
Never trust the french.
Alright, fun's fun, but now
the federal government's
Gonna be pissed again.
Way to go.
And on america's birthday
Or whatever the [bleep]
thanksgiving is.
Seal team leader:
Rick and morty!
You are under arrest
and surrounded
By an anti-portal shimmer!
Come out
with your hands up!
Well,
happy thanksgiving to me.
Can't wait to see what
a "shimmer" does to my prostate.
Dad, can you please
just end whatever this is --
I understand you're upset,
mr. President.
It's honestly
all morty's fault.
But in the meantime, you really
want to keep your army
Of pointlessly camouflaged
eagle scouts off my lawn.
Don't tell me what I want,
you anti-american
Piece of [bleep]
you terrorist!
You know, you use that word
so much
It's lost all meaning,
mr. P.
It's like, at this point,
what's a terrorist?
It's a guy you don't like.
Big deal.
Hoo-rah!
[ screaming ]
Told you to stand down.
You just lost two soldiers
over here. Good men.
Might be time to look
at the terrorist in the mirror.
You want a war?!
I'll put your outer-space ass
in a goddamn phantom zone
With a bar of kryptonite soap
around your neck.
You're done, sanchez!
You hear me?
Oof.
He's really pissed this time.
Why don't you guys just [bleep]
and get it over with.
Okay, well thank you,
summer,
But I think
I've got a better option.
Dad, no.
Ehh...
Hands are tied,
sweetie.
I have to turn myself into
a turkey and trick the president
Into giving me
a presidential turkey pardon.
Again? How many times
have you done this?
I don't know, jerry, how many
years have I lived here?
Careful how you answer that.
Geez, rick, y'know,
y-you've done this a lot.
Don't you think the president
might see it coming this time?
He probably will, morty.
That's all part of the dance.
In the past,
I've inserted myself
Into the potential turkey
pardonee population
By brainwashing
the presidential turkey wrangler
Prior to the ceremony.
But this time, the turkey
wrangler's been euthanized
And the turkeys
will be transported
By armored military vehicles.
Vehicles manufactured by ghost
corporations that I control.
-Which we have audited.
-Allowing me access to...
-Central computers...
-To track the...
Real armored transports,
which he can never...
Totally track
and sneak aboard.
And even if he does,
he'll be on a truck
Full of turkeys
and fully armed marines.
Who won't recognize me
because the human eye
Is inherently face blind
to turkeys.
President: Fortunately, those
marines won't have human eyes.
They'll have turkey eyes.
Jesus ever-loving christ,
why don't you two
Just [bleep]
and get it over with?
Careful, dwayne.
You're only vice president
Because I need 10%
of the white vote.
There's a giant french assassin
attacking new york,
And you're using the war room
to measure dicks
With your alcoholic
sci-fi boyfriend?
Rick sanchez
is more dangerous
Than some steam-powered
french bitch,
And new york can handle its own
global emergencies.
General?
Initiate operation deep gobble.
[ cellphone vibrates ]
Coop,
not on thanksgiving.
It's what I trained for,
mary lou.
It ain't our fight.
Baby.
That little race car driver
you got bakin' in your belly.
What world you want him
rearin' up in?
One where some...
Spiky-haired doctor who
In a lab coat can
change the color of the sky?
Or a world where he can fill
his pickup with hot dogs
And drive it to a jukebox
Full of our demographic's
current favorite music?
Obviously the latter,
but --
Well, that world, mary lou,
the one with those meals,
Vehicles, and songs people in
this 30-mile area prefer...
That world needs
a few good men.
In a secret pentagon lab.
Turning into turkeys.
You come back without feathers,
coop.
God, I love this country.
Hoooo-ah!
♪ I got a pregnant girl
and a pickup truck ♪
♪ I got one by choice
and the other by luck ♪
♪ but now it's time
to turn into a turkey ♪
♪ I hope there
can be peace one day ♪
♪ till then, I pray my dna ♪
♪ gets backed up ♪
General green: These pills
contain tracking chips
That identify each of you
as individuals.
That will be important later.
♪ gobble, gobble ♪
♪ when I turn into a turkey ♪
♪♪
Alright, boys,
search every bird.
If sanchez is here,
I wanna hear you gobblin'.
Let me look at you,
scum.
Get outta here,
you wobbleneck.
Sarge, this -- this ain't
like the simulation, man.
I don't like it
-keep it together, martinez.
Eyes are on the ground,
sir.
No sign of einstein.
Stay frosty, gentlemen.
I want this pardoning pipeline
airtight.
Sir!
We have hacked the garage door.
We are in.
Eyes on the bogey.
Or you've got eyes
on a robot.
All due respect, sir,
I know flesh when I see it!
Those flesh-covered [burps]
robots should buy us some time.
The pardonable turkeys
should be on that truck.
Ship, go stealth.
Rodriguez, fincher.
Get eyes on that.
Huh.
Turkey marines.
The president
came to play.
Jam those two radios.
Ship: Confirmed.
[ radio static ]
ah! Geez!
Fincher, rodriguez, come in!
Copy, copy, tango,
all good.
Just a couple of branches
on the roof.
Don't ever turn your radio
off again.
-We will not surrender.
-We will never surrender.
-Oh, yeah?
Bring in
the david blaine box.
Damn, is that
a david blaine box?
I told you we should have just
gone to my parents' house.
No, you didn't.
Well, I didn't say it out loud,
But it should be
well known by now
That I'd always
rather be there.
-Oh, god, oh no!
-Aw, geez, rick!
Sir, we've got rick and morty
inside the box!
Then that confirms it.
Sir?
No david blaine box
can hold rick sanchez.
Scan the turkey truck!
Huh. That's weird.
Id chips for fincher
and rodriguez are glitching.
Sanchez...
I'll deal with
this bastard myself.
Sir, don't be a cowboy.
You can't
get re-elected dead.
System is calibrated,
sir.
That pill contains a tracking
chip that will identify --
I know,
it'll be important later!
Do it.
[ screams ]
Reporter: Moments from now,
The president will be
pardoning a turkey...
Home stretch, morty.
Here comes dip [bleep]
right on schedule.
Nothing can go wrong now.
Morty: Jesus, is that --
oh [bleep]
The president
has the upper hand.
G-grandpa [bleep] up.
Sunglasses on.
Act like a turkey.
What? Wha--
are you scared?
Act like a turkey!
That's rodriguez
and fincher, sir.
It's rick and morty, you
useless [bleep] stump humper!
Sorry, don't tell 10% of
your friends I called you that.
Mr. President.
Sanchez, admit it.
You lose.
Say it and I'll let
your loser ass go.
[ exhales ]
Did you just try to spit
in my face with no saliva gland?
Just pardon me, dick.
Why the hell would I?
Oh, I dunno,
'cause if I move to canada,
They'll be the best country!
I'll peck your
goddamn eyes out!
Ow!
Hey!
Shit!
My plume!
Hey, back off!
Blueberries!
We got blueberries down!
Hold your positions,
it's a feeding frenzy!
I-I can't see.
I mean, I can see.
270 degrees --
it's too many degrees!
Sir, we are losing
the mental game down here.
General green:
Keep it together, soldier!
Potus is still in that pen --
We just lost new york
to France!
Pull out the president
right now!
Gobble tango --
I want potus out of that pen!
That is an order!
Locate the president's chip!
Roger, roger.
There he is, I got him.
Let's go, boys!
Let's fly out the eagle!
Hey, that's not me!
Package is secure.
Pull us out.
Computer:
Reinjecting subject dna.
[ all scream ]
Hoppin' jehovah, you look
like five pounds of shit
In a whore's lunchbox.
You alright,
mr. President?
Yes.
I am...
The president.
Clean his ass up
and get him to the war room.
Hey!
Gobble squad!
You got the wrong guy,
you morons!
[ gobbling ]
Look at this dumb piece
of [bleep]. Gobbling away.
Get back in there!
Alright boys, you heard the vp.
Pardon is tits up.
Pack up and ship out!
As for you, sanchez...
Bon appétit.
Where is
this elevator going?
Where all the
unchosen turkeys go.
The feeding chamber.
[ creature roars ]
What the [bleep]
is that?
Not what...Who.
The only thing to fear is...
Me!
How the [bleep] does
the white house
Have a cloned spider
of fdr?
It's no clone,
it's fdr.
He was a guinea pig
for the polio vaccine.
We asked ourselves
"what walks the most?"
"we?"
you're taking credit for this?
The office comes with baggage,
morty.
Rick,
I'm afraid to die!
You won't have to be for long,
morty!
We're due to return
to human form any second!
Then what?
Then we just have to not
get eaten by the spider!
Oh, so in other words,
be afraid to die?
Morty, if winning an argument
is that important to you,
You were never alive!
Time for a new deal...
Murder!
President: I'm sick of hearing
how iconic you were!
Try having an historical
administration after facebook
Goes online,
you old-timey bitch!
Morty,
tear open that panel!
How's this
for a fireside chat?
[ screaming ]
Woof.
You just killed fdr.
He was a monster,
though.
Don't mythologize him.
He was a politician.
Speaking of, you kind of saved
our bacon there,
So I'll make you a deal.
You pardon us
and I'll make you human.
Wrong turkey.
Man,
the face blindness is real.
I'd like these...
Men...
Turned back into humans,
please.
Uh, yes, of course,
mr. President.
But I thought we
already rehumanized
All the turkified marines.
I'd like these men
turned back into humans.
I am the president.
Yes, sir.
Uh, sure thing.
Increase their strength
by 1,000%.
But...
That wouldn't be human.
Turkeys have always been
more than human.
Okay, uh, so right there,
now I'm starting to --
I am selling new york
to France.
And giving all of the money
to congress.
[ cheering ]
Now that's how you do it!
He became president today.
[ gasping, murmuring ]
That's right, murmur!
And when you're done,
get me some pants.
If you're the president,
who the hell have we been
Governing the country with
for the last three hours?
An impostor, you good
for nothing idiot!
You humanized
the wrong turkey!
It's possible.
We shouldn't leave
anything to chance.
Wouldn't want congress working
with the wrong president.
A very good point,
mr. President.
Do we believe
this fine feathered,
Collaborative gentleman
to be our commander-in-chief?
Or are we gonna let "mr. Cash
bar at the christmas party"
Stay in office?
All in favor of
turkey president?
You can't be serious.
You think he cares
about america?
Is that why this is happening
to you?
Because you cared
about america?
Guards, these men are...
Oh, what is the word?
Uh, terrorists.
Okay, screw this.
Go, go, sanchez laser fists.
Oh [bleep] I was a turkey
for a while, wasn't I?
Okay, guy's pretty strong.
Mary todd lincoln!
Who's dead weight now,
bitch?
♪♪
You should regain feeling
in your ass in a minute.
Sorry my turrets
blew up your motorcycle.
Just give me
some goddamn clothes.
Must suck to have your only
safe haven be my house.
Y-you want
your regular outfit
Or should we dress you
like a terrorist?
I don't need to be here,
and I'm still the president.
Oh, glad to hear it. That means
you can give me that pardon.
Or -- or I could put you
out with the trash.
What is your problem?!
Why do you hate this country?
I hate every country
in the universe, brother!
They're job placement
programs
For the politicians
that invent them --
Okay,
fight club.
I get paid to protect
the sidelines you sit on!
You get paid
to make sports metaphors!
I clean your litterbox!
So your little nerd paws
don't have to touch
Another nerd's nerdy poopies
while you're flexing
Your grody little edge lord anus
all over it!
Guys, maybe you're both right
and both wrong.
Both: Shut up, morty!
You little bitch, you destroyed
the constitution.
You're the biggest
booger eater here!
Do not talk to my son
that way.
Sorry, mrs. Smith.
The two of you
are ruining thanksgiving.
Together.
And you can both either
come to the table
And eat food with my family
Or you can keep doing what
you're doing at the corner bar.
Bars actually suck
at thanksgiving.
Dorothy: I'm still trying to
sort through this.
One of you wishes you had
the personal quality
Known as courage
But the other two of you
want actual vital organs?
This charlie kaufman reboot
of "wizard of oz"
Is destroying itself.
That's why I need a brain!
I'm doing a terrible job
writing this!
Pass the potatoes.
Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
Good green beans, mom.
The turkey's raw, dad.
Shit's potato bunz.
Sorry, summer,
the united states enclosed us
In a shimmer bubble
that scrambled my oven timer.
So I guess elections
do have consequences.
Eat my ass, jerry.
I've seen your irs records.
You can blame me
once you have taxable income.
[ laughs ] yes, jerry is
a piece of [bleep].
I agree.
[ news fanfare plays ]
Um, guys?
What's that?
Paula, as you can see,
president curtis has enacted
A plan to turn
all turkeys in america
Into hybrid super soldiers.
The move has 100% approval
from congress
Following its third pay raise
in six hours.
Back to you.
♪♪
My god,
the bastard's unhinged!
There won't be a single bird
left in dc!
Oh, wow, wiping out a native
population on thanksgiving?
That's never happened before.
What did you just say?
Well, I-I associated
thanksgiving with genocide.
It's what young people do.
I wasn't trying to --
The crypt
of the new world.
That could be our one chance
to turn this thing around.
You know
about the crypt?
Ugh, so the treasure's
already gone.
Wait, is that why you were
stealing the constitution?
You old fart dick.
The crypt of the new world
isn't a treasure.
But it might be our only hope.
Come on.
But isn't the crypt
underneath dc?
The turkey president's
got an army.
An actual army.
And an air force.
And marines --
slow down, morty.
Walk us through
every military service.
Does somebody have a pen?
We've got something
more powerful
Than every army
in the world.
Well, no, we don't,
but with the right speech,
We could get a handful
of well-trained hillbillies.
Eh, it worked against
the british. I'm in.
Birds replacin' people.
What would johnny cash
or dale earnhardt say?
He'd say "it's time
to walk the line"
Or "drive very fast
between two of them."
We don't serve
your kind here.
Oh, my god,
are you serious?
Read the sign.
He's my boss, marvin.
It's okay.
Mistrusting presidents
is a patriotic duty.
And that guy on tv
isn't me.
He's a turkey
infused with my dna.
I'll be damned.
Well,
I'm racist.
You better not be here
to take my man again.
-Mary lou.
-I'm poor!
And pregnant!
With a poor person!
And I need you.
And 10% of your baby.
Now, look, I know it's gonna
take more than some speech.
But what is a speech?
Isn't it just a question?
And isn't that a question too?
Speeches are words.
Repeated words.
Listed words.
Repeated lists
of repeated words.
None of that matters.
You know what does matter?
Me. Asking you.
"will you do what I say?"
Just two questions,
chief.
Lock?
And load?
They're rhetorical, sir!
Lock and load!
[ cheering ]
♪♪
Sir, we've got rick and morty
coming in what appears to be
An unlicensed
"star wars" at-at.
Or as the millennials say,
a-t, a-t.
So it begins.
Gobblers!
Tonight, we rise!
[ gobbles ]
♪♪
Aww, geez, geez, geez.
Nice driving, sanchez.
Wire's down,
pen is clear.
You know the goddamn rules!
If you see something clucking
or pecking,
Put a buckshot
in its panties.
[ roars ]
♪♪
Jesus christ!
T-they got johnson!
He got off easy.
Cooper: Hold off the bastards!
What now, rick?
Time to turn up
the broiler.
[ roars ]
♪♪
Whoa, I-is that --
The crypt of
the new world.
The treasure you were after
is this country's oldest secret.
One disguised by centuries
of thanksgiving folklore.
Is that...
A turkey dinosaur?
America's original rulers.
Merciless beasts, grazing on
the flesh of cowering humans.
Then, in the 15th century,
a vessel crashed.
Two vessels, really.
On board --
our saviors.
Sanchez, pull that lever
at the same time I do.
♪♪
[ all growl ]
Oh [bleep]
they're gonna fight!
Morty:
No, wait, they love each other!
They were at war
when they arrived,
But they united over
their hatred of turkeys.
And what they love even more
than each other
Is kicking turkey butt.
Gentlemen!
Ba'ruka dar tin'in yo-tei!
Coooooooooorn!
♪♪
It's working!
Come on, sanchez, let's power
down the humanizer ray.
Whose side are we on?
I don't know, but we've done
enough to pay for college.
Look, we're almost there.
Sorry,
my turn for a surprise.
Damn, this guy loves
arriving from the shadows.
Look around. You can't
beat our ancient warriors.
Can't I? My kind has always
dealt with predators.
That's why
we sleep in trees.
And that's why, in the wild,
we fly.
♪♪
Now you must choose ---
Fight me,
or stop that weapon from turning
All of america's turkeys
into a new master race.
You dumb dip [bleep],
there's three of us,
And two of us
are spacemen.
Obviously they're gonna
save america
And bring that
monument home,
And I'm gonna
kick your ass.
Oh, and, sanchez?
You got your pardon.
Aw.
Shut up, morty.
Come on.
Let's go, bitch.
So be it.
Is it true
what turkey man said?
That turkeys
sleep in trees?
Who the hell cares,
morty?
Let's just [burps] deactivate
this [bleep]
Calibrating.
[ gobbles ]
Targeting all american turkeys.
Oh, my god,
they gave it a voice?
Who is this for?
We're in space.
Geez, rick,
I-I-I guess them?
Morty, use this carefully.
Crack the humanizer core
and cut the blue wire.
You hear me?
Blue wire.
Wha-- why don't we
just blow it up?
It's a national monument,
[bleep] nut!
We just got pardoned.
You really wanna do this again
next year?
[ both grunting ]
You forgot something,
turkey man.
No matter what you got people
to believe,
I'm still
the goddamn president.
And you forget, in the one day
I've had your job,
I've learned
10 times as much.
I've underestimated you.
For the last time.
♪♪
Rick, they're not exactly
primary colors!
A-are -- are we cool with, like,
t-turquoise?
Are you kidding me, morty?
Just cut the damn thing!
[ gobbles ]
Oh, shit, oh [bleep] --
Targets acquired.
Activating weapon.
Oh, shit! Oooooooh!
Heritage destroyed.
Morty!
God damn it,
you had one job!
[ groans ]
I beat you.
Look at me,
you turkey ass bitch.
[ laughs ]
Wait, why are you --
Is that a wishbone?
I wish to explode.
[ laughs ]
♪♪
Man:
The berlin wall has come down.
Man #2:
It's called the playstation.
The winner is...
"shakespeare in love."
-Playstation 2.
-Hurricane katrina
Slams louisiana...
-Playstation 3.
-This is maroon five...
-Playstation 4.
-The cubbies win!
-I want a playstation 5.
[ gasping ]
I wasn't sure when
to pull you out.
I-I assumed you were running
through your whole life.
Yes.
And what a life it was.
Gentlemen, thank you once again
for saving this nation.
Slloosh garg blurrg.
I don't speak googa.
The cia only taught me
your activation phrase.
But if I could say
anything...
I'd say give america
one more chance.
Kalaak 'ha
benben prilo garg.
Oh, my god, they're gonna fight.
Th-they're really gonna fight.
-Aw, they love each other!
-Never gets old.
I'll never get tired
of that.
So...After those aliens
discovered america...
They went into
hibernation,
Leaving us the technology
we used to lead the free world.
That and also to do stuff
like slavery.
I always thought we were...
More special than that.
Like we invented everything
and did everything
And that's why
we own everything.
Now I-I-I-I don't know
what to feel.
Feel thankful, morty.
Feel thankful.
♪♪
I know, baby.
Coop, honey, should we get
lucky charms or kibble bibbitz?
You know
we can't afford either.
Baby, the president owes you.
You saved him.
Ain't his fault our insurance
got cut.
They gotta build missiles.
Ugh, fine, just -- can y'all
hold jakey for a second?
[ high-pitched ringing ]
[ jakey crying ]
Bag boy:
What the hell's he doin?
Deli guy:
I think he's foraging.
Crazy bastard thinks
he's a turkey.
Well, I refuse to pay
for this man's health care.
♪♪
Did you get any of that?