Ahh, I love that new
T-shirt smell.
Chicks are gonna be up
all up in our biz
when they see us wearing these
Rick and Morty custom tees.
I bet we could
sell these.
Hells yeah.
I [bleep] love merch!
[ Thunder crashes ]
Aah!
The rain! It -- It burns!
Oh [bleep]
Quick, Morty,
protect the shirts!
The door!
Open the door!
Rick!
Is it --
Morty,
will ya stop tryna--
[ Lock clicks ]
Okay, there, it's open.
Jesus.
My skin is on fire.
W-Why is the rain
doing that?
[ Laughing evilly ]
My acid rain will destroy
all things green and natural
or my name isn't Diesel Weasel.
[ Laughs evilly ]
[ People screaming ]
Huh. Well, that guy's
easy to please.
Your acid rain is
an acid pain...
in the butt, Diesel Weasel!
Yikes.
Wow.
Who's the chick in need
of a dialogue pass?
First order of business
is to clean up this acid rain
with a little wind!
Yoww!
Ow! Ow, my leg!
Wow.
And now an elemental punch
that's too hot to handle!
Wa-kah!
Oh, wow.
Curse you, Planetina!
I'll get you next slime!
[ Laughs evilly ]
There's only one solution
for Earth's pollution -- you!
[ Ting! ]
Wow.
Morty, if you say "wow"
one more time,
I swear to [bleep] God...
Are you crazy, Rick?
She's right there!
Yeah, get that aluminum, Morty.
It's 8% of the Earth.
We'll need every atom.
Thanks!
Every litter-bit helps!
[ Gasps ] Your problem!
Excuse me?
S-Sorry.
I-I-I wanted to say,
"N-No problem, you're welcome,"
a-a-and it came out
"your problem."
[ Chuckles ]
I-I'm an idiot. Sorry.
You're not an idiot.
You recycled.
I-I'm Morty.
Nice to meet you, Morty.
I'm Planetina, and I hope you
have a wonderful day.
[ Horn honks ]
Rick: Hey!
The [bleep] we doin' here?
Uhh, y-y-you
like soft serve?
There's a shop
around the bend.
Oh, I don't eat
ice cream.
Veal is a product of
the dairy industry.
Oh, that's not good.
No, it is not.
[ Horn honks ]
Oh, my God!
Come on! Let's go!
I know a place that serves
cruelty-free doughnuts.
If you'd like, I could
fly you and your friend there
easy-peasy, lemon-squeezy.
Okay, I-I-I'll ask him.
He -- He said he can't come.
Let's go!
What the [bleep]
was that shit?
♪♪
[ Electricity crackling ]
Planetina:
The Earth is in danger!
Pollution and waste
are ruining our planet.
Mother Nature has enlisted
the help of four young adults
from each major ethnicity --
and when things look bad,
and I mean really bad --
they combine the powers
of their elemental rings
to create me!
Planetina,
conservationist super person!
There's only one solution...
for Earth's pollution -- you!
P-Pretty cool, huh?
I-I can't believe I actually
hung out with Planetina.
How old is this woman?
She looks very mature.
She's a sentient amalgam
of natural elements,
so I don't believe age
applies to her.
Great. Taylor Murphy dumps me
the day before his
hella-big pool party
and my little brother's
dating a phase four
super hero.
Just shoot me in the [bleep]
head until I die.
Hey, hey, none of that,
Summerfest.
Look what you're doing to your
sister, you piece of [bleep]
Is it weird that she hasn't
texted me yet?
Yes.
No.
What if I told you that
your Grandpa Rick's
got something up his sleeve
that's so Rick-diculous
that it's gonna make you
forget all about
that stupid asshole
that dumped you?
[ Plates clatter ]
Hey, my egg plate!
Morglutz, Slartivart,
and Ferkus 9 --
three planets are all ending
in a delayed succession
of cataclysmic events.
A jam like this comes around
only once in a lifetime.
Morglutz's sun is
going supernova,
Slartivart is falling
into a black hole,
and Ferkus 9 is getting
"Deep Impact"-ed
by an asteroid.
They're all having a major,
final blow out --
and I'm gonna drug it up
and suck it up before each one
goes ka-blamo,
and I'm taking
my favorite grandkid
along with me!
Hells yeah.
10 seconds on Morglutz,
and you'll be up to your
neck in I-could-give-two-
[bleep]-about-
what's-his-ass.
And also herpes.
Um...
Oh, my God,
thank you,
Grandpa Rick!
I'm gonna
go pack my rollie.
Um, Summer? I-I-I haven't given
you my approval yet.
[ Door closes ]
Summer, approval
is yet to be given here!
[ Phone chimes ]
There's a huge forest fire
like 200 miles from here!
This is amazing!
Planetina's bound to be there.
Mom, I-I need the credit card
to buy a train ticket.
Absolutely not.
Mom, this is the biggest
wildfire of the year!
You're not going!
Da [bleep] I'm not.
Last time I checked,
this wasn't Russia.
It's not Russia, Jerry.
My heart is broken,
and I deserve to let loose,
and if you don't like it,
you can suck my bigger [bleep]
Adios, C-words.
Morty, I don't want you
getting hurt.
Please, think this over.
I don't want to think!
I want to see
a girl I like.
If you don't want to
help me,
I'll find my own goddamn way
to the wildfire.
[ Door slams ]
[ Door slamming ]
I'll get the wine.
Thank you.
The Governor has implemented
a mandatory evacuation.
Abandon all hope, people!
Nothing will stop this fire.
Nothing!
[ Air whooshing ]
Scratch that! Here's Planetina,
Savioress of Earth!
Yeeouch!
Talk about a hot foot.
Better put this wildfire on ice!
Morty: Come here, little buddy.
Come on, come on, come on,
I gotcha.
Morty?! What are you
doing here?
Oh, hey!
Y-You're here, too?
Yeah, I heard about
the wildfire back home,
and, you know, I stopped
by to lend a hand.
H-Here you go, fella.
All safe now.
[ Chuckles ] Ahh, rabbits --
al-always hopping --
Never stoppin'.
[ Chuckles nervously ]
Y-Yeah.
S-So it was, uh,
great hanging --
hanging out
the other day.
I-I was getting kind of a --
I mean I-I got kind of
a p-positive vibe.
Oh, good.
I was putting one out.
I-I really like you.
Holy [bleep]
I-I-I mean, uh, well,
oh, all right.
Next step, you w-want to
go out again?
I do! But, uh, Morty,
I have kids.
Oh, I-I-I'll get along
with them. I'm-I'm a kid.
No, I mean the four kids
that bring me into existence
by combining the power
of their elemental rings
so I can save Earth
from ecological disasters.
Oh, them!
No, I-I know about them.
I-I like them.
Oh, good.
Well, here they are now.
Hey, buddy, you
want an autograph?
That's 20 bucks a pop.
No, Eddie,
he's my friend.
Morty, these are my kids,
The Tina-Teers.
Oh, hey.
Tina, girl,
have you gained weight?
Uh, well, I had a plant-based
doughnut yesterday.
Just a half.
Sugar is worst thing
for figure, darling.
You want to be ugly?
Heh, I-I thought
they'd be younger.
They've been manifesting me
since the mid-'90s.
A lot has changed
since then.
This is freaking
you out, huh?
It is a lot
to take in.
I understand.
Well, I guess
I'd better go.
See you around.
Hi-de-ho, TV 58!
Planetina,
you single-handily saved
a National Forest
with ease.
I do what I can,
but I can't do it alone!
And who's your friend
over there?
Oh!
This is Morty Smith.
He traveled 200 miles just
to save a rabbit from the fire.
He's a very special guy.
So, are you two dating?
Oh, um, w-- I-I-I --
Yes, we are.
[ '80s pop music plays ]
[Bleep] love.
All right, time
to set the rules.
Lay it on me.
No whining.
Done.
No crying.
As if.
And absolutely, positively
no getting attached.
We're here to smash max ass --
quantity over quality.
Deal?
Deal!
I'm gonna eat so much [bleep],
you're gonna shit.
Check this out. This is gonna
be me at the party --
b-b-laaaah!
B-b-blaaaah!
Oh, is that another [bleep]
Don't mind if
I-- b-b-blaaaah!
Ho-ho! This'll be me across
the room -- "Excuse me, miss.
It appears that you have
an uneaten [bleep]
Allow me --
lalalalalaaah!
Lalalalalaaah!
B-b-blaaaah!
Whoo!
[Bleep] super nova party!
Love is a lie!
Hack the planet!
The world's ending,
and for some reason,
I want to die with you
more than anyone else.
[ Giggles ] Wow!
Yo, Rick, don't look now,
but someone's giving you
the big eye.
[ Vomiting ]
'Scuse me.
I got to see a man about
a horse I'd rather
have sex with.
Aah!
Hello.
I'm Rick.
Hey. So, the world's ending,
and for some reason,
I want to die with you
more than anyone else.
Hello.
Summer:
Have fun, Grandpa Rick!
No commitments!
♪ I flew to you on an airplane ♪
[ Keys tapping ]
♪ I was afraid that
you gave me strength ♪
♪ Forever, birds were
soul twin loves ♪
♪ Baby, come back to me ♪
♪ Baby, come back like it was ♪
Surprise!
What are you doing here?
Mmm!
I told my kids I went out
to recycle batteries.
All kidding aside,
everyone should discard
used batteries at
proper disposal centers
instead of tossing them into
a regular waste bin.
Thanks for the tip.
♪ Flowers never last forever ♪
♪ But we can make it
past forever ♪
[ Dolphins squeaks ]
♪ Baby, come home to me ♪
♪ Baby, you're home with me ♪
[ Cheering ]
Solus is collapsing
in five zip-zops.
If we time it right,
we can [bleep] together
as the sun explodes.
Sounds ah-mazing.
Say, I think I left
my purse back at the bar.
Can both of you go
get it for me?
Anything for you,
Mrs. Obama.
Time to ghost,
Grandpa Rick.
Rick: Righty-right.
Meet me at the car.
One of these has to be hers.
Where'd she go?
I guess we'll have to
start without her.
Oh, her loss.
B-b-blaaaaaaaaah!
Whoo! Planet number two,
let's do it!
Sorry, I took so long.
I had to ditch some clingers.
[ Slurring ] Let's do it.
Up the [bleep], y'all.
Geez, you okay to drive?
Shiii!
'Course, I-I-I'm mable.
Bu[burps]ckle up.
[ Crashing ]
Yeah!
Whoo!
The best week of my life!
Daphne: Hello.
What was that?
Nothin'.
Who wants to see
the most radadelic
lady-version
of a super hero?
[ Cheering ]
Fire!
Water!
Air!
And Dirt!
[ Crowd gasps ]
Oh, no, the convention.
Morty, wake up!
We overslept.
What's happening?
Hey, there's a little
boy on her!
Oh, d-d-drop
the curtain!
There is no curtain!
Idiots, zap her away!
No, no, no.
Wait, I-I --
Whoa!
Security!
What did you do?
B-Bring her back!
No! Let me go!
Sorry, folks.
Planetina will be back
in a moment.
Until then, who wants a limited
edition Funko for only $50?
[ Cheers and applause ]
This is very bad.
We are about
to close deal.
We cannot
afford controversy.
Don't you worry.
I know how ta deal with
this Morty kid.
[ Cheering ]
Hey, a bunch of us
are going over to Hibler's place
to shoot ourselves.
Y-You want to come with?
Sorry, but no man's tying down
Sum-Sum tonight.
Hit the dicks.
Your loss, honey.
You could have
had allllllll this.
[ Sobs ]
Hey, check it out!
There's old people dancing!
[ Dance music plays ]
♪♪
Damn, girl.
Your moves is tight.
Hello.
Summer: Rick!
What the WTF is that
Morglutzian doing here?
Morglutzian? She's --
She's not Morglutzian.
She's the only blue person
here without three eyes!
Okay, fine. B-Busted.
Thi-Thi-This is, uh, Daphne.
Daphne, this is Summer,
my granddaughter.
Granddaughter?
Hello.
Daphne heard about
our little party crawl,
and I told her
she could come with.
I-I-In the trunk.
What in the actual
[bleep], Rick?
We said no commitments!
This was to be our
Apocalypse Party-crawl!
You broke the rules!
Squares follow rules, Summer.
Daphne's down to freak.
She's up for any [burps] sick,
nasty thing I want to do.
Hello.
Oh, yeah, baby.
[ Both moaning ]
All right, fellas,
take five.
He ain't gonna give me
any trouble.
[ Lock clicks ]
Morty: Where's Planetina?
Don't you worry about her.
I want to see her!
Planetina's got a lot of
responsibilities.
People depend on her.
And you, my friend,
are a distraction
we can't afford right now.
She's just a product
to you, isn't she?
Something to make
money off of.
W-Well, Planetina's
more than that.
She's a brilliant,
living thing, and I love her.
Oh, you love her?
Well, guess what.
We own her.
But not for long,
of course.
We're gonna sell her
to some Arab overseas.
Fire.
As for you,
maybe she won't
love you so much if you
ain't so pretty no more.
Stop! Yah!
Ow!
Y-You want to [bleep] with me?
Do you?
Stupid [bleep]
shit hole!
Aaaaaah!
[ Grunts ]
Guard: Boss, what's happening?
Let us in!
Aah!
[ Spits ] Fire!
[ Screaming ]
Fire!
Can we conclude our business?
I'm eager to celebrate
my purchase of
Planetina over dinner,
and these infant seals
aren't getting any younger.
Momentarily, comrade.
Soon, our partner
will return.
Ugh! What is taking
Eddie so long?
His phone keep going
to voicemail.
Eddie:
♪ Start leaving a message ♪
♪ I can't make it
to the phone ♪
Just kidding. It's Eddie.
Go [bleep] yourself.
[ Voicemail beeps ]
Which one of you
ordered a pizza?
No one order pizza.
What is this?
Well, I got a cheesy Italian,
extra crispy just for you.
I know those cheek bones
like they're me own!
It's Eddie!
[Bleep] Mother!
Kill him!
Stone! Stone!
Fire!
Aah!
Airs!
[ Air whooshing ]
Cold Water!
Dirt!
Fire!
Wa--
[ Screaming ]
Airs.
Now we can be together,
Planetina.
I am an individual
character.
I represent no group.
Fire!
Aaah!
Water! Dirt! Airs!
[ Screaming ]
Aah!
Not good!
[ Baby seals growling, barking ]
Blib...
Naga...
Threve...
Verillex...Gam!
Happy Apocalypse!
-Oh, my gaaah!
-This is awful!
Why were we cheering?!
[ Rumbling ]
Hello.
Got any agua around here?
Mama's got to hydrate.
Glove box.
Oh, yeah.
Rick is the coolest
guy ever.
We're total soul mates.
He's gonna show me the wonders
of the universe.
Ha! Once we get to
the next planet,
Grandpa Rick is gonna
ditch you, like, so fast.
Oh, is that so?
Uh-huh, nobody is tying
that guy down -- ever.
The only chick seeing
the universe with Rick is me.
Not if I keep Rick's
mouth full of these.
Oh, my --
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
That's right, girlfriend.
This is what
you're up against.
Wars were fought
over these.
They've ruined kings,
inspired presidents.
A hundred songs
and nine national anthems
have been written
about them.
Best set of elbow-titties
on Morglutz.
And now, thanks to Rick,
the best in the galaxy.
You want me
to put them away?
Please.
Sure.
But only because
you're Rick's granddaughter.
Daph? Daphne?
Where are ya, baby?
Papa needs some more
elbow grease.
Comin'! Ya might want to keep
your eyes on the road.
It's about to get sloppy.
Hello!
Hello.
Ugh!
[ Loud moaning, bed creaking ]
Then I put my sunglasses on
and walked out
like nothing happened.
I'm finally free.
All because of Morty.
What a romantic story
about our son killing
a room full of people.
Your turn.
Uh, seven.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven!
Oyyy, don't
punch my lunch!
A-ha! Eat it!
I'm out of food cards.
How 'bout I loan you
two quiche at 10%?
That's so generous.
My turn!
Double sixes, baby!
One, two, three...
So, what's next for Planetina?
Well, now that I'm not
distracted by book signings
and publicity stunts,
Morty and I can concentrate on
more important things.
Like school.
Like moving in.
Planetina doesn't have
a place to stay now,
so I said she could
live with us.
Holy shit. Morty, no.
I'm so full!
What do you mean, no?
Whoo!
Don't punch my lunch.
[ Laughs ]
I wouldn't be a burden,
Mrs. Smith.
I only want to spend
as much time
as possible
with your son.
My son is 14, miss.
I'm sorry, Morty.
You're way too young.
But y-y-y-you were a teenager
when Dad got you pregnant.
I was 17!
That's at least
26 in boy years.
I'm sure Planetina is very nice,
but when you're a teenager,
love is fleeting, at best.
You underestimate Morty.
He is a very mature young man.
See, Mom? I told you!
This is not happening.
End of discussion.
Planetina, I think you
should leave, please.
Okay, Mrs. Smith.
Oh, no! [ Belches ]
Mom, I hate you!
You suck!
Hey, now, it's only a game.
Shut up!
Okay.
My whole life,
I've never fit in
anywhere.
Everything I have to say
is always met with
an eye roll as if
the act of hearing
what I have to say is some
exhausting chore.
Nobody in this family thinks
I can say or do anything right!
I've been all over the universe,
met hundreds of people,
and Planetina's the only one
I've ever met that makes me feel
like I belong, and you just
kicked her out of our house!
Morty, please --
I will never
forgive you for this!
♪ Get the sword
and throw it far ♪
♪ Let it shine under
the morning star ♪
Morty! Morty, come back!
[ Air whooshing ]
♪ Who are you? ♪
♪ Who am I to you? ♪
♪ I am the antichrist to you ♪
[ Lightning crackling ]
♪♪
♪ Fallen from the sky
with grace ♪
♪ Into your arms race ♪
♪♪
Get out!
All of you, get out of there!
You're killing the planet!
Your people didn't
get the votes.
Leave, or I'll have
you arrested.
It's you people who
should be arrested.
Gutting the land, poisoning
the air your children breathe?!
Can't you see what
you're doing?!
Easy for you to say!
You can live how you want!
We need the jobs.
Let's go, boys.
She can't stop us.
W-We'll get
them next time.
There's no time left!
Can't you hear
the Earth screaming?
You filthy murderers!
Planetina, stop it!
There's only one solution
for Earth's pollution!
[ Screaming ]
Oh, my God, no.
♪ Who am I to you? ♪
♪ I am the antichrist to you ♪
No!
I can't believe I'm banging
my co-workers.
And I'm the boss!
This gay sex with
my Dad is terrific!
What was I thinking?
It'll all be over soon!
Last chance to pee on me!
Anyone?!
Okay, Grandpa,
the meteor's almost here.
We can go now.
Ah, nah, we still got time.
Well, then stop being in love
and start having fun.
Ah, love's pretty fun, Summer.
Just give it a chance.
It's not even
real love!
Daphne's just with you
so she can keep surviving!
Ah, the young --
so naive.
[ Footsteps squishing ]
[ Squishing ]
[ Groans ]
Eww, gross.
[ Engine starts ]
[ Windshield squeaking ]
[ Explosion ]
Congratulations, Ferkisians!
Your apocalypse is aborted.
And, Grandpa,
you and I can go home.
Daphne,
you may come with.
If you want to
and don't have to.
I don't know what
you're getting at, Summer.
Obviously,
Daphne wants to --
Aw, you cold bitch.
Hello?
Goodbye.
Hey, she's the one
that saved the world!
Now we got to go
to work tomorrow!
[ All booing ]
You [bleep]
Sorry I messed
things up with Daphne.
Just shut up.
I get it.
Really? You're not mad?
I'm furious.
But I have to admit,
it was pretty Rick of you
to avert an apocalypse
in a tantrum of cynicism
just to destroy
one dumb relationship.
Still, sorry.
Eh, I would've done
the same for you.
Promise?
Love you, Grandpa Rick.
Don't make it weird.
[ Phone chimes ]
[ Keys tapping ]
Please go.
I-I-I can't see you anymore.
Don't you even want to try
to make it work?
We were so close.
You murdered 300 people.
And you murdered
my kids.
They were gonna
sell you away forever.
Eddie was
trying to kill me!
Th-Those miners
were innocent.
Those innocent miners voted men
into power to protect
their precious jobs
so they can buy more
plastic garbage and eat
the corpses of tortured animals.
The system
is broken, Morty.
This is the only way
I can save Earth,
the only way
I can save you.
If that's the only way,
I-I don't want to be saved.
Please, go.
But...I love you.
I-I-I can't --
I-I can't love you.
I-I just can't.
Please understand.
No.
[ Sniffles ]
I'll go, but don't you dare
ask me to understand.
Planetina,
I-I'm so sorry.
[Bleep] you.
Morty?
Are you all right?
She's gone, Mom!
She's gone!
[ Sobs ]
I loved her so much!
I know you did, honey.
[ Crying ]
Shh, Mommy's here.
♪ Let it shine under
the morning star ♪
♪ Who are you? ♪
♪ Who am I to you? ♪
♪ I am the antichrist to you ♪
♪ Fallen from the sky
with grace ♪
♪ Into your arms ♪
[ Door bells jingle ]
[ Clears throat ]
Good morning.
'Morning.
Slow day, huh?
Yep.
Probably because
everybody thought
the world wouldn't be,
you know, like, here today.
Mm-hmm.
Mom in back?
Mom's not talking to us.
Because we had sex?
Yes.
Uh, yeah.
That makes sense.
Happy birthday,
by the way.
[ Sighs ]