Oh! Oh! Ah!
It's the crow man!
Give it a second.
Maybe he's taking
it out to surrender.
He's anti-heroic. Run!
I don't understand.
He's only one man!
With the power of
a thousand crows.
Oh, oh! Ooh!
Good luck.
Crows and owls have
always been at war,
but why do you care?
What's the point?
Here's two.
Ha-ha! Yeah. Cool. Morty?
Uh, h-hey, man!
Good to see you!
Y-You're, like, looking, like,
into crows... still.
Oh, uh, two crows,
you remember Morty.
Morty, two crows.
It's good to see you,
but if you'd given me
more of a heads up --
Well, I-I was just
in the neighborhood.
I-It wasn't like --It's just
that the battle for crows
is kind of never-ending.
Huh. Right.
A little pointless, then, right?
That came out wrong,
s-sounded judgy.
- Crowhorse. Crowhorse.
- Okay.
- Looks like...
looks like they're
leading you to a thing.
Take care, Morty.
You -- You too!
I-I'm doing good, by the way.
Oh, my dad was gonna eat
that yogurt you left in the fridge
but I-I told him --
I'm looking for...
Crow Scare.
The scarecrow?
The evil scarecrow?
Come on. Whoever
gives him up first lives.
Fine, I can kill
an extra asshole.
Helps me get my steps in.
Ah!
Ahhh!
Rick! Morty?
Wood?!
Aghhhh!
Uh, Morty, why
are you now like 40?
Th-That's how
long it's been, Rick.
Oh, uh, I guess we can
have a drink together, then.
Do you have a rum and Coke?
What are you, 20?
Oh, bless your heart.
Time be goin' by, don't she?
That's your reaction
to finding out
you wasted your entire life?
I feel okay.
Well -- well, what about me?!
Whoa. Excuse us, boys.
You don't wanna
be here for this.
I thought if I gave
you enough space,
you'd outgrow this... phase.
Here's your drink, poser.
Dad got sick, you know. Stage 4.
You would've loved it.
Summer's a nurse --
well, pretty much a nurse.
She -- She married a junkie.
Rick, come home,
while we still
got a little time.
Morty, what we
had wasn't healthy.
And this is?
Y-You've had a thousand
adventures with these crows.
When are you gonna
kill their big bad?
First off, the
"will they/kill they"
is everything to my guys.
And second, fuck you for trying
to undermine my happiness.
This may be the last time
you ever lay eyes on me!
I hope that's not true, Morty,
because you look like sshit,
and this is not how I
wanna remember you.
Now that I have his two crows,
nothing will stop me from
eliminating Crow Rick.
Don't defend him to me.
I don't even get
what you see in him.
You're right.
We should be enjoying
the time we have together.
Crow Rick!
Oh, I-I know what this
must look like, but --
It looks like my arch
nemesis, Crow Scare,
and my sidekicks planning
adventures together.
You are hardly the victim here.
I was adventuring
with these two crows
before you ever came along.
What do you mean,
"using me as a rebound?"
You feel like I was using
you as a rebound, too?
Well, shit, this
lost all meaning.
I guess it could
have been worse.
At least adventuring
was just a metaphor
for romantic partnership,
so it's not a real break-up.
Speak for yourself.
We immensely enjoy
each other's bodies.
What?! Ugh! No!
Sounds like the
man's asking for proof.
Let's show him, fellas!
- I-I asked for zero proof!
- Ahh!
Zero proof!
I'm giving you free will.
Yah!
Submit to Crow Horse!
Whoops.
- Rick?
- Wubba lubba dub dub! I'm back, pal!
Morty, who's at the door?
Wait a minute. I thought
you died gruesomely?
W-what the hell's going on here?
See, uh, the --
the thing is, uh...
Can you please make
Morty 14 again, Dad?
This is ridiculous.
Okay, look, I-I may
have used an aging serum
to kind of emotionally
blackmail you a little.
I kind of figured, and
I totally get it, Morty,
I-I'm done with the two crows.
Like, they were super clingy
and I'm ready to make this work.
Let's just hit the reset button.
Well, no, honey,
not a reset, okay?
Tell your grandpa that
you're worthy of his respect
and you want to be treated
differently from now on.
I refuse to do that.
I-I'm desperate to
get back together.
- Just like his old man.
- Don't worry, honey.
That's just Morty's
middle age talking.
He'll be less
codependent once we get
more of his life in
front of him again.
Uh, I'd like him to stay 40
so he can keep
buying my friends molly.
I'd rather throw my vote away
than use it to support
a flawed system.
Can we make our first
adventure fixing this?
I keep thinking about -lawn care.
- Okay, buddy.
Who sold you this
shitty aging serum?
- What did he look like?
- Just like you.
I-I got it -from the Citadel.
- Hot damn.
Hittin' the ground running
with a Citadel episode.
See ya later, masturbators.
Hi! I'm Citadel's
new mascot, Andy,
because this place
wouldn't be home
without Ricks "Andy" Mortys.
Dumb.
Ooh, what happened
to this place?
There's a Morty president now.
Aw, that's cute. They
rebuilt. They made it nicer.
They made it Glendale.
God damn, you are cantankerous.
Even pooping hurts now.
Yeah, well, this place
is gonna fix you right up.
Okay, so, we've
got a standard Morty
that's been aged to... 40?
Can you reverse it?
Well, if you look
at it like a bone,
what we can do is break
his age in two places,
remove the middle, and
graft its ends back together.
Th-that sounds really violent.
It's not a literal bone, Morty.
Oh, okay.
Ah, brace yourself,
the process does also
break every bone in your body.
Wait! Aah! Ooh! Ow!
- I like crayons.
- Girls are gross.
I-I think I feel
like myself again.
Uh, you look a little weird.
Your skin's all pink
like a baby mouse.
- I-Is that normal?
- Probably.
Uh, sign here for
storage or disposal
of the 26 years we removed.
Wait, what?
I ain't payin' to
store 26 years.
Well, then you're
taking it with you.
I'm almost ready to sell out.
Alright, what's disposal cost?
- Oh!
- S-something unfair's happening.
There's no escape. No escape!
Let me help you!
This is not a good look.
Oh!
Oh, boy. Hey! They
-- they shot me!
You are seriously hurting
the Citadel experience.
- Listen to me!
- Drop the gun!
Death is coming for us all,
and the Citadel is a
weapon of mass des--
Woof. You're about to
get suspended with pay.
Come on, Morty, let's get outta
here before this gets political.
Oh! Was I... influential?
Yeah, y-you were influential.
Y-You had like
seven -- seven blogs.
Tight. Oh.
Ugh. Too late.
Rick C-137,
President Morty requests
you join him for dinner.
Whoa! S-Seriously?
You know I destroyed this place.
You've been
pardoned for that, sir.
Rick! Let's have dinner
with the Morty President.
Morty, the idea was to get
back to simple adventures.
The Citadel runs on canon.
Okay. I guess things really
are just going right back
to how they were.
Fine. I could eat.
But the second he reveals
he's evil, we're gone.
I dunno. It tastes...
pretty good.
Okay, let me know if
you start feeling poisony.
Good to have you back, buddy.
Mmm!
Sorry I'm late. Never
really ends around here.
Look at this, Morty.
They really did make
a you the president.
And I hate 'em every day for it.
But wow! Rick C-137.
Now, that's a guy to move
your schedule around for.
Not -- Not here to blow
the place up again, I hope.
Ha! Not unless you
try to keep me here.
Ha-ha, geez.
Wouldn't dream of it.
But it's amazing you dropped by
because I was eventually
gonna hunt you down.
There's the reveal. Let's dance.
- Ha! Geez.
- Rick, come on, man.
The guy got elected
president by Ricks and Mortys.
- He's being really nice.
- All politicians are nice.
He's a hot bag of
peanuts, isn't he?
We've been through a lot.
A-And he does not
like --Serialized drama.
Right, no drama.
Keep it episodic.
Ricks never look back.
Waste of a legend in his case.
You know he practically -built this place?
- Wait, what?
And now you're running
it squeaky clean, right?
That's why you got
deformed Mortys
coming up through
the sewer lines
talking about hope and change?
- Fair enough.
- Good clapback, Rick.
What's the deal
with that, Mister P?
I got a little project going on.
Required some hands-on labor.
It would require less
if you were willing
to tell me how one might
bring down the
Central Finite Curve.
Alright, time to go, Morty.
I want to know what
he's talking about.
Yeah, you've come all this way.
Can you give me 10 more seconds?
Literally 10? Because
now it would be 6.
Oh, I'm fine with that.
Make it 2.
One.
Like I said, would have been
a big help for you to tell me,
but I should have everything
I need from you now.
Let me just make sure.
You can't scan an entire
brain over appetizers.
Oh, most of yours got
scanned a long time ago.
You probably don't remember.
Check out season 1,
episode 9, Rick Heads.
Excelsior!
- Evil Rick.
- We kicked his ass!
"Evil Rick." I love it.
Smartest man in the universe,
with an ego so big you
can just grab it like a joystick.
Looks complete.
I was afraid I'd have
to kill every Rick
on the Citadel to
get what I needed.
You asshole! I vouched for you!
He only came here
because I asked him to.
I'm sorry, Rick.
That apology and a
screwdriver in my hand
would be worth a screwdriver.
You sellout Mortys kill me.
I'd hate you more than
the Ricks you worship
if there was any point.
But you can't help it.
You were bred for it.
Wanna see?
You already know
Rogue Ricks used Mortys
to hide themselves
from the Citadel.
But you might not
know it worked so well
that the Citadel became its own
Morty Market.
And I'm sure you don't
know how far they've gone
to help supply meet demand.
Sure, Ricks could scour infinity
for naturally
occurring grandsons.
But why bother?
So much work.
Such an admission of need.
There aren't infinite versions
of our grandfather, Morty.
He's an infinite smear
of one shitty old man.
And he's attached
to us infinitely
through his weakness
and our forgiveness.
Oh! Oh!
This is why we're with him.
This is why we're alive.
What the fuck?
Rick, say this isn't true.
-It isn't the whole truth. Liar!
- It's complicated!
- I'm not busy.
Okay, Morty, remember
when I said all I need
was your apology and a
screwdriver in my hand?
Well, I forgot I literally have
a screwdriver in my hand.
I mean, duh-doy. I'm
basically Inspector Gadget.
Uh-oh.
It's okay. He's free to go.
He's the Rickest Rick.
We'll never see him again.
Morty, when you came
here for that serum,
did you refill this gun?
Yeah.
Oh. Ooh! Holy shit!
I only know one man that
ever hacked my portal gun,
and it turned out
it was evil you.
Yay! He's all caught up.
Wait. Hold it. Hold it.
- Who -- Who's that?
- Time for Big Boy. Duck!
Ohhhhhh! Ohhhhhh! Ohhhhh!
Does he like it?
It's a metaphor for
capitalism, Morty.
What do you think?
Ohhhhhh! Ohhhhhh! Ohhhhhh!
Ohh! Ohhhhhh!
Ohhhhhh! Ohhhhhh! Ohhhhh!
Ohhhhhh!
Yoink!
You can't outrun
your past, Rick.
Did you think my force field
would be down the second time?
I was expressing
disapproval of your dialogue.
Disapprove all you want.
Tonight, the quality of
dialogue stops mattering.
Tonight, I do that
thing I want to do
with the curve thing.
Nobody leave. Everybody stay.
Aaaaaaah!
In uncertain times like these,
I think it's important for
me to say, eat shit, fuck you.
The drug companies paid
for me to say every word.
I have millions of dollars,
and I don't care if
you live -- oh, God!
Oh, fuck! No! Aah!
And I'd just like to say that
prescription drugs are great,
and you should buy them now.
What's happening, Rick?
He hacked the entire
city's portal supply.
Come on, there still might
be one way out of here --
out the bottom.
What do you think he
needed from your brain?
I assume schematics for the
Citadel's dimensional drive.
If he's gonna use
it to blow the curve,
we do not want to be here.
What is the Central
Finite Curve?
Q&A after our survival.
Hopefully we can snag some
untainted fluid at the source
and get the fuck out of here.
Or not.
Wow. I thought my capitalism
metaphor was on the nose.
Ow! Oh!
So did you help
build the Citadel?
Do you just lie to
me about everything?
Can't we just sneak
through the cave base?
We turned a new leaf, Morty.
We're back to simple adventures.
It's not a new leaf until
you tell me everything.
Morty, we really
don't have time for this.
The whole place -is gonna blow.
- No, I-I don't trust you.
I-I don't want to
do this anymore
if I'm not gonna get
straight answers from you.
God damn it!
Here's my fucking
downloaded brain, Morty.
You want to jump the shark?
You want to know my
stupid crybaby backstory?
Knock yourself
out. Not -- not now!
- Boo ya, Rick.
- Nice one, Morty!
Whoa. Dead wife?
Yes, now everyone
can shut up about it.
Wow, Rick, I feel a lot
better having seen all that.
Of course that's the case.
In their minds,
they're the underdogs.
And that's how
they justify this.
Morty, I'm not responsible
for every fucked-up
Rick out there.
They literally all say that.
They all have that excuse.
It's part of their system.
None of them have
to be responsible.
They're all victims
of themselves.
Oh, it's so hard to be a
genius. Couldn't you just die?
Well, what are
you doing about it?
Jack shit. I'm leaving.
Do you know what the
Central Finite Curve is?
They built a wall
around infinity.
They separated all
the infinite universes
from all the infinite universes
where he's the smartest
man in the universe.
Every version of us
has spent every version
of all of our lives
in one infinite crib
built around an
infinite fucking baby.
And I'm leaving it.
That's what makes me evil --
being sick of him.
If you've ever been sick of
him, you've been evil, too.
Rick, did you really
leave the crows for me?
Or did you come back
because they dumped you?
There you go, kid. Now
you're Evil Morty, too.
Sooner or later we all are,
on this side of the curve.
- Ah!
Don't worry, Morty.
We still got a way out
they never thought of
-- Operation Phoenix.
Doesn't that still
mean, like, death?
Sure, but the joke's on them,
'cause we just found a
backdoor to getting off this rock.
REROUTED. REROUTED.
Rerouted. Rerouted. Rerouted.
Oh, my fucking God!
Come on, Morty. We gotta go.
You can come if you want.
Don't blame me if you don't.
Ugh! From where I sit, Morty,
that's the best
deal on the table.
I-I don't have a real plan.
Thanks, pal. I-I'm glad
you ignored my advice.
It's just as well. I lied.
That second seat's a toilet.
Oh. Super dick move.
But weirdly kind
of cool to admit it.
Geez, you guys really
are bred for forgiveness.
Let's go.
Say goodbye to
the Citadel, fellas.
Improved by KID
Resynced by KID
Enjoy the movie(s) / show(s)
Ooowee! Evil Morty.
That was quite a scheme.
Makes me wonder if
there's an evil me out there.
But I guess sometimes
I look at my life,
and I may not even
need him, 'cause, well,
guess I've made a pretty
big mess of things myself.
Ooowee.
Never got my job at
the university back.
Remember that? Rick
made me do karate.
It -- It was kinda funny.
But I guess things
went downhill from there.
Started isolating
myself from Amy.
Used to tell her
everything I was feeling,
but then I guess I stopped,
'cause I wanted her to
love who she thought I was,
not who I felt myself becoming.
Ever think about how horrified
the people we love would be
if they found out
who we truly are?
So we just dig ourselves
deeper into our lies every day,
ultimately hurting the only
people brave enough to love us.
Wish I didn't do that.
Wish I was brave
enough to love them back.
I don't know. Maybe
you should try it.
We don't have as
much time as we think.
Ooowee.
Did you get any of that?