C'mon, Rick. We're
-- We're almost there.
Ugh, leave me,
Morty. It's the only way.
Wha-- Were -- Wha-- Were we --
Were we Blades in that one?
That's fucking tight.
Just stay with me.
I'm -- I'm scared, Morty.
I can see the end.
I'm a silly man.
I'm a silly small man.
I'm -- I'm sorry I
got you into this.
Then how about I
get us outta this?
Hello? Hey, Jessica.
I-It's Morty. From school.
Oh, hey, Morty. What's up?
Um, I just want to say
that you're really great.
I know the timing never
really worked out with us,
but you're really great and I
wish I got to know you better.
Oh, I mean -- That's a lot.
Oh, uh, yeah,
sorry, I guess I just --
No, I just wish
you said it sooner.
- Wh-What?
- Yeah, I mean, being nervous
is sort of selfish
sometimes, y'know?
- Life support systems failing.
- Yeah, that's a great point.
Well, what are
you doing tonight?
Tonight? Yeah.
Do you, like, want to watch
a movie or something?
Um, yeah. Tonight. Sounds great.
Holy shit. Holy shit.
Come on, come on!
Oh.
- Where are we?
- We're home, Rick.
I-I landed us in the ocean.
The ocean?! The ocean on Earth?!
- Uh, yeah, I-I guess so.
- Oh, shit.
Holy shit. We have to go.
We have to go right fucking now.
- What?
- You touched the ocean, Morty.
What's the big --
-Oh, fuck. Shit.
What? Shit.
Richard!
You have desecrated
the sacred treaty
betwixt land and sea.
Now face the wrath of
your once and eternal foe --
Mr. Nimbus!
Sorry. Who is that?
My nemesis.
- What?
- My fucking nemesis, okay?
Okay, but what
was his name again?
I am Mr. Nimbus!
He's gonna say that a lot.
W-Wait, so who is
coming over again?
- He said his nemesis?
- Rick has a nemesis?
- I guess.
- Has hementioned him before?
I-I was gonna ask
you. First I'm hearing it.
Who is he? Like a magic guy?
Rick's science and he's magic?
He's like a-a fish?
- A fish.
- He's not a fish. He's Mr. Nimbus.
He's king of the ocean
and he's a piece of shit.
Are you happy, Morty?
Are you happy you
touched the ocean?
He's gonna be here any minute.
Just help me smooth this over
or this guy's gonna become
more trouble than he's worth.
Um, hey, I don't know how
much I can help out tonight, Rick.
Jessica's coming
over j-just to, like,
watch a movie or something,
but y'know,
t-t-that's a good step.
That's a solid step
to something, y'know?
Truly nobody cares
about your dick, Morty.
The sooner you
learn that, the better.
I think you just
don't want me happy
'cause then I'll stop
doing your crazy chores.
Trust me, after
that ocean fuck-up,
you don't get to
do anything crazy.
While I bullshit my way
through this peace
summit treaty with Nimbus,
Summer is gonna dive
into the Marianas Trench
to recover the forbidden shell
that gives him his power
because Summer can be trusted.
Let's lick tits.
- Okay, what?
- I don't love that.
Of course you don't,
'cause you guys
aren't getting any.
Actually, your father and I
have been very
sex-positive lately.
- Eww.
- Dr. Wong suggested we experiment.
We've been watching
pornography. Together.
- Gross!
- I might never come back from the ocean.
Oh, you'll have to
tone it down, babe.
The squares can't handle it.
There are suicide
capsules in all of your teeth.
Do what you want with that.
C'mon, Morty.
You're on booze duty.
Okay, Nimbus only
drinks the good shit.
So just toss this whale-ass
ocean-wine in here
and age it up a few centuries.
So time moves faster in there?
I-I-Is it like a Narnia thing?
I'm not a beaver who
believes in Jesus Christ, Morty.
But yeah, it's pretty
much a Narnia thing.
Okay, but Jessica --All you
have to do is bring wine, Morty.
When do I ask you -for anything?
- When do you --
I haven't been to a full
week of school in years!
I don't know shit! And for what?
How many enemies
do you have to have?
Why is everything
a fight with you?
You might want to
learn this early, Morty.
- Life is a fight.
- With Mr. Nimbus?
Are you makin' fun of me?
Mr. Nimbus is an
ice-cold dick killer, Morty.
Okay, let's go. That's
his magic ocean horn.
Is that Mr. Nimbus?
Nimbus. Richard.
You look like ass.
Let's get this over with.
I'm sorry. This is the guy?
Jerry. Hold on. No.
I've seen you fuck a planet,
and this is the guy
you're afraid of?
I like this one, Rick.
He is unbroken. Untamed.
Perhaps he could use a
firmer grip upon his leash.
Okay, that's enough.
I'm calling the police.
- Go ahead.
- Jerry.
I will! Good.
I control them. Excuse me?
He controls police, Jerry.
Right, that tracks.
In Dumb World. Police?
A strange horny ocean
man is on my lawn.
Well, I don't see
how that's relevant,
but we're white.
- Freeze! Freeze!
Fight.
Fuck.
Flee. Let's get outta here.
- Shall we, Richard?
- Okay, but how did he --
Jesus Christ, Jerry. He's
Mr. Nimbus. He controls the police!
Um, hello? Am I
in the right place?
I just saw a bunch of cops
having sex with each other?
Hi! Jessica! Hi!
Yeah, yup, y-you're
in the right spot.
Uh, everyone,
th-this is Jessica.
This is everybody.
Uh, this is --
I am Mr. Nimbus.
Jesus, Nimbus, just get inside.
Morty, grab the wine.
Yeah, in a minute.
C-C'mon, Jessica.
Stand aside.
Unless you are worthy of Nimbus.
If that means what
I think it means,
I'll have you know, we
watch porn together.
Oh!
Ooh!
Wow, okay! Looks like
you guys just got the nod.
The nod?
Mr. Nimbus has a
sense for these things.
I take it you're a
sex-positive couple?
Oh, yeah. Very much so.
- We watch porn together.
- Great!
I'll mark you down as
eligible for a threeway.
Here's all the
information you'll need.
The king of the ocean wants
to have a threesome with us?
Totally optional.
But a remarkable option to
have, I assure you. Very jealous.
There's a form on the last page
so we know where
to send the gift basket.
So that just happened.
You don't sound upset about it.
Neither do you.
Oh, my God. Is this
happening? To us?
I thought this only happened
in New York or on HBO.
Dr. Wong hasn't been wrong yet.
You're right.
This is exactly what
she was talking about.
So, uh, yeah. J-Just
make yourself comfortable.
Y'know, ch-choose a
movie or -- or we can watch
some interdimensional
cable if you want.
We now return to "Nintendo 69."
Nintendo, oh, what
are you doing to me?
Oh, Nintendo, oh, Nin--
Or we can watch
whatever, y'know.
Wh-Whatever you're into.
Morty, did I hear
you're getting wine?
Yeah, I gotta get some
wine for Mr. Nimbus.
Got any extra?
Oh. Uh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, I'll go
get some, just for you.
Cool. Hurry back.
Looks like you could use a hand.
Oh, hey! Yeah,
th-th-that'd be great.
No problem. Hoovy?
Dinner's ready!
Be right there, sugar hoof!
Just helping this young
man through a portal
with that crate full of alcohol
that's been here for decades.
Hey, thanks, Hoovy.
I-I really appreciate that.
I-I got a girl over, and
I really, really like her.
- I-I'm just nervous.
- Oh, I know that feeling.
When I first started
seeing Bova,
I could only think about all the
ways I was gonna mess it up.
- So what'd you do?
- Oh, I messed it up.
But I found the one
who loves me for that.
Thanks. I-I really
needed to hear that.
Here, -t-take one of these.
- Oh, you don't have to.
No, I-I want to. You
have a good day, Hoovy.
You have a great time
with that lady up there.
Just relax. Will do!
Bova?
Why did you leave us, Father?
Japheth? When were you born?
I swore to Mother
if I ever met you,
I'd avenge her.
It wasn't my fault.
Whose, then? Whose?!
The boy from the magic door.
Shall we discuss terms?
Yeah, fine. Whatever. Terms.
Term number one -- I
am King of the Ocean.
The place I shit? Go ahead.
Term number two --
Stop shitting in the ocean.
No idea what
you're talking about.
Delicious. Another.
Oh, uh, well, I-I was
thinking of using this one for --
Morty, just give him
the bottle. God damn.
Another!
Morty, you get the wine?
Hey, Jessica. Um, yeah, sorry.
I just -- just going
back to get it.
Oh. I thought you already went.
I did! I just -- just
got a little busy.
Going right now, again!
You go ahead and
fire up that movie!
That's okay. I'll wait for you.
Holy shit, holy shit,
holy shit, holy shit!
I've been waiting for you.
Oh, wow. Hoovy, right?
Never say his name!
Jesus Christ!
Why -- Why is every
old guy super jacked?
Sorry! I'm sorry!
I-I just need the
wine! I'm sorry! Stop it!
Fucking kill you!
Ow! Okay, screw this!
You know what?
You! Yeah, fuck you, Hoovy!
Father?
It's him! - I told you he'd come back!
- Holy shit.
Okay, look, he wasn't
old like 10 seconds ago.
Ow! Mother fucker!
I'm sorry, Father. I'm
sorry we never believed.
He'll come back.
Stop him.
Papa, why do we guard the gate?
Because one day, the
dark child shall return.
And we will be ready.
Delicious.
Where is your wine
boy, Richard? I thirst.
He's getting it. Stop
eating beignets like that.
Participant voids all liability
in the event of death by orgasm?
Are we really ready to
open things this wide?
What if it gets weird?
What if I fall in love with him?
No, no, no, no, no. Damn it!
What was that?
Another scheme
of yours, Richard?
I know you're
planning something.
It's nothing. Will you
excuse me, please?
What the fuck is going
on? Where's the wine?
Dad was horny and I dropped it.
God, I can't -- I can't
believe you're fucking this up.
I'm not fucking it up! There
was a guy in the thing and --
There's always a guy in a thing!
Land dwellers do not keep
Nimbus waiting and live.
Be right out! Goddammit.
Do you see this whisper
kitchen "Frasier" bullshit
you're making me do?
Morty, just get the wine.
Beth and Jerry, stop
trying to fuck Nimbus.
Well, -we wouldn't do it here.
- I'll have you know he propositioned us.
He propositions everybody!
Hey, hey, hey, Jessica.
- W-What's up?
- Seems like you're busy.
No, no, no! I ran
into a little trouble.
But -- But -- But I'll go
get that wine right now.
But you said were going
to get it like twice already.
I-I-I was and I-I'm
getting it right now.
Holy shit, it's him!
God damn it! What do
you want me to say?!
I-I'm sorry!
We finally beat him.
But let's always remain vigilant
because you never know.
He might be back one day.
Okay, Narnia! Let's go.
Let's fucking go!
It is over. The boy
is not coming back.
He always comes back.
You have wasted our lives,
our very futures, on a fantasy!
A lie! I know what I saw.
You saw nothing!
You are a foolish boy!
Those called fools
are the only ones brave
enough to see the truth.
Tell me, Father.
Am I a fool now?
I was born in the pits
that made these stones.
I lost my years building
a temple to a lie.
So I made lies my power.
And what is power
but a lie we --
Aah!
Oh, shit, he's real!
He's real! I was wrong!
I was so wrong! God is real!
Wow. Impeccable service.
Big tip. I liked your
other one more.
What was his name? Kyle?
What? Nothing.
Can we just sign
this thing and go?
Jessica, -I-I'm so sorry.
- I mean, it's fine.
You were only gone
like a couple minutes.
Morty, are you okay?
I'm -- I'm sorry, Jessica.
We just never seem
to get it right, do we?
No, I guess we don't.
But I'm glad you called me.
Maybe we can start
over, get it right this time.
Yeah. I'd -- I'd like that.
Thanks for bringing the wine.
Totally worth it.
Do we need an opener?
Oh. I'll -- I'll
-- I'll go get it.
Mmm.
I do so love to sign
upon the dotted line.
Shall we? Jesus Christ, yes.
And who is your witness?
My witness is the squid.
Really proud of this
SeaWorld theme, aren't you?
Hey, just get a witness, man.
Don't make this about me.
Or perhaps Richard has no one
with whom he can trust his life.
Who truly knows him.
Save me. Fine!
I'll get someone. Oh, my God.
Morty! C'mere. I need
you for some bullshit.
Look, Rick, I've done
everything you've asked.
Now can I just have some
time with my girlfriend?
Your girlfriend?
I mean, she's not -- we kissed,
but I'm just trying
to take it slow.
You gotta give these things
time to breathe, y'know?
Do you know why
you're special, Adam?
Because I am -The Traveler?
- Yes.
You will be the one to
pass through the door.
You will be the
one to end our pain.
But, Mother, what about my pain?
Your pain shall set us free.
It is time to begin.
Again.
Again!
- You are not ready.
- Please, Mother --
Do you think he will
show you mercy?
Like he did to us?
Again!
Does anyone need anything?
Does Nimbus need anything?
Holy shit! Don't judge.
We're growing -as a couple!
- Aah!
Why is this happening to me?!
For the future!
You dare assassinate Nimbus?
Sorry. Wait. Who -- Who is that?
Get in line, pal!
Such a waste.
M-Mother?
Aah!
Jessica!
You just had to touch the ocean.
Aaah! Shut up!
There isn't time to --
It's all fucked!
And you fucked it!
Huh?
You're early.
W-What is this place?
The end. But also a beginning.
Isn't every end a
beginning? Stay back!
I don't want your stripped
down Sundance sci-fi bullshit.
Where's Jessica? Jessica.
That was her name,
wasn't it? Thank you, Morty.
I had forgotten. Oh, right.
You'll be needing this.
For the wine.
Oh, shit, we got him!
Can you believe he bought
that fucking tree bullshit?
We fucking got him!
Very well.
If you seek war with
Atlantis, you shall have it.
Oh, I've already been
to war with Atlantis
when I D-Day'd
that Mermaid Puss!
I knew that was you!
Prepare my exit parade!
Say goodbye to your
precious dry land!
For soon it will be wet! Wet!
Yeah, global warming is
already doing that, asshole.
But sure, yeah, go for it.
Make us slightly more wet!
Am I a joke to you?
Yes, you are a fucking joke!
You fucking suck!
You've always sucked!
Y-Y-Y know why we
haven't fought in years?
'Cause you're an
embarrassment to me
and I don't need you anymore.
I don't need anybody.
All I do is eat ass
and 69 Nintendos, bro.
- Every day.
- Or maybe you hate me
because I am the only man
to see how far you have fallen.
I used to fear you. Respect you.
Now all that's left is pity --
for a sad, drunk shell of a man
too afraid to see
how alone he truly is.
If Diane were alive today,
what would she think --
Don't fucking establish canonical
backstory with me, you Red Lob--
Oh, good. You're awake.
I just took some wine!
I said I was sorry.
What the fuck is
wrong with you people?!
I have been asking
that for centuries.
I was created to study
you, Morty, to know you.
But the closer I looked,
the more I do not
recognize myself.
Uh, yeah, man, I really
don't have time for --
I have often wondered who
would we be without you, Morty?
Are we anything
beyond our hatred?
And when she came,
I thought she would
be the answer.
Frozen in time. Forever asleep.
We could not
understand her purpose,
so we hid her away.
Why do we always
hide the truths we fear?
I don't give a shit, nerd!
Let her go! Why -- Why
did I clone myself genitals?
Ow! I don't care, bitch! Do it!
Ooh! Asshole! Yeah,
guess I am an asshole!
Y'know, sometimes
you gotta be an asshole!
My grandpa taught me that!
Okay, okay, okay, fine!
Morty? Hey, Jessica.
Wow. Must've been some nap, huh?
I-Is that ooze or -- I'm
not sure what to call it.
It l-l-looks like ooze.
Okay. W-We can catch up later.
What the --
Rick! Rick!
-...obster motherfucker. Rick!
Screw this. What
am I even doing?
- Help!
- Where are you?
Come back here. I'm
going to make the land wet!
Y'know what, I'd love to see it.
Do it! God, do anything!
Just don't use me as
an excuse anymore!
Rick! Wow.
That was intense.
You look stressed.
We signed -the paperwork.
- I must go.
Well, your people
have our number!
Your starfish mentioned
some kind of basket?
- Jesus, Morty.
- Stop! No, no! Not today!
Can't you go one day
without --You don't get to --
What the --I fucked it up, okay?
It's okay, Morty.
That's what you do.
Now lemme Deus Ex Machina
this shit and let's go home.
God, why does everyone
go Cyber-Punk Bird?
So fuckin' hack.
Oh, shit.
Well, that's cool.
Okay, we might
be a little fucked.
Did you think I would let
you die alone, Richard?
I am Mr. Nimbus!
Wow. Phew.
You -- You still got
time for that movie?
Yes. Time.
I had nothing but time.
Endless time.
At first, it was madness.
Then enlightenment.
Then madness again.
But perhaps it was a gift.
I could see the life of time.
And as I watched
the life of time
in all its fleeting,
terrible light,
I wondered, had I lived?
Was I just the object
in another's story?
Was that all I ever
was? Could I be more?
I had nothing but time
and still no answer.
Time without
purpose is a prison.
I have glimpsed into
the mind of eternity.
Perhaps the mind of God.
And found nothing but silence.
I think we should
just be friends.
Oh, yeah.
I-I-I get that.
Guess we missed our moment.
Yes. But there will be more.
For both of us.
Goodbye, Morty.
Hey, how's it going?
Fuck off! I'm a Time-god!
Fighting by your
side again, Richard.
It was, uh --Yeah.
Then there is no treaty.
Because there is no war.
Aw, Nimbus.
That's -- That's really
chill of you, man.
Richard.
Before you were
my greatest enemy,
you were my only friend.
Grandpa, -I got the shell!
- Shit.
- Okay, Nimbus, look.
- You son of a bitch!
- Betrayal!
- My weapons, Morty!
I-I-I used them all! Grandpa!
Wait, Grandpa, what do I do?
I have the shell.
Should I blow it?
Is that -- I'm -- I'm
just gonna blow it!
Don't blow it! Destroy the horn!
What the hell, Summer?!
You were supposed
to destroy the horn!
How was I supposed to know that?
Police!
Take this piece of shit to jail.
I told, ugh, I told you.
He's an ice-cold dick killer!
Nimbus!
Wait. So how can he --
Jesus, Summer. He's Mr. Nimbus.
He controls the police!
Improved by KID
Resynced by KID
Enjoy the movie(s) / show(s)
Jer, I think more
than one safe word
sort of defeats the point.
I know, I just wanna make sure
we have every
opportunity to stop.
Super excited about it though.
Me too, so excited.
Jerry, are we doing this
because we both want this?
Or because it's what we
think the other one wants?
I just wanted to prove
that I love you so much
I would do this -for you!
- Same!
Let's take that
prize and get out
before we make a huge mistake.
Getting cold feet?
No.
- Please don't tell Rick.
- He wouldn't understand.
Yes, he would.