Ahh, I love that
new T-shirt smell.
Chicks are gonna
be up all up in our biz
when they see us wearing
these Rick and Morty custom tees.
I bet we could sell these.
Hells yeah. I
fuckin' love merch!
Aah!
- The rain! It -- It burns!
- Oh, shit.
Quick, Morty,
protect the shirts!
The door! Open the door!
Rick! Is it --
Morty, will ya stop tryna--
Okay, there, it's open.
- Jesus.
- My skin is on fire.
W-Why is the rain doing that?
My acid rain will destroy
all things green and natural or
my name isn't Diesel Weasel.
Huh. Well, that
guy's easy to please.
Your acid rain
is an acid pain...
in the butt, Diesel Weasel!
Yikes. Wow.
Who's the chick in
need of a dialogue pass?
First order of business is
to clean up this acid rain
with a little wind!
Yoww!
Ow! Ow, my leg!
Wow.
And now an elemental
punch that's too hot to handle!
Wa-kah!
Oh, wow.
Curse you, Planetina!
I'll get you next slime!
There's only one solution
for Earth's pollution -- you!
- Wow.
- Morty, if you say "wow"
one more time, I
swear to fucking God...
Are you crazy, Rick?
She's right there!
Yeah, get that aluminum,
Morty. It's 8% of the Earth.
We'll need every atom.
Thanks! Every litter-bit helps!
Your problem!
Excuse me? S-Sorry.
I-I-I wanted to say, "N-No
problem, you're welcome,"
a-a-and it came
out "your problem."
I-I'm an idiot. Sorry.
You're not an
idiot. You recycled.
- I-I'm Morty.
- Nice to meet you, Morty.
I'm Planetina, and I hope
you have a wonderful day.
Hey!
The fuck we doin' here?
Uhh, y-y-you like soft serve?
There's a shop around the bend.
Oh, I don't eat ice cream.
Veal is a product
of the dairy industry.
Oh, that's not good.
No, it is not.
Oh, my God! Come on! Let's go!
I know a place that serves
cruelty-free doughnuts.
If you'd like, I could fly
you and your friend there
easy-peasy, lemon-squeezy.
Okay, I-I-I'll ask him.
He -- He said he
can't come. Let's go!
What the fuck was that shit?
The Earth is in danger!
Pollution and waste
are ruining our planet.
Mother Nature has enlisted
the help of four young adults
from each major ethnicity
-- and when things look bad,
and I mean really bad --
they combine the powers
of their elemental
rings to create me!
Planetina, conservationist
super person!
There's only one solution...
for Earth's pollution -- you!
P-Pretty cool, huh?
I-I can't believe I actually
hung out with Planetina.
How old is this woman?
She looks very mature.
She's a sentient amalgam
of natural elements,
so I don't believe
age applies to her.
Great. Taylor Murphy
dumps me the day before his
hella-big pool party
and my little brother's
dating a phase four super hero.
Just shoot me in the
fucking head until I die.
Hey, hey, none of
that, Summerfest.
Look what you're doing to
your sister, you piece of shit.
Is it weird that she
hasn't texted me yet?
- Yes.
- No.
What if I told you that
your Grandpa Rick's
got something up his
sleeve that's so Rick-diculous
that it's gonna make
you forget all about
that stupid asshole
that dumped you?
Hey, my egg plate!
Morglutz, Slartivart,
and Ferkus 9 --
three planets are all ending
in a delayed succession
of cataclysmic events.
A jam like this comes
around only once in a lifetime.
Morglutz's sun is
going supernova,
Slartivart is falling
into a black hole,
and Ferkus 9 is getting
"Deep Impact" -ed
by an asteroid.
They're all having a
major, final blow out --
and I'm gonna drug it up
and suck it up before each one
goes ka-blamo, and I'm taking
my favorite grandkid
along with me!
Hells yeah.10
seconds on Morglutz,
and you'll be up to your
neck in I-could-give-two-
shits-about-what's-his-ass.
And also herpes.
Um... Oh, my God,
thank you, Grandpa Rick!
I'm gonna go pack my rollie.
Um, Summer? I-I-I haven't
given you my approval yet.
Summer, approval
is yet to be given here!
There's a huge forest fire
like 200 miles from here!
This is amazing!
Planetina's bound to be there.
Mom, I-I need the credit
card to buy a train ticket.
Absolutely not.
Mom, this is the biggest
wildfire of the year!
- You're not going!
Da fuck I'm not.
Last time I checked,
this wasn't Russia.
- It's not Russia, Jerry.
- My heart is broken,
and I deserve to let loose,
and if you don't like it,
you can suck my bigger tit.
Adios, C-words.
Morty, I don't want
you getting hurt.
- Please, think this over.
- I don't want to think!
I want to see a girl I like.
If you don't want to help me,
I'll find my own goddamn
way to the wildfire.
- I'll get the wine.
- Thank you.
The Governor has implemented
a mandatory evacuation.
Abandon all hope, people!
Nothing will stop this fire.
Nothing!
Scratch that! Here's
Planetina, Savioress of Earth!
Yeeouch! Talk about a hot foot.
Better put this wildfire on ice!
Come here, little buddy.
Come on, come on,
come on, I gotcha.
Morty?! What are you doing here?
Oh, hey! Y-You're here, too?
Yeah, I heard about
the wildfire back home,
and, you know, I
stopped by to lend a hand.
H-Here you go,
fella. All safe now.
Ahh, rabbits --
al-always hopping --
Never stoppin'.
Y-Yeah.
S-So it was, uh,
great hanging --
hanging out the other day.
I-I was getting kind of
a -- I mean I-I got kind of
a p-positive vibe.
Oh, good. I was putting one out.
I-I really like you.
Holy shit.
I-I-I mean, uh,
well, oh, all right.
Next step, you
w-want to go out again?
I do! But, uh,
Morty, I have kids.
Oh, I-I-I'll get along
with them. I'm-I'm a kid.
No, I mean the four kids
that bring me into existence
by combining the power
of their elemental rings
so I can save Earth
from ecological disasters.
Oh, them! No, I-I
know about them.
I-I like them.
Oh, good. Well,
here they are now.
Hey, buddy, you
want an autograph?
That's 20 bucks a pop.
No, Eddie, he's my friend.
Morty, these are my
kids, The Tina-Teers.
Oh, hey.
Tina, girl, have
you gained weight?
Uh, well, I had a plant-based
doughnut yesterday.
Just a half.
Sugar is worst thing
for figure, darling.
You want to be ugly?
Heh, I-I thought
they'd be younger.
They've been manifesting
me since the mid-'90s.
A lot has changed since then.
This is freaking you out, huh?
It is a lot to take in.
I understand.
Well, I guess I'd better go.
See you around.
Hi-de-ho, TV 58!
Planetina, you
single-handily saved
a National Forest with ease.
I do what I can, but
I can't do it alone!
And who's your
friend over there?
Oh! This is Morty Smith.
He traveled 200 miles just
to save a rabbit from the fire.
He's a very special guy.
So, are you two dating?
Oh, um, w-- I-I-I --
Yes, we are.
Fuck love. Fuck love.
All right, time
to set the rules.
Lay it on me. No whining.
Done. No crying.
As if.
And absolutely, positively
no getting attached.
We're here to smash max
ass -- quantity over quality.
Deal? Deal!
I'm gonna eat so much
ass, you're gonna shit.
Check this out. This is
gonna be me at the party --
b-b-laaaah!
B-b-blaaaah! Oh,
is that another ass?
Don't mind if I-- b-b-blaaaah!
Ho-ho! This'll be me across
the room -- "Excuse me, miss.
It appears that you
have an uneaten ass.
Allow me -- lalalalalaaah!
- Lalalalalaaah!
- B-b-blaaaah!
B-b-blaaaah!
Whoo! Fucking super nova party!
Love is a lie! Hack the planet!
The world's ending,
and for some reason,
I want to die with you
more than anyone else.
Wow!
Yo, Rick, don't look now,
but someone's
giving you the big eye.
'Scuse me. I got
to see a man about
a horse I'd rather
have sex with.
Aah!
Hello. I'm Rick.
Hey. So, the world's
ending, and for some reason,
I want to die with you
more than anyone else.
Hello.
Have fun, Grandpa Rick!
No commitments!
♪ I flew to you on an airplane
♪ I was afraid that
you gave me strength ♪
♪ Forever, birds
were soul twin loves ♪
♪ Baby, come back to me
♪ Baby, come back like it was
Surprise!
What are you doing here?
Mmm!
I told my kids I went
out to recycle batteries.
All kidding aside,
everyone should discard
used batteries at
proper disposal centers
instead of tossing them
into a regular waste bin.
Thanks for the tip.
♪ Flowers never last forever
♪ But we can make
it past forever ♪
♪ Baby, come home to me
♪ Baby, you're home with me
Solus is collapsing
in five zip-zops.
If we time it right,
we can skeet together
as the sun explodes.
Sounds ah-mazing.
Say, I think I left my
purse back at the bar.
Can both of you
go get it for me?
Anything for you, Mrs. Obama.
Time to ghost, Grandpa Rick.
- Righty-right.
- Meet me at the car.
One of these has to be
hers. Where'd she go?
I guess we'll have
to start without her.
Oh, her loss.
B-b-blaaaaaaaaah!
Whoo! Planet
number two, let's do it!
Sorry, I took so long. I
had to ditch some clingers.
Let's do it. Up the butt, y'all.
Geez, you okay to drive?
Shiii!
'Course, I-I-I'm mable.
Buckle up.
Yeah!
Whoo! The best week of my life!
Hello.
What was that? Nothin'.
Who wants to see
the most radadelic
lady-version of a super hero?
- Fire!
- Water!
- Air!
- And Dirt!
Oh, no, the convention.
Morty, wake up!
- We overslept.
- What's happening?
Hey, there's a
little boy on her!
Oh, d-d-drop the curtain!
There is no curtain!
Idiots, zap her away!
No, no, no. Wait, I-I --
- Whoa!
- Security!
What did you do?
B-Bring her back!
- No! Let me go!
- Sorry, folks.
Planetina will be
back in a moment.
Until then, who wants a limited
edition Funko for only $50?
This is very bad.
We are about to close deal.
We cannot afford controversy.
Don't you worry.
I know how ta deal
with this Morty kid.
Hey, a bunch of us are
going over to Hibler's place
to shoot ourselves.
Y-You want to come with?
Sorry, but no man's tying
down Sum-Sum tonight.
Hit the dicks.
Your loss, honey.
You could have
had allllllll this.
Hey, check it out! There's
old people dancing!
Damn, girl. Your moves is tight.
-Hello. Rick!
What the WTF is that
Morglutzian doing here?
Morglutzian? She's --
She's not Morglutzian.
She's the only blue person
here without three eyes!
Okay, fine. B-Busted.
Thi-Thi-This is, uh, Daphne.
Daphne, this is Summer,
my granddaughter.
Granddaughter? Hello.
Daphne heard about
our little party crawl,
and I told her she
could come with.
I-I-In the trunk.
What in the actual fuck, Rick?
We said no commitments!
This was to be our
Apocalypse Party-crawl!
You broke the rules!
Squares follow rules, Summer.
Daphne's down to freak.
She's up for any sick,
nasty thing I want to do.
Hello. Oh, yeah, baby.
All right, fellas, take five.
He ain't gonna
give me any trouble.
Where's Planetina?
- Don't you worry about her.
- I want to see her!
Planetina's got a
lot of responsibilities.
People depend on her.
And you, my friend,
are a distraction we
can't afford right now.
She's just a product
to you, isn't she?
Something to make money off of.
W-Well, Planetina's
more than that.
She's a brilliant, living
thing, and I love her.
Oh, you love her?
Well, guess what.
We own her.
But not for long, of course.
We're gonna sell her
to some Arab overseas.
Fire.
As for you, maybe she won't
love you so much if you
ain't so pretty no more.
Stop! Yah!
Ow!
Y-You want to fuck
with me? Do you?
Stupid fuckin' shit hole!
Aaaaaah!
Boss, what's
happening? Let us in!
Aah!
Fire!
Can we conclude our business?
I'm eager to celebrate
my purchase of
Planetina over dinner,
and these infant seals
aren't getting any younger.
Momentarily, comrade.
Soon, our partner will return.
Ugh! What is taking
Eddie so long?
His phone keep
going to voicemail.
♪ Start leaving a message
♪ I can't make it to the phone ♪
Just kidding. It's
Eddie. Go fuck yourself.
Which one of you
ordered a pizza?
No one order
pizza. What is this?
Well, I got a cheesy Italian,
extra crispy just for you.
I know those cheek
bones like they're me own!
It's Eddie!
Fucking Mother! Kill him!
- Stone! Stone!
- Fire!
Aah!
Airs!
Cold Water! Cold Water!
Dirt!
Fire!
Wa--
Airs.
Now we can be
together, Planetina.
I am an individual character.
I represent no group.
- Fire!
- Aaah!
Water! Dirt! Airs!
Aah!
Not good!
Blib...
Naga...
Threve...
Verillex... Gam!
Happy Apocalypse!
- Oh, my gaaah!
- This is awful!
Why were we cheering?!
Hello. Got any agua around here?
Mama's got to hydrate.
Glove box.
Oh, yeah.
Rick is the coolest guy ever.
We're total soul mates.
He's gonna show me the
wonders of the universe.
Ha! Once we get
to the next planet,
Grandpa Rick is gonna
ditch you, like, so fast.
Oh, is that so?
Uh-huh, nobody is tying
that guy down -- ever.
The only chick seeing the
universe with Rick is me.
Not if I keep Rick's
mouth full of these.
Oh, my -- Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah. That's
right, girlfriend.
This is what you're up against.
Wars were fought over these.
They've ruined kings,
inspired presidents.
A hundred songs and
nine national anthems
have been written about them.
Best set of
elbow-titties on Morglutz.
And now, thanks to Rick,
the best in the galaxy.
You want me to put them away?
Please. Sure.
But only because you're
Rick's granddaughter.
Daph? Daphne?
Where are ya, baby?
Papa needs some
more elbow grease.
Comin'! Ya might want to
keep your eyes on the road.
It's about to get sloppy.
Hello! Hello.
Ugh!
Then I put my sunglasses
on and walked out
like nothing happened.
I'm finally free.
All because of Morty.
What a romantic story
about our son killing
a room full of people.
Your turn.
Uh, seven.
One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven!
Oyyy, don't punch my lunch!
A-ha! Eat it!
I'm out of food cards.
How 'bout I loan you
two quiche at 10%?
That's so generous.
My turn!
Double sixes, baby!
One, two, three... So,
what's next for Planetina?
Well, now that I'm not
distracted by book signings
and publicity stunts, Morty
and I can concentrate on
more important things.
Like school.
Like moving in.
Planetina doesn't have
a place to stay now,
so I said she
could live with us.
- Holy shit. Morty, no.
- I'm so full!
- What do you mean, no?
- Whoo!
Don't punch my lunch.
I wouldn't be a
burden, Mrs. Smith.
I only want to
spend as much time
as possible with your son.
My son is 14, miss.
I'm sorry, Morty.
You're way too young.
But y-y-y-you were a teenager
when Dad got you pregnant.
I was 17!
That's at least 26 in boy years.
I'm sure Planetina is very
nice, but when you're a teenager,
love is fleeting, at best.
You underestimate Morty.
He is a very mature young man.
See, Mom? I told you!
This is not happening.
End of discussion.
Planetina, I think you
should leave, please.
Okay, Mrs. Smith.
Oh, no!
Mom, I hate you!
- You suck!
- Hey, now, it's only a game.
- Shut up!
- Okay.
- My whole life,
I've never fit in anywhere.
Everything I have to
say is always met with
an eye roll as if
the act of hearing
what I have to say is
some exhausting chore.
Nobody in this family thinks I
can say or do anything right!
I've been all over the universe,
met hundreds of people,
and Planetina's the only one
I've ever met that makes me feel
like I belong, and you just
kicked her out of our house!
Morty, please --
I will never
forgive you for this!
♪ Get the sword
and throw it far ♪
♪ Let it shine under
the morning star ♪
Morty! Morty, come back!
♪ Who are you?
♪ Who am I to you?
♪ I am the antichrist to you
♪ Fallen from the
sky with grace ♪
♪ Into your arms race
Get out! All of you,
get out of there!
You're killing the planet!
Your people
didn't get the votes.
Leave, or I'll
have you arrested.
It's you people who
should be arrested.
Gutting the land, poisoning
the air your children breathe?!
Can't you see
what you're doing?!
Easy for you to say! You
can live how you want!
We need the jobs.
Let's go, boys.
She can't stop us.
W-We'll get them next time.
There's no time left!
Can't you hear the
Earth screaming?
You filthy murderers!
Planetina, stop it!
There's only one solution
for Earth's pollution!
Oh, my God, no.
♪ Who am I to you?
♪ I am the antichrist to you
No!
I can't believe I'm
banging my co-workers.
And I'm the boss!
This gay sex with
my Dad is terrific!
What was I thinking?
It'll all be over soon!
Last chance to pee
on me! Anyone?!
Okay, Grandpa, the
meteor's almost here.
- We can go now.
- Ah, nah, we still got time.
Well, then stop being in
love and start having fun.
Ah, love's pretty fun,
Summer. Just give it a chance.
It's not even real love!
Daphne's just with you
so she can keep surviving!
Ah, the young -- so naive.
Eww, gross.
Congratulations, Ferkisians!
Your apocalypse is aborted.
And, Grandpa, you
and I can go home.
Daphne, you may come with.
If you want to
and don't have to.
I don't know what you're
getting at, Summer.
Obviously, Daphne wants to --
Aw, you cold bitch. Hello?
Goodbye.
Hey, she's the one
that saved the world!
Now we got to go
to work tomorrow!
You fucker!
Sorry I messed
things up with Daphne.
Just shut up. I get it.
- Really? You're not mad?
- I'm furious.
But I have to admit, it
was pretty Rick of you
to avert an apocalypse
in a tantrum of cynicism
just to destroy one
dumb relationship.
Still, sorry.
Eh, I would've done
the same for you.
Promise?
Love you, Grandpa Rick.
Don't make it weird.
Please go. I-I-I can't
see you anymore.
Don't you even want
to try to make it work?
We were so close.
You murdered 300 people.
And you murdered my kids.
They were gonna
sell you away forever.
Eddie was trying to kill me!
Th-Those miners were innocent.
Those innocent miners
voted men into power to protect
their precious jobs
so they can buy more
plastic garbage and eat the
corpses of tortured animals.
The system is broken, Morty.
This is the only
way I can save Earth,
the only way I can save you.
If that's the only way,
I-I don't want to be saved.
Please, go.
But... I love you.
I-I-I can't -- I-I
can't love you.
I-I just can't.
Please understand.
No.
I'll go, but don't you dare
ask me to understand.
Planetina, I-I'm so sorry.
Fuck you.
Morty? Are you all right?
She's gone, Mom! She's gone!
I loved her so much!
I know you did, honey.
Shh, Mommy's here.
♪ Let it shine under
the morning star ♪
Improved by KID
Resynced by KID
Enjoy the movie(s) / show(s)
♪ Who am I to you? ♪
♪ I am the antichrist to you ♪
♪ Fallen from the
sky with grace ♪
♪ Into your arms ♪
Good morning.
'Morning.
Slow day, huh?
Yep.
Probably because
everybody thought
the world wouldn't be,
you know, like, here today.
Mm-hmm. Mom in back?
Mom's not talking to us.
Because we had sex?
Yes. Uh, yeah.
That makes sense.
Happy birthday, by the way.