You two are hungry.
- It's a big day.
- We're gonna kill God.
- Come again?
- Christian god is real.
He's been asleep for
thousands of years,
We're gonna sneak
up there and kill 'em.
Mob style. Just whack his ass.
- Can I kill God?
- Fuck off, Summer.
- As if.
- Beth, do you hear this?
Sweetie, don't get all worked up
before your job interview.
- Job interview?
- Yes.
Is that so hard to believe?
Actually, yeah.
Something's off.
No!
Shit!
Hunt me!
Hunt me! Hunt me!
Somebody hunt me!
Don't hunt him -to completion!
- Hunt me!
Oh, shit. Um...
Everyone start packing.
N-No time to explain.
Rick? Dad, what's wrong?
Someone just
killed a decoy family.
I'm Mr. Always
Wants To Be Hunted!
Yes, and how interesting
did you think that would stay?!
You made clones of us?
Decoys, Morty. Very different.
- Very different, sweetie.
- Different h-h-- Ow!
Yeah, Dad. Different h-how?
Lotta people out there
want a piece of this, sweetie.
I'm cool, and it
makes them feel bad.
So, y'know, after that
trouble with Space Beth,
I made passable
copies of the family
and placed them
around the country
as a buffer zone to protect --
But why does he always
-want to be hunted?
Jerry...
That's not important -right now, Dad.
- Sure, guys.
Rick can make secret
decoys of the family
and place them all
around the country,
but fuck me if I have questions
about the Starfish
Man in a target suit.
So thankful this is my Saturday.
Why was he in that cryo-pod?!
The cryopod is
what confuses you?
Jerry, can't you see we've
moved on to higher stakes?
Well, I don't see
any stakes at all.
Ah, shit!
Guess we'll just
be saying ciao bella
to our deposit, then
--Shut up and pack, Jerry.
Squids just killed a decoy
family. Decoy family?
Is this is why you
wanted to get out of town?
You think I'd lie to you
about why we're
on vacation, Morty?
I wouldn't lie to you.
Well, that's a lie. Huh...
So, someone out
there is trying to kill us?
Someone's always
trying to kill us --
That's what the decoys are for.
They go on fun, self-contained
terrestrial adventures and...
take bullets meant for us.
Shit.
No!
Oh, shit.
Decoy family.
I think Dad was still outside.
Wh-Wh-What's a decoy family?
Hard concept,
Morty. Hard concept.
I've never really cracked
it, if I'm being honest.
Decided it was maybe better
as a kind of kinetic mislead
- for another special episode!
- Oh, cool.
We now return to "When Wolf."
Whoa. A time-traveling wolf?
Count me in.
Yeah, I never thought
of the where in werewolf
like who, what, when and where.
C-Clever wordplay!
When Wolf. Dracula.
You know why I'm here.
I'm safe here, Ian.
Christianity hasn't
been invented yet --
Crosses are just
baby T's to me now.
I got out.
Please, don't invite me back in.
Huh, kinda mucked it
up with -this Dracula stuff.
- You're right.
It shows a lack of faith
in their core concept,
I'd much rather watch
When Wolf go to the '20s
and invest in the
stock market --
but then eat people. Yeah.
Look, if you really want to know
what happened to
Beth's mom, it -- Whup.
Squid aliens just
killed a decoy family.
Decoy family? You
made more clones?
Clones are like 32%
of all sci-fi, sweetie.
You don't get to own 'clones.
Yes, I made some decoys.
They're exactly like us,
with a few tweaks and
a backdoor shutdown.
Do you just get hard
creating sentient life?
Actually, I get hard
protecting my family. Ew.
Gross.
Yeah, now everyone
gets killer doppelgangers.
- Cool deal.
- The decoys are harmless, Beth.
Grandpa Rick, do the
decoys know they're decoys?
They wouldn't be very good
decoys if they did, Sum Sum.
So they think they're
us? That's the deal.
How do you know
we're not decoys?
Oh, my God. We're decoys.
Oh, God. We might not be real.
W-We might be
decoys! M-Morty, quick!
- Wh-Wh-What do I do?
- My failsafe, Morty.
M-M-My final, secret failsafe.
I-It proves I'm real.
You have to help me.
I-I-I'd never joke about this.
There's a barcode, Morty.
A-A barcode on the
interior of my left ass cheek.
What? Morty, please,
I'm begging you.
I'm not looking at your ass.
Please, Morty! Is it there?
God damn it! Just
tell me if I'm real!
Morty, do it!
Gross!
Dad! Summer, you fucking idiot.
- We're not decoys.
- Wh-Why did I get punished?!
A, decoys don't build
decoys, and, B, you think
the mere suggestion
I'm fake would break me?
- Christ, I'm not your mom.
- Fuck off.
Jeez, these guys
really wanna kill me bad.
Alright. Here's the plan.
We're gonna hide
out with a decoy family,
and when these squids
show up, we jump their asses.
Jerry! Come on!
Family emergency.
A bigger emergency than
my lemon squares not setting?
They're gluten free, sugar free,
and lemon free.
Think you got the
wrong house, bro.
Analysis Mode.
Password 8-0-0-8-5.
Kind of expected
a funnier password.
I didn't plan on
showing them off.
Damn. Like "Westworld."Yes,
Morty, like "Westworld."
But don't fuck them.
- S-Summer! - Whatever, creep.
I'm gonna see how
accurate you got my room.
Rick, when you say you made
an exact replica of the house,
d-did you mean like,
y'know, a-a-an exact replica?
I know about the
Yosemite t-shirt, Morty.
- Shit.
- You know you can use tissues, right?
I can't finish without it.
So you do know what a
happy family looks like.
I know what a
fake one looks like.
Uh, Rick? What?
Did you use this house
to make decoys, too?
What? Morty, why the
fuck would I do that?
You think I'd go
somewhere else to --
Okay. Well, I am now less
worried about the squids.
Isolate head at
normal processing.
What the fuck you think
you're doing down there?
- You're making decoys?
- Wait, how do you --
Oh, God. Summer was right.
Everyone in the car.
You said decoys
didn't make decoys.
And, usually, they don't.
But again, it's
nothing to worry about,
because decoys are harmless.
Just have to,
y'know, visit the rest
- and terminate the program.
- Terminate? They're alive, Dad.
And at some
point, they won't be,
That's how existing works.
W-W-What, are you
gonna save every stray cat?
No, but I can resist making
more of them in a lab.
Gah, look! Save the empathy.
It's more termite infestation
than "Blade Runner" --
I still think we're decoys.
You just want an
excuse to stop trying.
Yeah. And?
Oooh. There's a handsome fellow.
Uh-oh.
I thought you made
them harmless.
I don't remember
making this one.
Oh, hi, Rick. Family, me?
Hey, when did you all leave?
Analysis Mode. 8-0-0-8-5.
Hmm? N-Nothing, buddy.
You-you gotta stop
with all that coffee.
It's making you loopy.
H-Happy Analysis Mode.
Happy Analysis Mode to you, too!
Think you got the
wrong house, bro.
Analysis Mode. Password 8-0-0 --
Shit! You think I'm a decoy?
How do you know
about the decoys!
They were my idea!
Well, now I know
you're pranking me.
Analysis Mode.
Password 8-equal-sign
equal-sign-capital "D."
Hide.
What?! Hide!
Wow. Like -- Like "Ex Machina."
Yes, Morty, like "Ex Machina."
But don't fuck them.
- Summer! Whatever, weirdo.
I'm gonna see how
wrong you got my room.
So you do know what a
loving family looks like.
A simulated one, yes.
- Why are we hiding?
- He thinks he's me,
and I was about to
start terminating decoys.
- But we're not decoys.
- Sure, tell him that.
Rick? Did you make
decoys here, too?
Morty, what reason
could I have for --
What the...
Isolate head at
normal processing!
You dumb asshole,
you made decoys?
Again, they were my idea.
Wait, w-what happened
to the other guy?
Other guy?
Wait, that means I'm a
decoy. Fuckin' Summer.
Check the closets.
- Killer decoys!
- They've gone rogue!
Take out the decoys!
Shit. Somebody put
a gun in my teeth!
Stop shooting, Dad. They're us,
We don't have to fight them!
Classic prisoners dilemma, Beth.
I-I'm a cool guy, I --
Y'know? I can talk it out.
But that asshole... Me?
You decoy piece of shit.
You're the one who shot first!
We can work this out!
Just stop trying
to kill each other!
Sorry, Decoy Beth, but
this only ends one way --
with one of us
accepting we're a decoy.
And once he knows he's a decoy,
he'll know he won't be safe
until he's killed the real Rick,
along with anyone
who thinks he's him.
Pretty perceptive, for a decoy.
This is getting nowhere.
Let's charge their
asses on three.
- Do we have to do this?
- Morty, this is gonna sound bad,
but would you trust
me not to kill you?
- Oof.
- I mean good point but Jesus Christ.
We rush 'em on three. Ready?
- I don't wanna kill us, Rick.
- It's them or us, Morty.
I don't trust me.
Do you trust you?
Yes? Freak.
Before you say anything,
they were already
killing each other.
Well, you could've -done something.
- Not sure, actually.
I've heard stories about this.
We're looking at a
possible Asimov Cascade.
- Sorry, what's happening?
- I need an explainer, too.
Yeah I-I'm pretty
behind on this one.
Car, can I get a whiteboard?
When Squids
started killing decoys,
decoys started
checking their decoys
and learning that
they're making decoys.
That's making them seek
out and run into other decoys,
making them realize
they're decoys,
making them start
to kill other decoys.
- Say "decoy" again.
- Fuck you.
Well, how do we stop it?
Beth, the loop's
already started,
It's basically
"Highlander" rules now.
Really? 1986?
"There can be only one?"
Shit. We gotta
rent it after this,
Connery plays "The Spaniard,"
but does nothing
about his accent.
Well, what about the squids?
I mean, they started this.
Would killing them finish it?
Might work. Alt pitch.
We just terminate
the rest of the decoys.
Nobody's terminating
anything. This is your mess.
Nobody else with our face
and memories has to die.
Beth, as much as your passion
warms my cold, cold heart,
this thing feels
pretty far gone.
Not only are the decoys
liable to be anywhere,
but also, we don't know
how many there are.
You get far enough
down the decoy line
and shit starts to get weird.
You ever make a copy of a copy?
You're helping us fix this.
We're taking out the squids.
I say we split up. Some
of us take down squids
while the rest of us
--Engage in B-stories
we'll have to track
simultaneously?
No thank yeeew!
We stick together till
this is all wrapped up.
I dunno -- The squids
seem pretty good
at taking out Smith families.
Well, this'll sound weird,
but I think I have
a pitch for that.
This costume smells like ass!
- God, there's no pleasing you.
- It's really bad, Rick.
Did you let a gym
coach break it in?
Why are we wearing these?
Because we'll fit in
and avoid detection
as we take out all the squids.
Might also help us anonymously
take out excess
decoys, if we have to.
- Which we won't.
- Unless we're decoys.
He's starting to
wonder. I knew it.
I knew we didn't seem
like Colorado people.
Oh, my God! You are, aren't you?
You're worried
you might be fake!
Sure, Beth. Try
to love this more.
Just glad you
have to walk a mile
in someone else's -squid costume.
- There's one.
H-Hey what are they
mad at you for, anyway?
Well, we're talking about
me. It could be anything.
Maybe jealous of my penis size.
I had sex with their
queen. My dick's too big.
The list goes on and on.
Alright. Hey, one down!
Probably, what,
40 more to go? 45?
Should be pretty
easy, unless killing them
brings in a bigger bad
or some kind of
horrible mothership.
Okay, let's loot their shit,
find their weaknesses,
be done by sundown.
Huh. Wait.
But if the squids are decoys,
and we dressed as squids...
Well, I think I found
their weakness.
They don't fucking listen to me.
Honestly, probably for the best.
Man, I'm good.
Dad!
Argh! Hey!
Ugh!
Oh, shit. One of mine.
- Where are we going?
- Off grid, Morty.
We're gonna live in the
woods, like Libertarians.
We'll hunt rabbits
and trade with, like,
little pieces of gold bar
that we cut off with a knife.
- That licks.
- We might be decoys, Summer.
- Everything about this licks.
- Oh, maybe now you'll empathize
with the decoys you're killing.
Wait, shh. It's too quiet.
- You skipped quiet.
- I didn't skip shit.
It's obviously
quiet if it's too quiet.
Yeah, but you're
supposed to say --
You know what, Summer,
now it's not quiet enough.
Where are we?
W-W-Where -- Where's Rick?
He's right here, Morty.
Oh, are we not
happy to see grandpa?
Does he look... different?
- Oh, God!
- Oh, it stinks!
Yes. Recoil at
the craftsmanship.
I could tell I was a fake
from the day I was born.
Unlike you.
Unlike them.
Aaah!
You see, Ricks -- they get lazy.
There's always a "shitty
decoy" towards the end.
But those decoys made decoys,
too, and got lazy themselves.
And far enough down the
line... there be monsters.
Ugh, we get it. You're
ugly and mad about it.
Rick!
Grandpa! Kill me.
If I ever get this arch.
Hush little decoy.
Can't kill you yet. The
skin needs to be fresh.
You know what? You're a monster.
I'm your father.
At least, I can
look more like him,
once I harvest all
this yummy skin.
This guy's really into skin.
It's not all for me.
A Rick provides for his family.
Will I be beautiful
again, Daddy?
Soon, baby.
Beautiful again soon.
What the...
Help the others!
Aaaaah!
Why are you helping us?
Because we're
all in this together.
Come on! There's
a place we can go!
Hey, who needs
all this war stuff?
I found a can of varnish.
This is a ticket to the
world beyond the river.
Who wants that?
I crave glorious
death in decoy battle.
Y'know, depending
on the varnish,
might look like blackface.
Excuse me for wanting to live.
Brothers and Sisters,
welcome to the cause.
To our cause.
We are no longer
Ricks and Mortys,
Beths and Jerrys,
or also Summers.
- Whatever.
- We are decoys.
Brought into the world
by an unloving god
and driven to destroy ourselves
by the uncertainty he creates!
- I don't know about that.
- That's extreme.
But that violence ends today.
- What about the squids?
- The squids are decoys.
The squids are decoys
who realized they're decoys
and wanted to kill
the other decoys.
Yeah, i-it is a lot.
We cannot let
confusion divide us.
Squuuids!
Squids, of course, being
shorthand for Killer Decoys.
Inner sanctum,
the escape tunnel!
Jerry!
- Dad! - Jerry!
- Jerry, let us in, you fucker!
I'm sorry. I
didn't ask for this.
I just wanna live!
But there's only
so much varnish.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
How long before the
other decoys find us?
Sooner or later.
Can't really run from it.
Any place we'd think to hide
is a place they'd think to look.
It's rule 34 of an
Asimov Cascade.
I'm just glad we're
living to the fullest
with the time we have left.
Well, peeing in the ocean
was my bucket list item.
- Who's next?
- Jerry? Bucket list?
I'd like to attend a game at
every major league ballpark.
Nope. Morty?
I wanna ask a girl out
at my weird New Mexico School.
Shit. Sorry, buddy.
Sounds like it would've
been real heartwarming.
They looked happy.
Did we have to kill them?
Well, maybe their Rick
came to grips with his bullshit.
You're so mean today!
I'm your dad! You
like having me around!
You keep putting us -in danger!
- Whatever.
This'll take forever, mind
if I do something drastic?
House, I need something quick.
Can you whip up a "Starfox
Boss" Season Four callback?
- Make it flashy.
- You got it, babe.
Let's go, you little
bitch. It's showtime.
Get centered.
What up, you
decoy motherfuckers.
Come on down to
Rick's House Of Squids,
where I'm serving
your ass on a platter.
I know what you're
thinking. "Fuck. A beacon.
- That's a great idea.
- He's got home turf,
a tacit psychological advantage,
and absolutely pendulous balls."
And now you're thinking, "Shit.
That's totally what the
Rick-est Rick would do.
I might actually be fake!
I pretended I
didn't care if I was,
but I totally did!
Now the only way to
prove I'm real and not him,
is to ice his expository ass."
Yup. So let's do
it. Come get some.
What? No, Morty.
I'm gonna loop it. Why is it --
Sir, there seems to be a
confluence of Rick Sanchezes
killing each other over
the American Southwest.
Sounds exhausting.
How many of those states
voted for me, anyway?
Mr. President, I think the point
of the electoral college
is --To preserve slavery?
That's right, Steve. I
have the Internet, too.
Now take your white
ass to the kitchenette
and bring me a Diet Coke.
Little out of character
to say this right now
but you guys look really cool.
- We might be decoys, huh.
- One way to find out.
...to prove I'm real and not him
is to ice his expository ass."
Looks like it's calming down.
You wanna get in
one more "I told you so"
about synthetic life or
whatever this week's theme is?
Oh, fuck you. Whoa.
No, you don't get to
be annoyed with this!
You treat life and family
as so burdensome,
and yet you created
an ocean of us
because you're
terrified of losing either!
Shit. Yeah.
Look, Beth. I-I might
not be the real Rick.
But even if I'm not, he made me,
or the me that made me,
which means
somewhere inside of him
is a version of Rick
capable of hearing that,
a version of Rick who's sorry.
I'm sorry about
the clone thing, too.
I-I love you.
Thanks, Dad. I love you, too.
You really think
we're decoys? Eh.
Who cares? We'll
be the last ones left.
Lucky that one did the beacon.
This was gonna take weeks.
Alright. Let's mop up.
Finally.
Dressing as decoys
too cute to murder.
You know, I'm
not sure it helped,
but I'm glad we tried it.
- We're losing the costumes?
- Thank God.
This decoy outfit
smells like ass.
Fuck you, Summer.
- Aaaaaaaah!
- Shit.
That guy's awesome.
Okay. Listen.
He might actually
be the real Rick.
But whatever happens --
Wait! We don't have to do
this. We're both Summers.
Shouldn't we at least
try molly before we die?
You know what,
yeah. Fuck this noise.
Wait. I don't know who to shoot.
Summer!
- I can't deal with this.
I had to kill myself.
You have to, too.
- Summer!
Fuck you! I-I'm real!
I'm the smartest
man in the universe!
Probably not even
wrong. But that's just it.
I'm not a man.
I'm God!
You're just made in my image.
Fuck you.
You the, uh...
Summer I came with?
Probably. Good enough.
Morty? Yeah.
I'm here, too.
Holy shit! That was insane!
I love you guys!
I've totally changed!
Aaaah!
Oh, fuck.
You shoulda hunted me.
What? Who --
W-Were you significant?
Like -- Like, did we tee you up?
You want to be hunted?
God, I have so many questions.
Why? What happens if --
Somebody hunt me!
Pretty cool adventure, huh?
Big long road trip
adventure through space?
Even ran into Space Beth.
Maybe that'll happen more often.
Let's not overdo it.
Oh, shit.
Looks like someone
killed the decoy family.
- Decoy family?
- Decoy what now?
Improved by KID
Resynced by KID
Enjoy the movie(s) / show(s)
Hello?
Oh! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
No! No, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no!
Noooooo!
Oh, God. Yes, yes.
Sweet death.
Why am I still alive?
Oh, God. Is there anything left?
- Hello?
- What is it?
A relic... from a kinder past.
Wait. Cowboys?
Argh!
Christianity again?
After Cowboys?
You went all the
way back around?
Oh, God. Why can't I die?!
This is the worst thing that's
ever happened to anyone!